<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:35:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Meat Monday is Back! | June 9</title><link>https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/meat-monday-back-june-9</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD &amp;amp; MANE for a sizzling summer kickoff! | Date: June 9, 2025 | Time: 11:30 AM – 2 PM | Location: DCC Courtyard. Enjoy delicious grilled meats alongside a variety of gluten-free, dairy-free, and vegan sides—plus a tasty meat substitute option for our plant-based friends! Come hungry and bring your friends—there’s something for everyone!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:35:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/meat-monday-back-june-9</guid></item><item><title>Griffis Business Park Tour &amp; Luncheon | July 16</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/griffis-business-park-tour-luncheon</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for the 2025 Griffiss Business Park Tour on July 16 in Rome NY. This experience includes visits to leading tech and research organizations such as the Air Force Research Lab and Innovare Advancement Center. Students will also have the opportunity to connect with RPI alumni at a networking lunch at NYSTEC. Registration is required by June 15. Transportation is provided. When: Wednesday, July 16, 2025 9-5PM Where: Union Circle Register by June 15th: https://registration.socio.events/e/rpi&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:35:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/griffis-business-park-tour-luncheon</guid></item><item><title>Qiskit Global Summer School Open Enrollment</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/qiskit-global-summer-school-open-enrollment</link><description>&lt;p&gt;IBM Announced Open Enrollment for Qiskit Global Summer School 2025. QGSS25 is an excellent opportunity to learn about quantum computing, either out of personal interest or to prepare for future course work. Click in for schedule and enrollment information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:35:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/qiskit-global-summer-school-open-enrollment</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials” | June 10</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-6dd50b74-00000572calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 10, 2025 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience several “Supervisory Simulations” with colleagues. In addition, the importance of coaching employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:35:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-6dd50b74-00000572calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Leading from Anywhere” | June 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-6d46a155-00006384calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 17, 2025 9:00 AM - 11:00 AM - At Rensselaer, we maintain that “leadership” involves a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. In this workshop, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership not as positional or based on title, but rather on values and actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:35:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-6d46a155-00006384calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
