<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>2025 Student Climate Survey Launched</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-student-climate-survey-launched</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2025 Student Climate Survey launched by email on March 31, 2025. Your honest opinions about campus life—how it impacts your ability to learn and grow, both academically and personally—are important. You will find your personal link to complete the survey in your email from President Schmidt. Our goal is to achieve at least a 50% response rate this year. Please submit the completely anonymous survey by April 25, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-student-climate-survey-launched</guid></item><item><title>Do you know RPI’s Mission and Goals?</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/do-you-know-rpis-mission-and-goals</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know our new Rensselaer Forward Plan carries forward our founder’s mission: to instruct “persons who may choose to apply themselves in the application of science to the common purposes of life”? The mission, vision, and core values of RPI are outlined alongside the former Rensselaer Plan 2024 and the new Rensselaer Forward Plan. For more details, dive into Standard 1 of RPI’s Self-Study for Middle States Accreditation, a team led by Dr. Lee Ligon and Ms. Colleen Smith.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/do-you-know-rpis-mission-and-goals</guid></item><item><title>Math Colloquium &amp; Annual SIAM Seminar: Angel Pineda (Hofstra University) | April 4</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-b48e460f-0000198dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, April 4, 2025 12:30 PM - 1:30 PM - This Mathematical Sciences Colloquium and Annual SIAM Seminar will feature a presentation titled “Qrtificial Intelligence in Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI): Using Mathematical Modeling, Statistics and Human Observer Experiments to Improve Image Quality” by Dr. Angel Pineda , Professor of Mathematics at Hofstra University&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-b48e460f-0000198dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Out of the Darkness Suicide Prevention Walk | April 6</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-c9a8b3d9-0000400ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Sunday, April 6, 2025 11:00 AM - 1:00 PM - RPI Circle K, in collaboration with the American Foundation for Suicide Prevention, is hosting our third annual Out of the Darkness Suicide Prevention Walk: April 6th on the ’86 Field from 11:00 AM to 1:00 PM. Tabling, registration, raffles, entertainment, and more beginning at 10:00 AM. This event aims to raise awareness about suicide prevention and mental health, bringing these critical topics to the forefront of RPI’s campus and the Troy community.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-c9a8b3d9-0000400ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CBE Seminar Series Continues with Dr. Rajesh Khare | April 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-c988cc9a-0000465fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 2, 2025 9:30 AM - 10:30 AM - The CBE Seminar Series continues with Dr. Rajesh Khare, Professor and Whitacre Department Chair of the Department of Chemical Engineering at Texas Tech. Dr. Khare’s seminar, titled “From Molecules to Rheology: A Journey across Length and Time Scales” is open to all. Refreshments will be available at 9:00 a.m. in the Ricketts’ Coonley Lounge (RI 120).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-c988cc9a-0000465fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Future of Computing Institute (FOCI) Sneak Preview: Project Chapel film by Chris Groban |April 2 (Please RSVP)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-d8d04edf-00000a5ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, April 2, 2025 6:30 PM - FOCI invites the campus community to an exclusive sneak preview of Project Chapel, the new film by acclaimed director Chris Groban. Project Chapel follows the historic, world-first installation of a quantum computer inside RPI’s very own VCC chapel. &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/rsvp-project-chapel-film-chris-groban-sneak-preview"&gt;Please RSVP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-d8d04edf-00000a5ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Advanced Digital Imaging Spring Exhibition Opening Reception to be held April 8</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/echoes-process-advanced-digital-imaging-spring-2025-exhibition</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The opening reception of Advanced Digital Imaging Spring 2025 Exhibition is on Tuesday April 8, 6 to 7pm in SAGE Lab 5th floor Dean’s Gallery. The exhibition consists of works-in-progress and short study projects created in class in response to studies in gesture, emotion, the human body, virtual and augmented realities, and expanded notions of perception and time. Included in the exhibition are multimedia, photography, archival digital and hand drawn works on paper, canvas, and other materials.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/echoes-process-advanced-digital-imaging-spring-2025-exhibition</guid></item><item><title>“Create Reproducible R Environments with renv!” RPIrates Monthly Meeting (Weds, 02 Apr, 6p, AE217)</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/create-reproducible-r-environments-renv-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-02-apr-6p-ae217</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI R users are invited to the April 2025 meeting of RPIrates: The RPI R Users Group! Our topic for Weds, 02 Apr (6p, AE217) will be “Create Reproducible R Environments with renv!,” led by Dr. John S. Erickson, Director of Research Operations of the Future of Computing Institute (FOCI) at Rensselaer and Chief Instigator of RPIrates. In this session we’ll learn how R’s renv package can be used to create reproducible R environments that are more isolated, portable and reproducible.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/create-reproducible-r-environments-renv-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-02-apr-6p-ae217</guid></item><item><title>Student Health Services Releases Updated Gender Affirming Care Support Directory</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-gender-affirming-care-support-directory</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In honor of Transgender Day of Visibility (March 31, 2025), Rensselaer’s Student Health Services releases an updated Gender Affirming Care Support Directory: https://adobe.ly/4kWNEXj&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-gender-affirming-care-support-directory</guid></item><item><title>Math Colloquium: Yunan Yang presents “Transport- and Measure-Theoretic Approaches for Dynamical System Modeling” | April 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-4306678a-000024a8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 2, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM Green Building Rm. 10- This Mathematical Sciences Colloquium will feature a presentation titled “Transport- and Measure-Theoretic Approaches for Dynamical System Modeling” by Dr. Yunan Yang, Assistant Professor in the Department of Mathematics at Cornell University.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-4306678a-000024a8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Information Session | April 4</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-a48c0757-00001391calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, April 4, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., will be reviewing the online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates. Expect to hear details about how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment. Please RSVP below if you plan to attend and learn more about Rensselaer at Work.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-a48c0757-00001391calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Do you know RPI’s Student Handbook?</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/do-you-know-rpis-student-handbook</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that for RPI students, the Student Handbook and Graduate Student Supplement outline academic and disciplinary policies? For faculty and staff, these are detailed in the Human Resources Policy Guidelines and the Faculty Handbook. For more information, explore Standard 2 of RPI’s Self-Study for Middle States Accreditation: Ethics and Integrity, a team led by Dr. Dorit Nevo.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/do-you-know-rpis-student-handbook</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff In Person Workshop - Reviewing Supported Polling Tools On Campus for Courses or Meetings | April 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-c8f3f556-00002a88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, April 7, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - In this workshop we will take time to look at a couple polling software tools that are available and supported on campus and discuss the differences. The tools we will be discussing include iClicker and Slido. We will also take a quick look at the free version of Kahoot! (not supported on campus with license but fun!). Please register for this workshop by April 4th as space is limited. Please look in the See section for the registration link and more details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-c8f3f556-00002a88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Call for Faculty Reflective Pedagogy Fellows – Applications due April 11th</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/call-faculty-reflective-pedagogy-fellows-applications-due-april-11th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Inquiry-based learning and creativity are key elements toward creating engaged learning. The Gameful and Immersive Learning Teams invite interested faculty to apply to redesign one of their courses (or a course element). Following the successful spring 2024 Innovative Pedagogy Fellows initiative, the Office of Undergraduate Education is capitalizing on this momentum by funding a professional development opportunity for a new cohort of fellows in 2025, the Reflective Pedagogy Fellows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/call-faculty-reflective-pedagogy-fellows-applications-due-april-11th</guid></item></channel></rss>
