<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>DotCIO Announces Next Phase of AFS Retirement</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-announces-next-phase-afs-retirement</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As previously announced, Andrew File System (AFS), a legacy file storage system, needs to be retired to maintain an acceptable cybersecurity posture for the Institute. The service will be retired in stages and sunsetting completely in September 2024. Among affected services, AFS housed all content for homepages.rpi.edu and dept.rpi.edu. The next stage of this process, access to departmental and personal AFS space (homepages/dept), will be discontinued on June 5, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-announces-next-phase-afs-retirement</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Session to Review Supply Chain, Lean Six Sigma, Systems Engineering</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348fcc01-00001031calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, May 29, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/SCCT29"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D. as he highlights Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in areas surrounding Supply Chain and Logistics, Systems Engineering, and Lean Quality. Attendees can expect to learn how these graduate certificates were created in consultation with enterprises that recognize the opportunity and risks of a global supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348fcc01-00001031calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Cuthand to Lead “Be the Media!” Participatory Radio Workshop</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-018f-82b228d2-00004237calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 30, 2024 5:00 PM - 9:00 PM - In a second event co-presented by iEAR Presents and the EMPAC curatorial program, Theo Jean Cuthand will lead a participatory radio workshop at The Sanctuary for Independent Media in Troy, to be followed by a talk and screening with an emphasis on his methods of film and game production and a particular focus on Indigiqueer and ecological issues. Please &lt;a href="https://www.mediasanctuary.org/event/theo-jean-cuthand/"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-018f-82b228d2-00004237calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Men’s and Women’s Track &amp; Field, Men’s Tennis to be Represented at NCAA Championships</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/5/21/general-mens-and-womens-track-field-and-mens-tennis-represented-at-weekend-ncaa-championships.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Five student-athletes from the Rensselaer men’s and women’s track and field teams, as well as two individuals from the Engineer’s men’s tennis program, will represent RPI in NCAA Division III Championships this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/5/21/general-mens-and-womens-track-field-and-mens-tennis-represented-at-weekend-ncaa-championships.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Four Engineers Ink Professional Contracts</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/5/22/womens-ice-hockey-four-engineers-ink-professional-contracts.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Four members of the Rensselaer women’s ice hockey team have each signed professional contracts in a ceremony inside Houston Fieldhouse: Asiah Taylor-Walters is headed to Hungary to play for MAC Budapest, Isabelle Hardy has signed on with the EC Graz Huskies, and Taylor Zahirnyi and Meagan Byrum will both be joining the DEC Salzburg Eagles.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/5/22/womens-ice-hockey-four-engineers-ink-professional-contracts.aspx</guid></item><item><title>HR Accepting Forms for Public Service Loan Forgiveness (PSLF) Program</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/public-service-loan-forgiveness-pslf-program</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Division of Human Resources is now accepting completed forms from members of the campus community who require employment verification for the federal Public Service Loan Forgiveness (PSLF) Program. Please &lt;a href="mailto:hrmail@rpi.edu."&gt;direct questions&lt;/a&gt; to Human Resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/public-service-loan-forgiveness-pslf-program</guid></item><item><title>SoS to Host Field Trip to American Museum of Natural History</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7de715e1-00003404calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 11, 2024 6:45 AM - 6:45 PM - The School of Science will host an academic field trip to the American Museum of Natural History. This opportunity is open to all Arch students but registration is due by May 27; to sign up, please send &lt;a href="mailto:getwrk@rpi.edu"&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; to the School of Science.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7de715e1-00003404calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Reminder to Faculty: Update and Publish Summer Term Course Syllabi in HelioCampus</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/reminder-faculty-update-and-publish-summer-term-course-syllabi-heliocampus</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of the Provost reminds all faculty that they are required to enter and publish their syllabi two weeks after the semester begins; for the summer 2024 semester, that deadline date is June 3. HelioCampus will publish the syllabi automatically on June 10. Those needing help with entering and/or publishing their syllabi can get in-person assistance at 3:00PM on Wednesday, May 29 in Sage 2313; for assistance at other times, &lt;a href="mailto:svirsa2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Amy Svirsky&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/reminder-faculty-update-and-publish-summer-term-course-syllabi-heliocampus</guid></item></channel></rss>
