<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>If you could go anywhere in the world, where would you go? Fulbright Information session</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-dd13fc45-0000622fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 4, 2026 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Students interested in doing graduate level research, seeking a degree, or teaching English for a year abroad, should attend this information session on the Fulbright U.S. Student program. Students that will have a bachelors degree by fall 2027 and are U.S. citizens are encouraged to attend. Many Master’s and PhD students conduct research abroad for their U.S. degree program. Register: https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV_6L3FFwv0qCROrvE For…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-dd13fc45-0000622fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Become an I-PERSIST Mentor for Fall 2026 – apply by January 30!</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/become-i-persist-mentor-fall-2026-apply-january-30</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in becoming a mentor to new students in Calculus, Physics, or Chemistry? Apply to become an I-PERSIST mentor today! Share your subject knowledge, gain leadership skills, connect with faculty, and help new students adjust to RPI! Our application for Fall 2026 closes on January 30, so don’t wait. Click to view the application!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/become-i-persist-mentor-fall-2026-apply-january-30</guid></item><item><title>Webinar on Friday January 30: RPI Digital Asset Management (DAM) System</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-rpi-digital-asset-management-dam-system-1</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Jim Evans, Director of MultiMedia Services, on Friday January 30 from 11am to 12pm, for a live webinar introducing Rensselaer’s Digital Asset Management System. Discover how to access campus‑wide photography, multimedia files, and institutional assets—all in one place. Register now: https://rensselaer.webex.com/webappng/sites/rensselaer/webinar/webinarSeries/register/783d951c6ab8482e9198a7bd6075a700&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-rpi-digital-asset-management-dam-system-1</guid></item><item><title>Parking enforcement begins January 26, 2026</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/parking-enforcement-begins-january-26-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A variety of parking permit options are available to meet the needs of students, faculty, and staff. Please review the parking policies and make sure your vehicle information is up to date. If you have questions or need help getting a permit, contact Parking at parking@rpi.edu or 518-276-8528.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/parking-enforcement-begins-january-26-2026</guid></item><item><title>RPI Libraries: Guided Group Tours</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-guided-group-tours</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Guided library tours are now available for students, faculty, staff, and campus groups at both the Folsom Library and the Architecture Library. These brief, bookable tours introduce library spaces, services, and resources, and can be customized to fit your group’s needs or research interests…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-guided-group-tours</guid></item><item><title>Campus Community Invited to ISC2 Cybersecurity Chapter Meetup | Jan 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-e5ab4d34-00007b59calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, January 27, 2026 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - All are welcome to join an upcoming ISC2 Capital District NY chapter meeting for a cybersecurity briefing from the FBI, including active and emerging threats, trends in ransomware, and latest in data breaches. Open to the RPI community!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-e5ab4d34-00007b59calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Watch PBS’s NOVA documentary featuring RPI professor Karyn Rogers and grad student Meri Herrero</title><link>https://rare.rpi.edu/announcements/rare-research-featured-upcoming-pbs-nova-documentary</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The astrobiology research of Karyn Rogers, Ph.D., director of the Rensselaer Astrobiology Research and Education Center, and RPI graduate student Meri Herrero are featured in PBS’s 1st NOVA documentary of the season, “Asteroids: Spark of Life?” If you missed it on PBS, watch online at &lt;a class="uri" href="https://to.pbs.org/3LJjnhM"&gt;https://to.pbs.org/3LJjnhM&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rare.rpi.edu/announcements/rare-research-featured-upcoming-pbs-nova-documentary</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: Supervisory Essentials</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience a “day in the life” of a Supervisor. In addition, the importance of managing employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team capacity will be explored.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-3</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: Steps to Effective Communication: Extended DISC; February 3, 2026</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-4-steps-effective-2</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, February 3, 2026 9:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Our success, both personally and professionally, is largely determined by our ability to communicate effectively with a variety of people. The Extended DISC system is based on behavioral theories that have been used for over one hundred years. In this workshop, participants will receive individualized Extended DISC reports (based on the completion of the Extended DISC questionnaire) that reflect both their “natural” and “adjusted” behavioral…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-4-steps-effective-2</guid></item></channel></rss>
