<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Don’t Miss the Arch’s End-of-Summer Block Party!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0190-f06647a3-00006c2fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, August 7, 2024 4:30 PM - 10:30 PM - Students are welcome to join The Arch Office as it celebrates the end of the Arch summer term! The event will feature Bicentennial Ice Cream, BBQ ribs, a pizza truck, giveaways, live music, games and activities, and an outdoor movie screening, so don’t miss the fun!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0190-f06647a3-00006c2fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rob Hradsky Named Vice Provost of Student Experience</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/29/rob-hradsky-named-vice-provost-student-experience-rpi</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rob Hradsky, Ed.D., has been named Rensselaer’s Vice Provost of Student Experience, and will join RPI in mid-August. Currently Vice President for Student Engagement at Syracuse University, Hradsky is recognized by a number of professional organizations and is known nationally for his work helping students succeed and flourish during their college experience. His professional experience includes student affairs, academics, and higher education leadership.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/29/rob-hradsky-named-vice-provost-student-experience-rpi</guid></item><item><title>Administration Division: Roof Replacements Scheduled for Summer Months</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/administration/06/06/2024/roof-replacements-materials-research-center-mrc-empire-state-hall-esh-and</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All members of the campus community should note that roof replacements are scheduled for the Materials Research Center (MRC), Empire State Hall (ESH), and the west wing of the Jonsson Rowland Science Center (JRSC). Construction will begin on Monday, June 17 and be completed by Friday, August 9, with tentative daily work hours set for 6:00AM to 2:30PM, Monday through Friday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/administration/06/06/2024/roof-replacements-materials-research-center-mrc-empire-state-hall-esh-and</guid></item><item><title>RAA to Sponsor “College Discovery” Webinar September 11</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10016&amp;cid=22964&amp;ecid=22964&amp;ciid=79674&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with RPI’s Offices of Alumni Engagement and Enrollment Management, the Rensselaer Alumni Association will present a “College Discovery” webinar from 7:00PM to 8:30PM on Wednesday, September 11, covering a range of important topics for alumni who are preparing their children for the college selection, recruitment, and admissions process.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10016&amp;cid=22964&amp;ecid=22964&amp;ciid=79674&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Joint ECSE/COGS Seminar to be Held August 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0190-ff0e72e7-00002b8fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, August 5, 2024 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Join ECSE and COGS for a seminar titled “Transforming General-Purpose Robots into Trusted Teammates with HARMONIC,” with Dr. Sanjay Oruganti, Post-doctoral Researcher in the Language-Endowed Intelligent Agents (LEIA) Lab in Rensselaer’s Cognitive Science Department.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0190-ff0e72e7-00002b8fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI Autism Researcher Juergen Hahn Elected to European Academy of Sciences and Arts</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/29/rpi-autism-researcher-juergen-hahn-elected-european-academy-sciences-and-arts</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Juergen Hahn, Ph.D., professor and head of Rensselaer’s Department of Biomedical Engineering, has been elected to the prestigious European Academy of Sciences and Arts for his outstanding and sustained impact on science and society. Hahn, who will be formally inducted into the organization in 2025, is the first RPI faculty member to be elected to this academy, an international organization of top scientists, artists, and decision makers that includes 38 Nobel laureates.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/29/rpi-autism-researcher-juergen-hahn-elected-european-academy-sciences-and-arts</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Hold Lean Six Sigma Info Session</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-03d705d2-00007b21calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, August 9, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/LXCT9"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews RPI’s online, project-based graduate certificates and degrees, highlighting the Lean Six Sigma Certificate. Expect to hear details about how completion of the certificate results in an LSS Yellow Belt and Green Belt, and also about RPI Instructor Mentors, who provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-03d705d2-00007b21calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Five Engineers Announced As Cobalt All-American Scholars</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/7/30/mens-golf-five-engineers-announced-as-cobalt-all-american-scholars-by-golf-coaches-association-of-america.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Golf Coaches Association of America has named Matt Buckley, Owen Himmer, Ryan Komp, Jacob Lindsay, and Rodrigo Muelas of the Rensselaer golf team as 2023-24 Cobalt Golf Division III All-America Scholars. To be eligible, a nominee must be a sophomore, junior, or senior both academically and athletically in NCAA Division I, II, III, and NAIA; take part in 50% of their team’s competitive rounds; post with a certain per-round stroke average; and maintain a minimum cumulative career GPA of 3.20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/7/30/mens-golf-five-engineers-announced-as-cobalt-all-american-scholars-by-golf-coaches-association-of-america.aspx</guid></item></channel></rss>
