<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Outdoor Professional Headshots with the CCPD | June 18</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/outdoor-professional-headshots-ccpd-june-18</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a student looking to update your professional profile or need a fresh headshot? Join the CCPD for outdoor headshot session on Wednesday, June 18th 2025 between 1 - 2PM! Don’t miss this opportunity to get a polished, professional photo taken in a beautiful outdoor setting.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/outdoor-professional-headshots-ccpd-june-18</guid></item><item><title>Graduate Summer Lunch &amp; Learn-Writing Research and Teaching Statements for Academic Careers- Registration Required | June 18</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-600aa591-0000690dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 18, 2025 12:00 PM - 2:30 PM - Writing Research and Teaching Statements for Academic Careers- Research and teaching statements are core components of the academic job application. In this lunch and learn, we will break down their key elements and offer strategies for translating your work and vision into compelling narratives. We’ll discuss how to tailor your statements to different institutions and articulate impact. Ideal for graduate students and postdocs preparing for…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-600aa591-0000690dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Virtual Summer Series: Western Digital | June 17</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-virtual-summer-series-western-digital-june-17</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The CCPD’s virtual summer series is wrapping up! Join Western Digital for a virtual session on Tuesday, June 17th, 2025 to discuss life at the company, as well as learning about available co-ops and internships during the 2025-2026 academic year! More information can be found in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-virtual-summer-series-western-digital-june-17</guid></item><item><title>Join the Rensselaer Consulting Club This Summer</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/join-rensselaer-consulting-club-summer</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking to gain real-world consulting experience this summer? Join the Rensselaer Consulting Club (RCC). Open to all undergrads, RCC offers hands-on projects in AI for small businesses and immigrant-led entrepreneurship. Build your resume, work with real clients, and make a local impact. No prior consulting experience needed. Just curiosity, commitment., flexible and collaborative. Interested? Contact Dr. Kevin Fletcher at fletck3@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/join-rensselaer-consulting-club-summer</guid></item><item><title>Volunteer with Sidewalk Warriors | July 3</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/volunteer-sidewalk-warriors-july-3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Take time to give back during your summer break! Join the CCPD and engage with the local community as we volunteer with Sidewalk Warriors on Thursday, July 3rd from 4:30-8pm. Register and learn more in Handshake and reach out to Dean Burke, burked5@rpi.edu, with questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/volunteer-sidewalk-warriors-july-3</guid></item><item><title>STEM Outreach Survey For Parents</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0197-5a5944aa-000009becalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 10, 2025 12:00 AM - Mon , June 16, 2025 12:00 AM - Are you a parent of a K-12 student? The RPI Engineering Outreach Program is looking to better understand how families engage with STEM and how we can improve access and support. This short, anonymous, survey (about 5 minutes) will help. Your input is greatly appreciated! If you have multiple children, please enter one form per child. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0197-5a5944aa-000009becalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Playwriting Workshop with Alyssa Haddad-Chin | June 23</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/playwriting-workshop-alyssa-haddad-chin</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join award-winning NYC playwright Alyssa Haddad-Chin and for an Arch Summer Workshop. Write a ten-minute play suitable for the stage and adaptable for the screen. Monday, June 23rd from 4-7pm in Sage Lab 4101.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/playwriting-workshop-alyssa-haddad-chin</guid></item><item><title>2025 RAA Annual Meeting (Virtual) | June 17</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10629&amp;cid=23967&amp;ecid=23967&amp;ciid=82661&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: 6/17/2025 7:00 PM to 8:00 PM The Rensselaer Alumni Association (RAA) will hold its annual meeting and election on Tuesday, June 17 at 7 p.m. Eastern Time. Once again, the annual meeting will be held in a virtual format. During the meeting, the RAA will share a recap of the last year, discuss plans for the upcoming year, and review the 2025 Board member slate and bylaw amendments.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10629&amp;cid=23967&amp;ecid=23967&amp;ciid=82661&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>2025 National Organic Chemistry Symposium (NOS) June 22-26</title><link>https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-national-organic-chemistry-symposium</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 49th NOS will be held June 22–26, at RPI! Sponsored by the ACS Division of Organic Chemistry, this 100th-anniversary event is expected to welcome over 450 participants from across the United States &amp;amp; around the world. It will feature top speakers highlighting advances in synthesis, biocatalysis, polymers, and drug discovery. Nobel Laureate Dr. Morton Medhal will give the keynote. The program also includes poster sessions and career panels. More info: https://www.nationalorganicsymposium.org/&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-national-organic-chemistry-symposium</guid></item><item><title>Standing on the Shoulders of Heroes Pride Exhibit | June 16-July 13</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0197-6a188862-00005986calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, June 16, 2025 - Sun , July 13, 2025 (all day) - In celebration of Pride Month, the LGBTQ+ Task Force presents an exhibit celebrating heroes who have stood tall in the face of injustice. Please visit these posters on the main floor of Folsom Library. Each one shares the story of people who have risked much to speak for others. Exhibit courtesy of Stonewall National Museum and Archives and thanks to the generosity of Jason Hagopian ’91, ’92, the Rensselaer Alumni Association and the…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0197-6a188862-00005986calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>No Pressure, Just Pride: LGBTQ+ Mixer | June 18</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/no-pressure-just-pride-lgbtq-mixer-june-18</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Celebrate Pride Month with the CCPD! On Wednesday, June 18th from 5-7pm, students, faculty, and staff who identify as LGBTQ+ or allies are invited to a low-stakes mixer in Sage Banquet Hall. Participants will get to know each other in a relaxed environment and learn about resources on- and off-campus. Hors d’oeuvres and refreshments will be served and the CCPD’s Clothing Closet will be available. Come as you are and join us for a night of community and joy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/no-pressure-just-pride-lgbtq-mixer-june-18</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Information Session with Rensselaer at Work | June 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-364095fc-00001dd5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 17, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join Rensselaer Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-364095fc-00001dd5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>The Division of Human Resources is relocating!</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-relocating</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Division of Human Resources is relocating from the Gurley Building (21 Union Street, 2nd Floor) to our new home in the Chasan Building (405 Broadway, 1st Floor) on June 16, 2025. While our physical location is changing, all phone numbers and email addresses will remain the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-relocating</guid></item></channel></rss>
