<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Postponed - Frosty February Fling</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-6cbfecf9-00006809calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 18, 2026 3:00 PM - 5:00 PM - The Civil &amp;amp; Environmental event scheduled for 2-18 at 3:00 PM has been postponed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-6cbfecf9-00006809calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>What’s Next After Graduation? Explore Your Options.</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/whats-next-after-graduation-explore-your-options</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Considering a coterminal or accelerated master’s degree? Join the Lally School of Management and invited RPI graduate program representatives on Wednesday, February 25 from 12:00–1:00 p.m. in PITTS 5114 to learn more about graduate programs, how coterminal pathways work, and what funding opportunities may be available. All RPI students are welcome. Pizza will be provided. Register using the link on our website.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/whats-next-after-graduation-explore-your-options</guid></item><item><title>Schmidt Science Fellowship Seeking Applicants for Prestigious Post-doctoral Fellowship</title><link>https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/schmidt-science-fellowship-seeking-candidates-2-year-post-doctoral-opportunity</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fellows receive $110K per year for two years, are placed at an internationally prestigious lab, and are mentored by world leaders in science and industry. PhD students graduating between May 2026 and June 2027 who are interested in developing skills in a discipline different than their own should contact Betty Madigan, madige@rpi.edu, by April 10th for information on the internal selection process. A committee will select 2 nominees to be submitted in May. Questions? madige@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/schmidt-science-fellowship-seeking-candidates-2-year-post-doctoral-opportunity</guid></item><item><title>Apartment Search 101 Workshops</title><link>https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/apartment-search-101-workshops</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Off-Campus Services Office will be holding workshops to learn about the process, resources available, and important considerations in selecting your housing. 2/19 2:30-4:30 p.m. RU3602 2/20 2:30-3:30 p.m. RU3202 2/25 2:30-4:30 p.m. 1525 15th St Questions, please email offcampus@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/apartment-search-101-workshops</guid></item><item><title>Milan Olympics Watch Party</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-6de62d42-00001d5acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, February 19, 2026 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - Whether you’re a sports enthusiast or just looking for a lively community event, join us at the Milan Olympics Watch Party to witness the world’s best compete in the Winter Olympics! This event is Thursday, February 19 in the Union Theater from 8:30 a.m. to 4:00 p.m. (EST). Hosted by International Services for Students and Scholars (ISSS), the Rensselaer Union, and RecWell.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-6de62d42-00001d5acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Webinar Friday February 20: Webex Application Training</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-february-20-webex-application-training</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on Friday, February 20, from 11am-12pm for a hands-on Webex Training Session, part of the MMS Collaboration Software Training series. This session focuses on the Webex application and its integration with Outlook and Blackboard, so you can efficiently schedule, launch, and manage meetings directly from the tools you use every day. Register now: https://rensselaer.webex.com/webappng/sites/rensselaer/webinar/webinarSeries/register/783d951c6ab8482e9198a7bd6075a700&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-february-20-webex-application-training</guid></item><item><title>Kipu Quantum Iskay Optimizer — Onboarding Workshop for RPI Students and Researchers</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/kipu-quantum-iskay-optimizer-onboarding-workshop-rpi-students-and-researchers</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI is in the process of onboarding Kipu Quantum Iskay Optimizer. The solver will be available via the IBM Quantum Qiskit Catalogue in the near future. To help you you with Iskay Optimizer you are invited to a concise, high-impact onboarding workshop to be held: Wednesday, February 18th at 9:30 AM in CII 3206. If your work involves optimization, scheduling, routing, portfolio design, materials discovery, or related areas, this session is for you. Please click in for more details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/kipu-quantum-iskay-optimizer-onboarding-workshop-rpi-students-and-researchers</guid></item><item><title>Mercer X Project Management Q&amp;A Seminar and Hands-on Workshop with Monica Johns (TTM Technologies)</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-x-project-management-qa-seminar-and-hands-workshop-monica-johns-ttm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come to our Mercer X Scrum/Agile Project Management Q&amp;amp;A Session (Friday, February 20th) and/or Hands-on Workshop (Saturday, February 21st) with Monica Johns (TTM Technologies)! We have Sticky notes, Poster paper, a Mercer XLab dynamic workspace, and a veteran project management professional to help organize your projects. Join us for an engaging, hands-on workshop designed to introduce (or deepen) your understanding of Scrum and Agile methodologies from Project Management. BYOP!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-x-project-management-qa-seminar-and-hands-workshop-monica-johns-ttm</guid></item><item><title>Teaching and Learning Collaboratory Faculty Call for Proposals: Submissions due March 9, 2026</title><link>https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory-faculty-call-proposals-submissions-due-march-9</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The OUE and the TLC invites proposals from full time tenure track faculty members or lecturers/Professors of Practice for piloting and assessing pedagogical innovations, especially those integrating interactive technologies into the classroom. We wish to fund seed projects that will serve as the foundation for external grant applications. Project proposals should entail the implementation of new interactive approaches, gaming, remote laboratories, or other innovative methods.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory-faculty-call-proposals-submissions-due-march-9</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff In Person Workshop - Beta Classroom - Teaching with Technology Preview</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c22e423-019c-5378f164-0000229bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 4, 2026 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Come see the Collaboratory space in the main library, and the exciting technologies available to you in the Beta Classroom. The beta classroom is a high technology testing space for interactive learning. The goal of the beta classroom is for faculty to pilot new or interactive technologies and pedagogical approaches that can be recommended for other classrooms on campus. This is also the February 27th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c22e423-019c-5378f164-0000229bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
