<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:32:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Study Abroad Applications Now Being Accepted for Spring 2025</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of International Programs’ &lt;a href="https://rpi-sa.terradotta.com/index.cfm?FuseAction=Abroad.Home"&gt;application portal&lt;/a&gt; is now open to undergraduate students who wish to apply for spring 2025 study abroad. Deadlines, contact info, and application guidelines are available via the &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025"&gt;International Programs website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</guid></item><item><title>Book Your COMM+D Appointment Online!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/08/20/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you working on a writing assignment, oral presentation, or visual design project? Whether you’re at the beginning brainstorming stages or finishing up your final revisions, the Center for Global Communication+Design (Comm+D) can help! Just &lt;a href="https://rpi.mywconline.com/"&gt;schedule an appointment&lt;/a&gt; with a member of our trained staff, then stop by the Comm+D offices on the lower level of Folsom Library.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/08/20/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</guid></item><item><title>Discounted Adobe Creative Cloud Subscriptions Available for Students</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/adobe-creative-cloud-discounted-subscription-students-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO will be offering Students an option to purchase Adobe Creative Cloud through Rensselaer at a significant discount over Adobe’s normal student pricing. Pricing is as posted and subject to change at any time. Currently licenses purchased through Rensselaer will cost $110 and will be valid from activation through the following summer term or until you are no longer an active Rensselaer student, whichever comes first. Please view the full announcement for details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/adobe-creative-cloud-discounted-subscription-students-0</guid></item><item><title>Applications Now Open for 2024-2025 Barry Goldwater Scholarship</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/23/2024/applications-now-open-2024-2025-barry-goldwater-scholarship</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Established by Congress in 1986 to foster and encourage excellence in science and mathematics, the Barry Goldwater Scholarship and Excellence in Education Foundation runs an educational scholarship program designed to provide opportunities for U.S. undergraduate students with strong academic records and outstanding research potential. The pre-application deadline is Monday, November 25, 2024; the final application deadline for nominated students is Monday, January 20, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/23/2024/applications-now-open-2024-2025-barry-goldwater-scholarship</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2024 Academic and Refund Policy Changes Announced</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/office-registrar/06/26/2024/policy-changes</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past year, Provost Rebecca Doerge carefully reviewed the Institute’s academic policies and procedures alongside student leaders and academic and administrative groups. Based on their findings, she is excited to announce drop period, refund, and undergraduate course repeat policy changes that will become effective for the Fall 2024 semester.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/office-registrar/06/26/2024/policy-changes</guid></item><item><title>Webex LTI Legacy Upgraded to Webex LTI 1.3 in Blackboard</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</link><description>&lt;p&gt;MultiMedia Services wishes to inform the campus community that Webex LTI Legacy (formerly Webex Education Connector) has been upgraded in Blackboard to the new Webex LTI 1.3 connector. This is the final upgrade prior to the start of the semester, and brings in increased stability and features for utilizing Webex within a course in Blackboard. Please refer to the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/sections/360008224951"&gt;ITSSC Knowledge Base&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</guid></item><item><title>Campus Community Invited to Cybersecurity Meetup with CISA, ISC2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8f30277e-00002d2fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, August 28, 2024 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM - All are welcome to join the Rensselaer Cybersecurity Collaboratory and DotCIO in Academy Hall Auditorium for their monthly ISC2 Capital District NY chapter meeting. This month, Crystal Wilson, NY Cyber State Coordinator for CISA, will give a talk. Please &lt;a href="mailto:callab5@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Dr. Brian Callahan&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8f30277e-00002d2fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
