<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Nominations Being Sought for RAA Teaching Award</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22919&amp;ecid=22919&amp;ciid=79492&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Nominations are now being accepted for the 2024 Rensselaer Alumni Association (RAA) Teaching Award, which recognizes current members of the faculty for their outstanding teaching techniques, contributions to the campus experience, and commitment to students. Nominations are due by Wednesday, July 31.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22919&amp;ecid=22919&amp;ciid=79492&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Leading and Managing Graduate Certificates Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4ab6fdca-00005e82calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 31, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/LCCTMTCT31"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., as he highlights Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Leading Change and Innovation, and Managing Technical Organizations. Attendees will learn how individuals can manage and lead effective cross-functional teams, and implement changes designed to optimize the realization of tactics and strategies….&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4ab6fdca-00005e82calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Leaders in Action” Conversation to be Held with Trustee and CDPHP CEO Dr. John Bennett</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-b46338ed-000053e7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, July 29, 2024 4:00 PM - 6:00 PM - During this session, hosted by Prof. Azita Hirsa, Trustee John D. Bennett, MD, FACC, FACP, immediate past President and Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of Capital District Physicians’ Health Plan, Inc. (CDPHP®), will discuss the principles of authentic leadership and what it means to embody this practice. Participants will have the opportunity to ask questions related to the topic. Refreshments will be served following the session.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-b46338ed-000053e7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Quantum Computing Users Group Meeting</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Quantum Computing Users Group will meet on Wednesday, July 31st, from noon to 1 pm, in Amos Eaton 214. A number of our members are attending the IBM Qiskit Summer School. Their experiences and other topics the group is interested in will be discussed. Please join us! RSVP: Tom Morgan, morgat5@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-meeting</guid></item><item><title>Joint ECSE/CBIS Seminar on Life Science Automation Scheduled for July 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0190-e5500128-00001be3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, July 29, 2024 10:30 AM - 11:30 AM - Professors Kerstin Thurow and Heidi Fleischer — from the Center for Life Science Automation (Celisca) at the University of Rostock, Germany — will jointly present a seminar focusing on life science automation research in Celisca.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0190-e5500128-00001be3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC Announces Fall 2024 Programs</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/news/2024/empac-announces-fall-2024-programs</link><description>&lt;p&gt;EMPAC is pleased to announce its schedule of public presentations for the fall 2024 season! From August through December, the EMPAC Curatorial Program will present 20 opportunities in which audiences can explore the boundaries of art, science, and technology with its curators and artists-in-residence. The season begins with Laurie Anderson on August 29.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/news/2024/empac-announces-fall-2024-programs</guid></item><item><title>Update Regarding CCPD MathWorks Info Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2631</link><description>&lt;p&gt;CCPD’s info session with Mathworks, which was originally scheduled for July 18, will now take place from 6:30PM to 7:30PM on Tuesday, July 30. Students are welcome to join the MathWorks team to learn about the company’s career paths and culture, as well as upcoming opportunities for Arch students seeking an Away experience. Also review the &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/edu/jobs/8911739"&gt;Engineering Development Group Spring Co-Op&lt;/a&gt; opportunity posted in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2631</guid></item><item><title>Campus Summer Shuttle Service to Continue for City Station Residents</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/06/13/2024/campus-summer-shuttle-service</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Parking and Transportation will be continuing shuttle service to Rensselaer students living at the City Station residences for the summer, with shuttle service to run from 10AM to 10PM Monday through Saturday, and from noon to 8PM on Sunday. The City Station shuttle bus stop is located in front of City Station East.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/06/13/2024/campus-summer-shuttle-service</guid></item></channel></rss>
