<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:31:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Administration Division Announces 2024 Annual Utility Shutdown</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/administration/04/12/2024/2024-annual-utility-shutdown</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All members of the campus community should note that the dates have been set for this year’s 2024 Annual Utility Shutdown for Assessment and Repair, with steam outages scheduled to take place May 3-11. Electrical outages, which are necessary to exercise distribution feeders and test the campus’ automatic power transfer switches, are scheduled for May 6-9. Please check the spreadsheet links on the Administration Division’s website for specific outage dates and times for each building.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/administration/04/12/2024/2024-annual-utility-shutdown</guid></item><item><title>9th Annual Graduate Research Symposium to be Held May 10</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8c5f644f-018d-6a5e954e-000067aacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 10, 2024 (all day) - The Graduate Research Symposium is organized for and by graduate students. Past symposiums have featured keynote speakers, the final round of the Three Minute Thesis academic research competition, podium and poster presentations, career and alumni panels, and networking sessions. Please &lt;a href="https://rpi.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_5uukxOGriyGeEwm"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8c5f644f-018d-6a5e954e-000067aacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Hold Information Session May 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348ac52d-000001a3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, May 7, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., will review the online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates, and participants will learn how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/general26"&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348ac52d-000001a3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>OnStream IPTV Service is Now Online</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/onstream-iptv-service-now-online</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO is pleased to announce a new service, OnStream IPTV streaming. With OnStream, you can watch a lineup of live streaming TV anywhere on campus, as well as have access to your other on-demand streaming services through one convenient portal, so it’s ready whenever and wherever you are!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/onstream-iptv-service-now-online</guid></item><item><title>CDPHP Nurse, Member Services Consultations Available to Faculty, Staff May 9</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/cdphp-nurse-or-member-services-consultations</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Because Rensselaer’s Division of Human Resources and our partners at CDPHP, Inc. know how important it is to provide you with opportunities and support in answering questions about your health and medical plan benefits, faculty and staff enrolled in Rensselaer’s medical plans with CDPHP can meet in person with our dedicated nurse and/or a member services representative from 9am to 3pm on Thursday, May 9 at the Heffner Alumni House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/cdphp-nurse-or-member-services-consultations</guid></item></channel></rss>
