<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Be a Part of RPI’s Premier Cybersecurity Team!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-dc57237a-000062cfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - The #1 collegiate cybersecurity CTF team in the country is looking for new players, so if you’d like to be part of the Rensselaer Cybersecurity Collaboratory, just stop by Sage 3101 every Wednesday evening through the end of the semester! No experience necessary, just a willingness to learn and try new things. &lt;a href="mailto:mailto;callab5@rpi.edu"&gt;Contact Dr. Brian Callahan&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-dc57237a-000062cfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>September 17 Marvell Semiconductor Info Session for RPI Students Only</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2691</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 5:30PM to 6:30PM EDT on Tuesday, September 17 in Low/CII 3112, students are welcome to attend this special session to learn more about Marvell, Inc, a leading semiconductor company at the forefront of data innovation, and the exciting internship opportunities the company has available. If you’re looking for an internship and are passionate about semiconductor design, this is a great chance to discover how you can be a part of Marvell’s journey to shape the future of data technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2691</guid></item><item><title>BD Edge Program Student Information Sharing Virtual Session to be Held September 18</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/bd-edge-program-0918-student-information-sharing-virtual-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re ready to bring your big ideas and ambitions to BD and make your contribution to their next innovation, attend this virtual session on Wednesday, September 18 from 5:30 pm to 7:30 pm for insights about working life at BD and their focus on developing new professionals. You’ll hear firsthand how BD’s early career professionals in the Edge Program (Technology &amp;amp; Global Services) are developing their own skills while supporting BD’s mission of advancing the world of healthTM.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/bd-edge-program-0918-student-information-sharing-virtual-session</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Updates LabView Software with New Activation Serial Number</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-updated-labview-software-new-activation-serial-number</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO has updated the LabView activation serial number for students, so all students are asked to please use this new serial number when activating LabView products on single-user machines. The &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/articles/360014415652-LabVIEW-Installation-Instructions-for-Windows"&gt;ITSSC article&lt;/a&gt; providing LabView installation instructions has also been updated with this new serial number.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-updated-labview-software-new-activation-serial-number</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Tech Tip Tuesday: Highlighted ITSSC Articles and Laptop Care Tips</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/tech-tip-tuesday-highlighted-articles-and-laptop-care-tips</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When you’re a new student at Rensselaer, it’s good to know that many articles are available in the IT Services and Support Center, or ITSSC, to assist you! There you’ll find helpful information about available licensed software, device compatibility, network connections, printing, and laptop care tips. You can also use ITSSC to &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu"&gt;submit a support request&lt;/a&gt; if you have any questions or require assistance.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/tech-tip-tuesday-highlighted-articles-and-laptop-care-tips</guid></item><item><title>“It’s Your Final Semester — Now What?” Topic of ISSS Workshop</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-a4d1461f-000076b1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Join Rensselaer’s Office of International Services for Students and Scholars (ISSS) for a virtual workshop to learn about the immigration options for life after graduation. Topics will include employment, continuing one’s studies, departing the U.S., and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-a4d1461f-000076b1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Learn How a Nuclear Submarine Works” Seminar Scheduled for September 18</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-b96f1a2e-00007ee8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM - If you’ve ever wanted to know how a nuclear-powered submarine works, attend this session in the CBIS Isermann Auditorium for a discussion and Q&amp;amp;A opportunity! Like spacecrafts here on Earth, these amazing ships operate submerged and independent for months at a time; this session will focus on the submarines’ nuclear reactor, key engineering systems, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-b96f1a2e-00007ee8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>UPDATE: September 17 “Congress to Campus” Community Town Hall Postponed</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e274bf38-00002bf0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 17, 2024 6:30 PM - 8:00 PM - This event, featuring former members of Congress The Honorable Elizabeth Esty (D-CT) and The Honorable John J. Faso (R-NY), has been postponed and will be rescheduled for later in the fall 2024 semester. In the meantime, make sure you are registered to vote by going to &lt;a href="https://www.rockthevote.org/"&gt;RockTheVote.org&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.vote.org/"&gt;Vote.org&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e274bf38-00002bf0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Posts Security Warning Regarding Duo/MFA Passcodes</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/security-warning-regarding-duomfa-passcodes</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Division of the Chief Information Officer is encouraging everyone to please be aware of sophisticated phishing attempts targeting our community, and to not provide their Duo codes in response to any text messages, phone calls, emails, or other communications they may receive. These requests are fraudulent and designed to steal your information and compromise your RCS account.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/security-warning-regarding-duomfa-passcodes</guid></item><item><title>Sarah Davachi to Present “Constants” at EMPAC</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c8f716d2-00004e03calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 7:00 PM - Join EMPAC for “Constants,” a concert by musician and composer Sarah Davachi! Performing a single work of electronic analog synthesizer-based music, Davachi will fill EMPAC’s Concert Hall with gradually transforming musical strata, inviting listeners to an inner world of sonic detail informed by minimalist tenets, formal concepts from early music, and experimental recording practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c8f716d2-00004e03calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Help Ensure the Upcoming Reunion &amp; Homecoming is a Success!</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23170&amp;ecid=23170&amp;ciid=80446&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Institute Advancement | The Office of Alumni Engagement is looking for assistance/volunteers during Reunion &amp;amp; Homecoming weekend from Friday, September 27 – Sunday, September 29, 2024. Visit the &lt;a href="https://signup.com/go/WuTBGKb"&gt;Reunion &amp;amp; Homecoming SignUp page&lt;/a&gt; to view opportunities and to select the time slots that work for you; training will begin September 18. Your participation will help ensure that our alumni and guests have a great weekend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23170&amp;ecid=23170&amp;ciid=80446&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Rajani Bhatia to Speak at STS Colloquium September 18</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-speaker-rajani-bhatia</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled from from 11:30am to 1pm in Sage 5711, this talk argues that, in the context of intensifying climate change impacts, populationist thinking and agendas tempt broad audiences by providing an easy scapegoat. Analyzing how mainstream and extreme rhetoric on population amplify one another, Bhatia turns to feminist critics of population control to affirm the possibility of another future based on the vision articulated by reproductive and environmental justice movements.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-speaker-rajani-bhatia</guid></item><item><title>Four Different Engineers Score in 4-2 Win at SUNY Brockport</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/14/field-hockey-four-different-engineers-score-in-win-at-suny-brockport.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer field hockey team scored three times in the second half to register a 4-2 win at SUNY Brockport on the afternoon of Saturday, September 14. All four RPI scores were recorded by four different Engineers in the team victory.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/14/field-hockey-four-different-engineers-score-in-win-at-suny-brockport.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Physics, Applied Physics and Astronomy Colloquium Scheduled for September 18</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-80a8e4d8-00003f02calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - This colloquium will feature a presentation by Dr. Simon J.L. Billinge.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-80a8e4d8-00003f02calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Quantum Computing Users Group Monthly Meeting Scheduled for September 18</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-monthly-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join students and colleagues interested in quantum computing or those currently working on the subject at noon on Wednesday, September 18 in Amos Eaton 217. If you are interested in participating, please &lt;a href="mailto:morgat5@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Tom Morgan.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-monthly-meeting</guid></item><item><title>CDPHP Nurse, Member Services Consultations Available to Faculty, Staff September 17</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/cdphp-nurse-and-member-services-consultations</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Because Rensselaer’s Division of Human Resources and our partners at CDPHP, Inc. know how important it is to provide you with opportunities and support in answering questions about your health and medical plan benefits, faculty and staff enrolled in Rensselaer’s medical plans with CDPHP can meet in person with our dedicated nurse and/or a member services representative from noon to 3pm on Tuesday, September 17 at the Heffner Alumni House.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/cdphp-nurse-and-member-services-consultations</guid></item><item><title>“Viewing Summer Student Course Evaluation Results in HelioCampus” Topic of Instructor/TA Webinar</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-bd8d3cf7-00005b12calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Instructors and TAs are encouraged to &lt;a href="https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/r9849f150d6dddb4bbda1efbcaca59394"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; for this session, which will review how to run course evaluations results in HelioCampus and view the data in various ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:32:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-bd8d3cf7-00005b12calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
