<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Meat Monday 2! | August 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-424dcb88-00005dc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, August 11, 2025 11:30 AM - 2:00 PM - Join the CCPD &amp;amp; MANE for a sizzling end of summer! | Date: August 11, 2025 | Time: 11:30 AM – 2 PM | Location: DCC Courtyard. Enjoy delicious grilled meats alongside a variety of gluten-free, dairy-free, and vegan sides—plus a tasty meat substitute option for our plant-based friends! Come hungry and bring your friends—there’s something for everyone!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-424dcb88-00005dc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty vs Student Volleyball Game | Aug. 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-56d61a6a-000035bdcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, August 11, 2025 12:00 PM - 2:00 PM - Serving up BBQ and volleyballs on Meat Monday! Join us on ’86 Field during Meat Monday from 12-2 PM to have a friendly rivalry volleyball match, faculty vs. students! Bragging rights are on the line.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-56d61a6a-000035bdcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ISE Professor, Dr. Jennifer Pazour, to Speak at The National Academies of Sciences, Engineering &amp; Medicine Webinar</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/national-academies-sciences-engineering-and-medicine-webinar-august-12-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join The National Academies of Sciences, Engineering, and Medicine on August 12 for a webinar on creating more resilient supply chains using the latest insights from the mathematical sciences. Speakers will discuss their work on optimizing supply chains, including ways to address drug shortages, improve military logistics, and leverage on-demand manufacturing. Register here: https://www.nationalacademies.org/event/45383_08-2025_building-resilient-supply-chains-innovation-by-the-numbers&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/national-academies-sciences-engineering-and-medicine-webinar-august-12-2025</guid></item><item><title>Overview of Webex Webinar New Features Offered on Thursday August 14</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/overview-webex-webinar-new-features-offered-thursday-august-14</link><description>&lt;p&gt;An overview of the Webex Webinar application included in our site license will be provided, including many new features which have been recently added to the application. This training is open to all members of the Rensselaer community and will be conducted remotely via Webex. Don’t miss this opportunity to enhance your skills and make the most of the new features! View the full description and register at https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/r3ccd51d0b9dae0a77db228dc5ad5c324.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/overview-webex-webinar-new-features-offered-thursday-august-14</guid></item><item><title>Raven Chacon’s Lazyhorse opens EMPAC’s TOPOS Music Festival in Troy! | Aug. 28</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-7aecc5b8-00001e40calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, August 28, 2025 12:00 AM - Sat , August 30, 2025 12:00 AM - This inaugural music festival from EMPAC brings together some of today’s most innovative artists working at the edge of sound, space, and perception. From ethereal chamber minimalism to immersive electronic ritual, TOPOS invites you to gather, listen, and imagine differently. Join us for TOPOS 2025 at EMPAC and in Troy! August 28–30. 3 FREE events. 7 NEW and rare productions. Experience everything with the all-access…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-7aecc5b8-00001e40calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>OVPR &amp; Foundation Philanthropy Workshop: The Research Bio | Aug. 20 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-09d5c9e7-00002dbfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, August 20, 2025 10:00 AM - 12:00 PM - The Research Bio: How to Communicate Your Work to External Agencies. A research biography is concise and informative, highlighting your professional identity, research interests, and significant accomplishments. Join us for a hands-on workshop aimed at crafting effective research bios. The workshop will begin with a presentation, followed by small working group breakouts (bring your current research bio and laptop). REGISTER AT LINK ABOVE&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-09d5c9e7-00002dbfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Fall 2025 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-fall-2025-course-requests</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Fall 2025 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-fall-2025-course-requests</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work MBA for Professionals Review on August 13</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-37b3dd03-00004acfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, August 13, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join Rensselaer Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-37b3dd03-00004acfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-1</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience a “day in the life” of a Supervisor. In addition, the importance of managing employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team capacity will be explored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-1</guid></item></channel></rss>
