<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Deadline Approaching for December 2024 Late Degree Application</title><link>https://registrar.rpi.edu/announcements/deadline-december-2024-late-degree-application</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The late application deadline for December 2024 graduation is Friday, October 25. The Registrar’s Office won’t accept any applications after that date, so apply today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://registrar.rpi.edu/announcements/deadline-december-2024-late-degree-application</guid></item><item><title>Industry Evening with Lally School of Management to be Held November 13</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/industry-evening-lally-school-management-1113</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD and the Lally School of Management from 5:30PM to 8:00PM on Wednesday, November 13 in the Russell Sage Banquet Hall for an evening of professional networking and recruiting conversation surrounding careers in the financial services, business, and management consulting industries. &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/events/1621467/share_preview"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; in Handshake today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/industry-evening-lally-school-management-1113</guid></item><item><title>Co-Terminal Program Info Session to be Held October 25</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-ad989b9e-0000125ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 25, 2024 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - The Office of Graduate Education invites students interested in learning about the application process and the great opportunities the Co-Terminal Program provides to attend this session! Please &lt;a href="mailto:atkins3@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Steven Atkinson&lt;/a&gt; if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-ad989b9e-0000125ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Book Your COMM+D Appointment Online!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/08/20/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you working on a writing assignment, oral presentation, or visual design project? Whether you’re at the beginning brainstorming stages or finishing up your final revisions, the Center for Global Communication+Design (Comm+D) can help! Just &lt;a href="https://rpi.mywconline.com/"&gt;schedule an appointment&lt;/a&gt; with a member of our trained staff, then stop by the Comm+D offices on the lower level of Folsom Library.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/08/20/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</guid></item><item><title>Applications Now Open for 2024-2025 Barry Goldwater Scholarship</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/23/2024/applications-now-open-2024-2025-barry-goldwater-scholarship</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Established by Congress in 1986 to foster and encourage excellence in science and mathematics, the Barry Goldwater Scholarship and Excellence in Education Foundation runs an educational scholarship program designed to provide opportunities for U.S. undergraduate students with strong academic records and outstanding research potential. The pre-application deadline is Monday, November 25, 2024; the final application deadline for nominated students is Monday, January 20, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/23/2024/applications-now-open-2024-2025-barry-goldwater-scholarship</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of SSTF’s Annual Litter Bug Battle!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-90b707b9-00000321calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Sunday, October 27, 2024 12:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Join Rensselaer’s Student Sustainability Task Force and compete to collect the most litter around campus and in the city of Troy! Gloves, garbage bags, and refreshments will be provided. For more information on this event, stop by the Mueller Center or &lt;a href="mailto:manerl@rpi.edu"&gt;send an email&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-90b707b9-00000321calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>October is Cybersecurity Awareness Month!</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/october-cybersecurity-awareness-month</link><description>&lt;p&gt;To help all members of the campus community enhance their cybersecurity knowledge, brush up on best practices and stay informed about the latest campus cybersecurity threats, DotCIO has worked with Rensselaer’s Division of Human Resources to curate a number of training resources in Percipio.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/october-cybersecurity-awareness-month</guid></item><item><title>“Be the Media” Workshop with Film Director Mark Decena Scheduled for October 25</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/be-media-workshop-film-director-mark-decena</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join HASS at 5pm on October 25 at The Sanctuary for Independent Media in North Troy for a “Be the Media” workshop and film screening with film director Mark Decena, Founder of Kontent Films and Director of “Farming While Black.” The film examines the historical plight of Black farmers in the United States, as well as the rising generation of Black farmers reclaiming their rightful ownership to land and reconnecting with their ancestral roots.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/be-media-workshop-film-director-mark-decena</guid></item><item><title>Women’s XC Puts Three in Top 10, Finishes Third at Geneseo</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/10/19/womens-cross-country-puts-three-in-top-10-finish-third-in-team-standings-at-geneseo.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On october 19, the Rensselaer women’s cross country team finished third out of 29 teams at the Mike Woods Invite hosted by SUNY Geneseo. The Engineers placed three runners among the first ten finishers, with Julianne Bleskoski, Olivia Pisacano, and Erin vonHousen highlighting the day for RPI.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/10/19/womens-cross-country-puts-three-in-top-10-finish-third-in-team-standings-at-geneseo.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of Black Families Technology Awareness Day</title><link>https://bftad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/be-part-black-families-technology-awareness-day-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled for Saturday, February 1, Black Families Technology Awareness Day 2025 is designed to excite and engage K-12 students and their parents or guardians in science, technology, engineering, the arts and mathematics! Program proposals are being sought for the event and submissions are due by November 1; campus community members are invited to register through December 5 to volunteer.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bftad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/be-part-black-families-technology-awareness-day-2025</guid></item><item><title>“Life and Legacy: Unpackaging the Last Thirty-Six Hours of Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.” to be Held October 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-b9987f91-00002eefcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 29, 2024 10:00 AM - 11:30 AM - This symposium aims to delve into several important topics, including exploring Dr. Howard Thurman’s enduring influence on the formation of King’s unique leadership style; examining Black theology, civil rights activism, and the Black Power Movement; reflecting on King’s involvement with Alpha Phi Alpha and the Poor People’s Campaign; and providing an overview and in-depth analysis of the “I Dream” production.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-b9987f91-00002eefcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Webex LTI Legacy Upgraded to Webex LTI 1.3 in Blackboard</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</link><description>&lt;p&gt;MultiMedia Services wishes to inform the campus community that Webex LTI Legacy (formerly Webex Education Connector) has been upgraded in Blackboard to the new Webex LTI 1.3 connector. This is the final upgrade prior to the start of the semester, and brings in increased stability and features for utilizing Webex within a course in Blackboard. Please refer to the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/sections/360008224951"&gt;ITSSC Knowledge Base&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</guid></item><item><title>Abstract Submissions for CMDIS Annual Research Symposium Open through October 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-fd70885a-00006338calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 16, 2024 12:00 AM - Wed , October 30, 2024 5:00 PM - The Center for Materials, Devices and Integrated Systems will host its Annual Research Symposium on November 22, and all faculty, visiting scholars, researchers, graduate students, facility users and undergraduate researchers are invited to submit abstracts for oral/poster presentations, and to join the Art-in-Science competition.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-fd70885a-00006338calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Cell Therapies Conference Speaker B. Wayne Bequette on the Life Saving Benefits of Cell and Gene Manufacturing</title><link>https://www.aiche.org/chenected/2024/10/cell-therapies-conference-speaker-b-wayne-bequette-on-life-saving-benefits-cell-and-gene</link><description>&lt;p&gt;B. Wayne Bequette, a professor in Rensselaer’s department of Chemical and Biological Engineering, and Technology Manager at the CESMII Northern Regional Manufacturing Center, discusses what he will share at the 5th Cell Therapies and Immunotherapy Conference, to be held October 28-30 in San Diego, California.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aiche.org/chenected/2024/10/cell-therapies-conference-speaker-b-wayne-bequette-on-life-saving-benefits-cell-and-gene</guid></item><item><title>2024 United Way Pledge Campaign Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-a04d1e4c-00001f38calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 18, 2024 12:00 AM - Mon , December 16, 2024 12:00 AM - The United Way of the Greater Capital Region works to advance the common good by focusing on basic needs, family support and financial stability, and Rensselaer has long been an active and proud partner in helping to create long-lasting systemic change toward a better tomorrow. Once again, Rensselaer’s United Way volunteers call upon the generosity of the campus community to help address societal challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-a04d1e4c-00001f38calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
