<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CMDIS BYOND Build Your Own Nano Device Program | Sept. 15-Nov. 14 (Applications due by Sept. 5)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-426e8069-00001212calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 15, 2025 12:00 AM - Fri , November 14, 2025 12:00 AM - Fall 2025 Applications Now Open for CMDIS BYOND Build Your Own Nano Device Program. The Center for Materials, Devices and Integrated Systems’, Micro and NanoFabrication Clean Room, offers a four-module certificate program for undergraduates, an exciting opportunity for those planning to pursue a graduate degree or those looking to prepare for a professional career in microelectronics, medical, and energy industries…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-426e8069-00001212calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Annual State Fire Inspections in Residential Buildings Begin September 3</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/annual-state-fire-inspections-residential-buildings-begin-september-3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The New York State Office of Fire Prevention and Control (OFPC) conducts annual building inspections of all college and universities across the state. Inspections of RPI residential buildings will begin on September 3, 2025, and are expected to take approximately three to four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/annual-state-fire-inspections-residential-buildings-begin-september-3</guid></item><item><title>OGE Dissertation and Thesis Preparation Workshop | Sept. 16</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-1b27c20c-00005a71calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 16, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:30 PM - Learn the basics of correct thesis organization and format, appropriate paper attribution and reference citation styles—plus a review of the most commonly found mistakes and ways to avoid them. This workshop is for any student who will be writing a MS thesis or PhD dissertation. Bring your questions! To register for this WebEx event: https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScVfJONdDnqLJmBM1YWYt8rdBoIHCrMxri39nN2j4QPs_eLmg/viewform?usp…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-1b27c20c-00005a71calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ID Cards Required to Access Meal Plans in Dining Hall</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/id-cards-required-dining-hall-access</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We hope your semester is off to a great start! Please be reminded that starting immediately, all students with an active meal plan must present their valid student ID card to access meals in the dining halls. This policy helps ensure efficient service and accurate meal tracking.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/id-cards-required-dining-hall-access</guid></item><item><title>Closure of Sage Avenue Roadway and Sidewalk Beginning September 22</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/closure-sage-avenue-roadway-and-sidewalk-beginning-september-22</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Beginning Monday, September 22, 2025, RPI Facilities Management will begin a project to replace leaking steam pipes along the north sidewalk in front of E Dorm and across the roadway at the Sage Avenue campus entrance. As a result, the north sidewalk and entrance to the academic campus off Sage Avenue will be closed and will remain closed for approximately five to six weeks. Additionally, Sage Avenue will be closed between the crosswalk at Troy Building and the crosswalk on the east side of E…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/closure-sage-avenue-roadway-and-sidewalk-beginning-september-22</guid></item><item><title>RAA Entrepreneurship Series | Colleen Costello ’12 | Sept. 16</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10810&amp;cid=24406&amp;ecid=24406&amp;ciid=83514&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: 9/16/2025 6:00 PM to 8:00 PM The Rensselaer Alumni Association in 2024 announced a 3-part speaker series on Entrepreneurship and Venture Capital. In our third and final session, Charting the long-term course, we will be highlighting the work of &lt;a href="https://vyv.tech/team/colleen-costello/"&gt;Colleen Costello ’12&lt;/a&gt;, co-founder of Vyv, a company focused on inventing smarter ways to slow the spread of microbes to make the world a better place.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10810&amp;cid=24406&amp;ecid=24406&amp;ciid=83514&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; Trinity Consultants Info Session | Sept. 16</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-trinity-consultants-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Trinity Consultants will be hosting a virtual info session on Tuesday, 9/16 at 4pm! Learn more about careers in consulting and engineering as well as available opportunities. Registration and more details (including a link to join the meeting) are available in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-trinity-consultants-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Stephanie Boluk and Patrick LeMieux: Hands Free: A History of Accessible Alt Ctrls |Sept. 23</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/stephanie-boluk-and-patrick-lemieux-hands-free-history-accessible-alt-ctrls</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This presentation begins with a brisk survey of the history of hands-free video game interfaces before comparing and contrasting two devices that articulate two different design philosophies: the NES Hands Free and the Octopad. Rather than thinking about accessibility as a single-player problem, these controllers engage the social, political, and environmental aspects of video games to change the way we play. Join us on September 23 at 4:30pm on Webex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/stephanie-boluk-and-patrick-lemieux-hands-free-history-accessible-alt-ctrls</guid></item></channel></rss>
