<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:32:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>RPI - SME Student Chapter S-141 Informational Meeting | July 9 (RSVP)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0197-9d086e0b-00004f87calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 9, 2025 12:30 PM - 1:30 PM - JOIN THE SOCIETY OF MANUFACTURING ENGINEERS RPI - SME Student Chapter S-141 Informational Meeting Become part of a national network of manufacturing leaders and innovators! Ready to get involved? Have questions? Join us for the information session! RSVP by July 8 – noon to Sam Chiappone, SME Faculty Advisor, by email: chiaps@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:32:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0197-9d086e0b-00004f87calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Potential Traffic Disruption - Roadway Between JRSC and JEC begins July 7</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/potential-traffic-disruption-roadway-between-jrsc-and-jec</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Potential Traffic Disruption - Roadway between JRSC and JEC Generator/Fuel Tank Removal and Generator Installation, July 7th - Months End. Please be advised that beginning July 7th, work will commence on the removal and replacement of an underground fuel tank and generator at the roadway between JRSC and JEC. This multiphase project may result in intermittent disruptions to vehicular and pedestrian traffic in the area throughout the month of July.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:32:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/potential-traffic-disruption-roadway-between-jrsc-and-jec</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Performing Maintenance on Academic, Printer and License and Academic Servers week of 06/30</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-performing-maintenance-academic-printer-and-license-servers-week-0630</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO staff will be performing maintenance on over 50 servers to include academic, print and license servers between June 30th to July 3rd. Please click in for further details on scheduling.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:32:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-performing-maintenance-academic-printer-and-license-servers-week-0630</guid></item><item><title>July 4th Week Dining and Retail Hours</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/july-4th-week-dining-and-retail-hours</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please note that our Rensselaer dining halls and retail locations will have adjusted hours during the upcoming July 4th week. For the most up to date hours, please visit the Rensselaer Dining webpage at https://rpi.sodexomyway.com/en-us/locations/ for hours of operation. Thank you for your continued support of Rensselaer Dining and have a safe and fun holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:32:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/july-4th-week-dining-and-retail-hours</guid></item></channel></rss>
