<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>NPZ Law Group - Free Immigration Workshop | Oct. 28</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-1ace1803-00003c39calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 28, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:30 PM - ISSS will host a virtual workshop presented by NPZ Group (Nachman Phulwani Zimovcak (NPZ) Law Group, P.C.). Hear from expert immigration lawyers about the visa options after graduation, including H-1B, O-1, and much more!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-1ace1803-00003c39calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>New Minor in Quantum Computing Now Available</title><link>https://compsci.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-quantum-computing-now-available</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new interdisciplinary minor is available for any student who wants to explore quantum computing. Students will gain both theoretical insight and practical exposure to quantum algorithms, hardware platforms, and the concept of quantum advantage, the point at which quantum systems outperform classical approaches on meaningful tasks. Minor requirements can be found in the RPI catalog. To discuss declaring this minor, please contact the School of Science Hub at ScienceHub@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://compsci.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-quantum-computing-now-available</guid></item><item><title>Panera Hours of Operations for October 25, 2025</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/panera-hours-operations-october-26-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Due to a scheduled event in the McNeil Room in the Student Union on Sunday, October 26th, Panera will open at 1:00 PM. Thank you for your understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/panera-hours-operations-october-26-2025</guid></item><item><title>Hokkaido University Joint Virtual Seminar on Semiconductors and Chips Technology | Oct. 28</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-12061d32-000047c7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 28, 2025 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM - You are cordially invited to attend this WEBEX Seminar, fourth one of a series, to explore joint research proposals for prospective funding on Semiconductors and Chips Technology with Hokkaido University Tuesday evening 7-8 PM (which is 8-9 AM Japan Time)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-12061d32-000047c7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Information Session: 2026 Project RFP: IBM-RPI Future of Computing Research Collaboration (FCRC) Quantum Computing Track</title><link>https://fcrc.rpi.edu/announcements/information-session-2026-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us via Microsoft Teams on Monday, October 27, from 4:00–5:00 PM (ET) for an Information Session on the Track-4: Accelerate Quantum Computing Research (2026 Projects) RFP. The Future of Computing Research Center (FCRC)—a partnership between RPI and IBM—advances innovation in AI algorithms, hardware-software co-design, semiconductor technologies, and quantum computing. This session will outline research topics of interest, the proposal template, and submission timelines for Track-4 projects,…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://fcrc.rpi.edu/announcements/information-session-2026-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research-0</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Colloquia: Justin Hsu - From Discrete to Continuous: Programming Languages for Time and Space | Oct. 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-dd80b703-00003fadcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, October 27, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Justin Hsu is an associate professor of Computer Science at Cornell University. His research focuses on formal verification of probabilistic programs and quantitative programs. His work has been recognized by the EATCS Presburger Award, a Royal Society Wolfson Visiting Fellowship, a NSF CAREER award, a SIGPLAN John C. Reynolds Doctoral Dissertation award, distinguished paper awards from POPL and CAV, and industrial awards from Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-dd80b703-00003fadcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Neil Rolnick Performs: SoloS | Oct. 24</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/neil-rolnick-solos</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Composer and electronic music pioneer Neil Rolnick will perform SoloS, a program of works for solo laptop that spans his career from the late 1970s to the present. The performance includes a range of works from early pieces for digital sampler to his multimedia collaboration with experimental filmmaker Barbara Hammer. Join us October 24 at 7pm at the RPI Chapel and Cultural Center.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/neil-rolnick-solos</guid></item><item><title>HASS Family Weekend Music Showcase on Saturday October 25</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/hass-family-weekend-music-showcase</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This program features the RPI Orchestra, Concert Choir, and Wind Symphony in a musical preview of works that will be included on the Dec. 6th RPI Holiday Concert, including Mark Camphouse’s “A Movement for Rosa”, Christopher Tin’s “Baba Yetu”, and Bedrich Smetana’s “Die Moldau”. Admission is free. Showcase starts at 2:30pm in DCC 308.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/hass-family-weekend-music-showcase</guid></item><item><title>New Letterhead Available in the RPI Brand Hub</title><link>https://www.rpi.edu/announcements/new-letterhead-available-rpi-brand-hub</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new letterhead template is now available in the &lt;a href="https://brand.rpi.edu"&gt;RPI Brand Hub&lt;/a&gt;. You can also personalize and order the new letterhead directly through the Dupli punchout in the OSCAR Marketplace. For any questions, please contact the Project Management Office at &lt;a href="mailto:brandrefresh@rpi.edu"&gt;brandrefresh@rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.rpi.edu/announcements/new-letterhead-available-rpi-brand-hub</guid></item><item><title>Chemistry Fall 2025 Seminar Series | Oct. 28</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-11718d5a-000016f7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 28, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Kendell Pawelec, from the Department of Radiation at Michigan State University, will speak on the topic “Determining in situ Polymeric Device Behavior from CT Imaging Enabled by Radiopaque Nanoparticles”.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-11718d5a-000016f7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials” | Oct. 28</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-e2a90780-00000628calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 28, 2025 9:00 AM - 5:00 PM - In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience a “day in the life” of a Supervisor. In addition, the importance of managing employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-e2a90780-00000628calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review | Oct. 28</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-c47e0079-000040c5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 28, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join RPI at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-c47e0079-000040c5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff: Sign up for Community RAD</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-sign-community-rad</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Faculty and Staff: If you haven’t already signed up for a Community RAD account, now’s a great time to get started and take advantage of the added convenience, flexibility, and savings.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-sign-community-rad</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 SoE Midterm Student Course Evaluations: Reviewing Evaluation Results (Training for Instructors and TAs) Webinar | Oct. 31</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-026954a3-00001a60calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 31, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - This webinar is for instructors and TA’s that would like to understand or have a refresher of the various ways to review their student course evaluations in HelioCampus. This webinar focuses on reviewing midterm course evaluations for instructors in the School of Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:31:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-026954a3-00001a60calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
