<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Nutrition Workshop | March 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-428df490-000078c6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, March 27, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:00 PM in the Mueller Center Classroom - Fuel your body and mind at our Nutrition Workshops! Learn practical tips for healthy eating, meal prepping, and making nutritious choices. Open to all—empower yourself with knowledge for a healthier you! Use the link to register today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-428df490-000078c6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Join Velan Studios - An Introduction to Tech Art in the Games Industry! | April 1st, 2025</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/join-velan-studios-introduction-tech-art-games-industry</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Velan Studios for an engaging session with their developers as they introduce the exciting world of Technical Art in the games industry. Learn how tech artists bridge the gap between art and engineering, bringing creative visions to life. Whether you’re an artist, programmer, or are simply passionate about games, this conversation will shed light on the role of Tech Art at Velan Studios. Register and learn more in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/join-velan-studios-introduction-tech-art-games-industry</guid></item><item><title>Join HR for a Conversation on Key Initiatives - April 2nd at 2:00 PM</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/join-hr-conversation-key-initiatives</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This Webex meeting is an opportunity to engage with HR and discuss the Division’s four key initiatives designed to drive growth and engagement, while strengthening organizational trust, accountability, and leadership – all aligned with the RPI Forward Strategic Plan. 1. Transform Staff Performance Management Process 2. Create Impactful Leadership Development Programs 3. Strengthen Rewards and Recognition Program 4. Assess Institute-wide Total Compensation (Pay and Benefits)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/join-hr-conversation-key-initiatives</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Posts Reminder Regarding Compliance with Campus Email Policy</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-posts-reminder-regarding-compliance-campus-email-policy-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Members of DotCIO’s IT Security team wish to remind all members of the Rensselaer community that Institute policy states that email accounts obtained through third parties may not be used in conducting the business of the Institute, and that ensuring compliance with the Rensselaer email policy is crucial.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-posts-reminder-regarding-compliance-campus-email-policy-0</guid></item><item><title>Lecture and Panel Discussion with Media Theorist Jussi Parikka and others | April 4</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/jussi-parikka-operational-images-theories-vision-boundaries-art-science-games-and</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us in the CBIS Auditorium from 9am to 5:30pm for a lecture and panel discussion with media theorist Jussi Parikka (Aarhus University) in conversation with art historian/theorist Caroline A. Jones (MIT), architectural theorist/historian Theodora Vardouli (McGill University), architectural historian Michael Abrahamson (University of Utah), and architect Viola Ago (Toronto Metropolitan University).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/jussi-parikka-operational-images-theories-vision-boundaries-art-science-games-and</guid></item><item><title>Leaders in Action Conversation with Major General Kimberly M. Colloton’92 PMP, Deputy Chief of Engineers &amp; Deputy Commanding General U.S. Army Corps of Engineers scheduled for March 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-1fb1d01f-000037a0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, March 27, 2025 12:00 PM - 2:00 PM at the Heffner Alumni House Great HallDuring this session, host Prof. Azita Hirsa and Major General Kimberly M. Colloton’92 PMP, Deputy Chief of Engineers &amp;amp; Deputy Commanding General U.S. Army Corps of Engineers will discuss Engineering Ethics in the 21st Century. Participants will be able to ask relevant questions; refreshments will be served following the session.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-1fb1d01f-000037a0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Colloquia: Utkarsh Ojha - On the creative potential of generative models and detecting their images | March 31</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-618c44b3-000012d9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, March 31, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM in CII 3206 - Utkarsh Ojha is currently a postdoctoral fellow at Carnegie Mellon University. He received his Ph.D. in computer science from the University of Wisconsin-Madison. His research work has centered around generative models for images. He has developed algorithms that can enable those models to create new visual concepts not seen during training. As of late, his research focus has shifted to developing methods which can distinguish real and AI-generated images.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-618c44b3-000012d9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Intellectual Property &amp; Technology Licensing Seminar | April 1 (RSVP)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-5dd2bd8a-00005381calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, April 1, 2025 11:00 AM - 1:00 PM, Biotech Auditorium - Are you working on groundbreaking research? Curious about how to protect and commercialize your innovations? Join us for an exciting campuswide seminar hosted by the Office of Intellectual Property and Technology Licensing (IPTL) at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI)! This is your chance to learn how IPTL supports faculty and students in turning research into real-world impact—whether through patents, licensing, or industry partnerships.RSVP: &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/intellectual-property-technology-licensing"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-5dd2bd8a-00005381calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Did You Know RPI Has 209 Clubs and Intramural Sports?</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/did-you-know-rpi-has-209-clubs-and-intramural-sports</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Many students participate in multiple activities, totaling 8,735 participations per academic year! And here’s another fun fact: the median earnings of RPI undergraduates 10 years after graduation (as of 2021) is $102K. There’s so much more to explore! Dive into Standard 4 of RPI’s Self-Study for Middle States Accreditation a team led by Mr. Louis Trzepacz and Ms. Karen Long.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/did-you-know-rpi-has-209-clubs-and-intramural-sports</guid></item><item><title>Marx, Mars, and Hyrule: Imagining Planetary Futures: Christian P. Haines to Speak on March 28</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/marx-mars-and-hyrule-imagining-planetary-futures-christian-p-haines</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, March 28, 4:30 - 6:00 PM, SAGE 3303: What do Marxism, science fiction, and video games have in common? They are all efforts to imagine what it’s like to live in complex planetary ecosystems. In this lecture, Christian P. Haines (Assoc. Prof. of English, Penn State) critically examines fantasies of terraforming as alibis for socioeconomic inequality and political injustice.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/marx-mars-and-hyrule-imagining-planetary-futures-christian-p-haines</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO - Update for Microsoft Office 365 Applications &amp; Add-Ons</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-update-microsoft-office-365-applications-add-ons</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All 3rd party applications and add-ons used within Rensselaer’s Office 365 environment must be reviewed to ensure compliance with Rensselaer policies and requirements for data security, privacy, accessibility, and licensing. DotCIO has established a list and a self service tool for adding approved applications and add-ons, as well as a process to initiate a review for an application or add-on not listed&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-update-microsoft-office-365-applications-add-ons</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity Confidential Consultation (In Person) | April 1</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-5dd36304-000054c1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, April 1, 2025 8:00 AM - 4:30 PM at the Heffner Alumni House - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits. To schedule an appointment, call 1-800-642-7131, Monday through Friday, 8:00 am to midnight, or online at https://nb.fidelity.com/public/nbpreloginnav/rpi/microsite/#/tem/meet-with-us&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-5dd36304-000054c1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review | April 2 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-67067033-00005468calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 2, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. You’re invited to join Rensselaer Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event.Registration: &lt;a class="uri" href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MBAP2"&gt;https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MBAP2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-67067033-00005468calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: Leading from Anywhere | April 18 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;At Rensselaer, we maintain that “leadership” involves a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. In this workshop, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership not as positional or based on title, but rather on values and actions.When: Friday, April 18, 2025- 9:00 AM - 11:00 AMWhere: Human Resources-Gurley BuildingCost: Free: Registration is RequiredSee: &lt;a class="uri" href="https://share.percipio.com/cd/biKhfYhXa"&gt;https://share.percipio.com/cd/biKhfYhXa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere-0</guid></item><item><title>Information Session for 2025 Project RFP: IBM-RPI Future of Computing Research Collaboration (FCRC) Quantum Computing Track | March 28</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/information-session-2025-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research-collaboration-fcrc</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on March 28th, 2-3pm for the Info Session concerning the Request for Joint RPI/IBM Research Proposals in the Quantum Computing Track, a collaborative research initiative between RPI and IBM (FCRC) to drive world class innovation and fundamental advances in artificial intelligence algorithm, AI hardware software co-design, Semiconductor Technology and Quantum Computing for the benefit of society. The full RFP is available via the IDEA Intranet. REGISTER to participate at idea.rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/information-session-2025-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research-collaboration-fcrc</guid></item><item><title>Spring 2025 End of Term Course Surveys in HelioCampus: Adding Additional Questions to a Course Section (Faculty/Instructor Training) | March 31</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-c8de75d0-0000245ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, March 31, 2025 12:30 PM - 1:00 PM - This webinar offers faculty/instructors of course sections to add additional questions to their student end of term course evaluations. This is an optional process and only needed if instructors wanted to add other questions than what is on the institute course evaluation. Please click the link in the See section to register for the session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-c8de75d0-0000245ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
