<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:34:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Become an I-PERSIST Mentor for Fall 2026 – apply by January 30!</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/become-i-persist-mentor-fall-2026-apply-january-30</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in becoming a mentor to new students in Calculus, Physics, or Chemistry? Apply to become an I-PERSIST mentor today! Share your subject knowledge, gain leadership skills, connect with faculty, and help new students adjust to RPI! Our application for Fall 2026 closes on January 30, so don’t wait. Click to view the application!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:34:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/become-i-persist-mentor-fall-2026-apply-january-30</guid></item><item><title>Snow Removal Notice</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/snow-removal-notice</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Snow removal in parking lots is scheduled for Wednesday 1/28/2026 and Thursday 1/29/2026. Please click the link above to see the dates, areas, and instructions. If you have any questions please contact Parking at 518-276-6616 or email parking@rpi.edu. Please move vehicles to allow crews to complete snow removal efficiently. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:34:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/snow-removal-notice</guid></item><item><title>Cloud Control: Interactive Networks for Audio-Visual Performance with Eric Souther</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cloud-control-interactive-networks-audio-visual-performance-eric-souther</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This three-hour workshop in West Hall 211 will introduce the node-based programming environment TouchDesigner for creating real-time audiovisuals. The session will begin with a brief introduction to TouchDesigner’s interface and core concepts, followed by a demonstration of my own work created with the platform. Participants will then learn hands-on techniques for mapping data and creating interactive controls for live performance, with a focus on particle systems manipulation. Join 1/28 at 5pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:34:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cloud-control-interactive-networks-audio-visual-performance-eric-souther</guid></item><item><title>Regeneron seeking nominees for Annual Prize for Creative Innovation</title><link>https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/regeneron-seeking-nominees-annual-prize-creative-innovation</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Regeneron seeks to award creativity and innovation in the biomedical sciences with an unrestricted check for $50,000 and an invitation to present a project at Regeneron’s headquarters. Up to 10 finalists will receive a $5,000 award. Rensselaer will select 2 PhD students and 2 post-docs from any discipline for nomination. Contact this office (madige@rpi.edu) for full details and instructions to submit for the internal selection process. Applications will be due to OGE by February 15th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:34:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/regeneron-seeking-nominees-annual-prize-creative-innovation</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review with RPI at Work | Jan. 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-2c719c99-00002fd7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, January 30, 2026 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join RPI Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:34:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-2c719c99-00002fd7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: Steps to Effective Communication: Extended DISC; February 3, 2026</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-4-steps-effective-2</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, February 3, 2026 9:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Our success, both personally and professionally, is largely determined by our ability to communicate effectively with a variety of people. The Extended DISC system is based on behavioral theories that have been used for over one hundred years. In this workshop, participants will receive individualized Extended DISC reports (based on the completion of the Extended DISC questionnaire) that reflect both their “natural” and “adjusted” behavioral…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:34:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-4-steps-effective-2</guid></item><item><title>RPI Faculty and Staff In-Person Workshop: Talk Smart, Teach Strong: Sharpening Your Academic Presentation Skills</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-e1638373-00007c1acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, February 10, 2026 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - This session aims to strengthen academic presentation and facilitation skills, combining elements of presentation best practices with effective teaching strategies. You will explore techniques to enhance voice, presence, and impact in the classroom, while also engaging in train-the-trainer methods to foster active student participation. Please register by 2/6 using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:34:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-e1638373-00007c1acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
