<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Lavender Graduation | May 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-211684d5-00004a6fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, May 7, 2025 2:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Celebrating Rensselaer students of the LGBTQ+ community, Lavender Graduation is sure to be an inclusive and celebratory experience! We look forward to acknowledging your accomplishments and evolutions into college graduates of Rensselaer. Business casual recommended, but come as you feel comfortable. Graduating students who wish to be recognized must register at http://bit.ly/4klWQnL by Monday, May 5. There is no charge to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-211684d5-00004a6fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Ph.D. Hooding Ceremony | May 9</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-1a98bc9c-00003d3dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 9, 2025 8:30 AM - 10:30 AM - The hooding ceremony is a unique recognition of the achievement of each student who has earned a doctorate. Each doctoral candidate is introduced individually during the ceremony. They will have their hood placed on them while standing on the stage in the concert hall. Check-in starts- at 7:45 AM Ceremony- at 8:30 AM Refreshments- after the ceremony concludes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-1a98bc9c-00003d3dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering Commencement Dinner and Celebration | May 9 (RSVP Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-71605693-00003247calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 9, 2025 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM - Join faculty and staff as we honor our graduates and their families at the Hilton Garden Inn in Troy.The sit-down dinner will be followed by the presentation of awards and prizes. A professional photographer will be on hand to take photos of the graduates with their families and friends. Reservations are due May 1, 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-71605693-00003247calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Nominate a student for a 2025 Lavender Graduation Award by May 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-58c087a3-00002668calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, April 21, 2025 11:00 AM - Mon , May 5, 2025 5:00 PM - The Rensselaer LGBTQ+ Task Force is seeking nominations for students, faculty, and staff to be honored at the 8th Annual Lavender Graduation, to be held on Wednesday, May 7th at 2PM in the CBIS Auditorium. These awards celebrate some of our most deserving students for the contributions they have made to the Rensselaer LGBTQ+ community. Our community is better as a result of their time at Rensselaer and these awards are a way of…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-58c087a3-00002668calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>2025 Annual Steam &amp; Electrical Shutdowns | May 10-May 17</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/facilities-management/03/26/2025/2025-annual-steam-electrical-shutdowns</link><description>&lt;p&gt;2025 Annual Shutdowns • Campus wide steam and electrical distribution systems outages will take place beginning Saturday May, 10th and ending on Sunday May 17th. This work is done on the main Rensselaer campus annually in order to perform critical infrastructure preventative maintenance. The Physical Plant works closely with the Registrar’s Office, Summer Arch, Summer at Rensselaer and Rensselaer’s Conference Services to minimize the impact to our students.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/facilities-management/03/26/2025/2025-annual-steam-electrical-shutdowns</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Reviews Single Course Enrollment Options for Summer Term | May 6</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5ef1ddff-00003bfbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, May 6, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., will host this Rensselaer at Work information session reviewing the online graduate programs for working professionals and provide course enrollment options to make an immediate impact on one’s work. Participants can also explore courses for developing valuable skills that benefit employee and employer alike. Please register to attend&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5ef1ddff-00003bfbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ECSE Seminar: “Progress and advancements in surface-conducting diamond for high performance FETs” | May 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-8c1a7f02-00007923calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, May 5, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join us for an ECSE Seminar: “Progress and advancements in surface-conducting diamond for high performance FETs” with Prof. David Moran from University of Glasgow. Abstract and speaker bio can be found at the event URL.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-8c1a7f02-00007923calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>You’re Invited to a Special Fireside Chat: May 9</title><link>https://commencement.rpi.edu/announcements/youre-invited-special-fireside-chat-presidents-commencement-colloquy-driving</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Martin A. Schmidt ’81, Ph.D., and his wife, Lyn, invite you to the President’s Commencement Colloquy, a special Fireside Chat featuring Lisa Su, Ph.D., chair and CEO of AMD, TIME’s CEO of the Year, and one of TIME’s 100 Most Influential People in AI. Don’t miss this opportunity to hear firsthand from two visionary leaders about driving technology innovation in industry. This free event is open to the public and will be followed by a reception with refreshments in Evelyn’s Café.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://commencement.rpi.edu/announcements/youre-invited-special-fireside-chat-presidents-commencement-colloquy-driving</guid></item><item><title>RPI Announces $10 Million Gift from Alumnus and Entrepreneur Ajit Prabhu</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2025/05/01/rpi-announces-10-million-gift-alumnus-and-entrepreneur-ajit-prabhu</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI) has received a $10 million gift from Ajit Prabhu ’98, founder and CEO of Quest Global, to establish the Ajit Prabhu Catalyst Endowment and the Ajit Prabhu Catalyst Fund, both in support of the Office of Strategic Alliances and Translation (OSAT). Prabhu launched the fund, which will assist RPI student and faculty entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2025/05/01/rpi-announces-10-million-gift-alumnus-and-entrepreneur-ajit-prabhu</guid></item><item><title>Student Success Announced 2025 Last Lecture Speakers</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/2025lastlecture</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Over 300 graduating seniors chose Christianna Bennett, Ron Hedden, Benjamin Weissman, Wes Turner, and Sarah Parker Ward for the Class of 2025 Last Lecture Series. Inspired by Dr. Randy Pausch’s tradition, five 20-minute talks will be held, followed by a reception. The event is open to the Rensselaer community, with priority for graduating students.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/2025lastlecture</guid></item><item><title>Teaching &amp; Learning Collaboratory In-Person Spring Event - Learning Today: Neuroscience, Digital Technologies, and Distraction | May 13</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/04/01/2025/teaching-learning-collaboratory-person-spring-event-learning</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Education and the Teaching and Learning Collaboratory are pleased to announce our spring guest speaker, James M. Lang, who will talk on Learning Today: Neuroscience, Digital Technologies, and Distraction on May 13th from 11 - 12:45pm. Please review session details. Registration required by May 5th. We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:32:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/04/01/2025/teaching-learning-collaboratory-person-spring-event-learning</guid></item></channel></rss>
