<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Got a Residential Meal Plan? You’ve Got Guest Swipes!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/new-guest-swipe-benefit-residential-meal-plan-holders</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Good news students! If you have a residential meal plan you now have 4 Guest Swipes to use.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/new-guest-swipe-benefit-residential-meal-plan-holders</guid></item><item><title>Counseling Center Announces Drop-in Counseling Hours for Fall 2025</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/drop-counseling-hours-fall-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI Counseling Center invites students to meet with a counselor without a formal appointment, during designated drop-in hours. There are two hours available for walk-in each day (M/F - 10 a.m. to 12 p.m.; T/W/Th - 2 to 4 p.m.). Drop-in counseling is available on a first come, first served basis on days when classes are in session. Students who cannot attend drop-in times can call (518) 276-6479 to schedule an appointment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/drop-counseling-hours-fall-2025</guid></item><item><title>Cognitive Science Undergraduate Information Session | Sept. 13</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cognitive-science-undergraduate-information-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you considering a major or dual-major in Cognitive Science, Psychological Science, or Philosophy? Please join us on Wednesday, September 3 in Carnegie 113 at 12pm for FREE PIZZA! Learn about degree requirements, dual-major opportunities, the BS+MS co-term program, and hear about active research going on in the Cognitive Science department from faculty and graduate students. You will also learn about opportunities to get involved in research through the Undergraduate Research Program (URP).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cognitive-science-undergraduate-information-session</guid></item><item><title>Student Insurance Plan Change for 2025 - 2026</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/student-insurance-plan-change-2025-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI student health insurance plan has renewed for the 2025-2026 year. There are no changes to the insurance benefits and there is no increase in the health insurance fee. However, there has been a change in the insurance carrier. The new carrier is Aetna. Students are encouraged to complete enrollment on the insurance portal to activate their health insurance benefits. The deadline to waive out of the plan is September 1st.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/student-insurance-plan-change-2025-2026</guid></item><item><title>Level Up with Lally Clubs | Sept. 4</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/level-lally-clubs</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for Level Up Lally on September 4th from 5:00–6:00 PM in Lally Hall 104! Kick off the semester by connecting with RCC and Lally’s top clubs, including Women in Business, Finance Club, and the Business Honors Society. Meet upperclassmen and alumni, learn how to get involved in real-world projects, and discover the club that best aligns with your goals. Contact: saunde2@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/level-lally-clubs</guid></item><item><title>Calling all new students! Join us for RPI Libraries’ Open House (pssst… there’s ice cream and raffle prizes!) | Sept. 3</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/calling-all-new-students-join-us-rpi-libraries-open-house-pssst-theres-ice-cream-and</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, Sept 3 from 2-3:30pm. Enjoy some ice cream and enter to win raffle prizes from local establishments. Complete your raffle entry card by visiting each library station to learn about our services, including the library’s service desk, discovery tool, individual and group study rooms, interlibrary loan, LibKey Nomad, the Architecture Library, Institute Archives, and the Student Success Center.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/calling-all-new-students-join-us-rpi-libraries-open-house-pssst-theres-ice-cream-and</guid></item><item><title>Annual State Fire Inspections in Residential Buildings Begin September 3</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/annual-state-fire-inspections-residential-buildings-begin-september-3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The New York State Office of Fire Prevention and Control (OFPC) conducts annual building inspections of all college and universities across the state. Inspections of RPI residential buildings will begin on September 3, 2025, and are expected to take approximately three to four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/annual-state-fire-inspections-residential-buildings-begin-september-3</guid></item><item><title>Fellowship info Session to Highlight Competitions for Grad School Salary and Tuition | Sept. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-aeefb2db-000063d1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 3, 2025 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Competitive fellowships provide salary and tuition for masters and PhD students. Seniors and graduate students will learn how to find and apply to appropriate programs that will fund fall 2026 and beyond. Programs are available for all stages of your academic career. International students are welcome! Register for the virtual session. Email madige@rpi.edu for information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-aeefb2db-000063d1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>A Night of A Cappella | Sept. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-0601045a-00000539calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 3, 2025 8:00 PM - 10:00 PM - Get to know RPI’s 5 a cappella groups in our first performance of the semester! You will get to meet all of the members from each group, engage in some fun warm-up and ice breakers, as well as hear short performances from each group. We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-0601045a-00000539calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>NSF Graduate Research Fellowship Information Session Scheduled for Sept. 10th.</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-af095d54-000051c0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 10, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - NSF GRFP provides three years of salary and tuition for Masters or PhD students. Seniors, 1st and 2nd year grad students are invited to learn about the award, eligibility, and how to apply. U.S. citizens and permanent residents in 35+ STEM fields are welcome. &lt;a href="https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV_bHneSByWlXEJeOW"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://graduate.rpi.edu/funding-and-fellowships/nationally-competitive-fellowships"&gt;visit the…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-af095d54-000051c0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; GE Vernova Info Session | Sept. 9</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-ge-vernova-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;GE Vernova will be on campus on Tuesday, September 9th for an info session. Come learn more about the company and available opportunities to work with them! Additional details are available in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-ge-vernova-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Parents dine at no cost in Campus Dining Halls</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/parents-dine-no-cost-campus-dining-halls</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Students with a residential meal plan (Unlimited,19 On Demand,15 On Demand,12 On Demand,5 On Demand), great news, your parents can dine with you at no cost at any campus dining hall from August 28, 2025 to December 22, 2025!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/parents-dine-no-cost-campus-dining-halls</guid></item><item><title>Deep Dive into Webex Webinar Advanced Features Offered Monday September 8</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/deep-dive-webex-webinar-advanced-features-offered-monday-september-8</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jim Evans, Director of MultiMedia Services, will be providing a deep dive into the Webex Webinar application: learn how to customize your webinar and how to work with the data after the webinar is done. This training is open to all members of the Rensselaer community and will be conducted remotely via Webex. Please register in advance for this event which will occur on Monday, September 8 from 10am to 11:30am: https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/rd49009520e351dc5f068fee4d79a77cd&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/deep-dive-webex-webinar-advanced-features-offered-monday-september-8</guid></item><item><title>Permit Enforcement Resumes: September 2, 2025</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/parking-permit-enforcement-resumes-september-2-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All parking gates will be fully operational, and regular enforcement of parking permit policies will resume. Please ensure you are parked in your designated areas and that your permit is active.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/parking-permit-enforcement-resumes-september-2-2025</guid></item><item><title>CMDIS Facilities Open House | Sept. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-9aaa9d40-00003b9ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 3, 2025 10:00 AM - 5:00 PM - Center for Materials, Devices and Integrated Systems (CMDIS) invites you to the Facilities Open House. Sign-up for facility tours to learn about new acquisitions, tools, instrumentation capabilities, fabrication and characterization techniques. Get information about educational programs and short courses. Meet with our technical team and discuss how we can help your research. The event will be followed by BBQ. Sign-up to tours by 08/29.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-9aaa9d40-00003b9ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Information Session Friday, September 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f73e0b-00003baecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 5, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., will be reviewing the online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates. Expect to hear details about how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment. Please RSVP if you plan to attend and learn more about Rensselaer at Work.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f73e0b-00003baecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>New Jersey | Amazon Fulfillment Center Tour | Oct. 22</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10796&amp;cid=24386&amp;ecid=24386&amp;ciid=83520&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: 10/22/2025 10:45 AM to 2:30 PM Ever wonder how Amazon gets your packages to you so quickly? Here is your chance to go on a behind-the-scenes tour at the Amazon Fulfillment Center in Edison, NJ. Mario Munoz ’07 will lead RPI alumni on a private guided tour and show you in real time how orders are fulfilled. Space is extremely limited, and you can bring only one guest (age 6 or over). We will have lunch nearby after the tour. Please register ASAP so you won’t miss out.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10796&amp;cid=24386&amp;ecid=24386&amp;ciid=83520&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO announces upcoming upgrade to SIS</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-announces-upcoming-upgrade-sis</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Members of DotCIO’s Enterprise Information Services team are pleased to announce upcoming changes to SIS (Student Information System) on Wednesday September 17. This upgrade brings a fresh look, improved navigation, and a more user-friendly experience. Please click in for a link to a short video providing a tour of the new landing page and where to find the tools you use most.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-announces-upcoming-upgrade-sis</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials” | Sept. 4</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-429a692f-0000699dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 4, 2025 9:00 AM - 4:30 PM - In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience a “day in the life” of a Supervisor. In addition, the importance of managing employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-429a692f-0000699dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff In-Person Workshop: Tips for Incorporating Digital Story Telling as Assignments | Sept. 8</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-be9de0be-00007c23calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 8, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - In this workshop we will discuss a high overview of the meaning of digital story telling, advantages, story telling assignment practices, and review the Six-Word Story, Six Unique Shots assignment concept. Maureen Fodera (Office of Undergraduate Education) will be presenting this workshop. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-be9de0be-00007c23calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
