<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>New Graduate Student Welcome to be Held August 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8d8f1ce6-018e-148872cd-00007d4fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, August 27, 2024 12:00 PM - 6:00 PM - Following check-in and a boxed lunch, this event will feature a welcome and introductions, a student panel, small group breakout sessions, a resource fair, and a coffee hour with all graduate students.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8d8f1ce6-018e-148872cd-00007d4fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ARCH 2024 Post-Summer Semester Feedback Survey Now Available</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/arch-2024-post-summer-semester-feedback-survey-now-available</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As the Arch semester ends, the Arch leadership team would like to know about your experience this summer, so please take a few minutes to share feedback about the Arch summer semester by completing the survey sent to your email. You have a very important role to play in our efforts to continuously improve the Arch summer semester experience!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/arch-2024-post-summer-semester-feedback-survey-now-available</guid></item><item><title>Habitat for Humanity Offering Opportunity During Freshman Orientation</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-6ab44bba-00005684calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, August 31, 2024 7:30 AM - 2:30 PM - In partnership with a local community chapter in Massachusetts, Rensselaer’s Habitat for Humanity Club will provide this “Beyond block” opportunity for freshmen, featuring an all-day build that will include lunch. No experience is necessary, but space is limited to 15, so &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/BMZRSKigjDAkptLe7"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; early! Participants need to bring long pants and closed-toe shoes/boots, and meet at 7:30AM at the Union horseshoe.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-6ab44bba-00005684calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Adobe Creative Cloud discounted subscription for Students</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/adobe-creative-cloud-discounted-subscription-students-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO will be offering Students an option to purchase Adobe Creative Cloud through Rensselaer at a significant discount over Adobe’s normal student pricing. Pricing is as posted and subject to change at any time. Currently licenses purchased through Rensselaer will cost $110 and will be valid from activation through the following summer term or until you are no longer an active Rensselaer student, whichever comes first. Please view the full announcement for details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/adobe-creative-cloud-discounted-subscription-students-0</guid></item><item><title>Middle States Accreditation Community Open Forum Event Scheduled for August 27</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/12/2024/middle-states-accreditation-community-open-forum-event</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 2:00PM to 3:00PM on Tuesday, August 27, the Middle States Committee will be hosting an open forum to present the findings of the Middle States Self-Study draft and obtain additional feedback. The in-person event will take place in the CBIS Isermann Auditorium; participants can also choose to attend the forum remotely via Webex.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/12/2024/middle-states-accreditation-community-open-forum-event</guid></item><item><title>Webex Education Connector Becomes Webex LTI Legacy</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-education-connector-becomes-webex-lti-legacy</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As of June 2024, the Webex Education Connector — utilized to embed Webex meetings in a course in Blackboard — has been migrated to the Webex LTI Legacy tool, which has been updated and improved, and has a new look. Please watch for more changes the week of August 19!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-education-connector-becomes-webex-lti-legacy</guid></item><item><title>OUE Announces ChatGPT/AI Tools Informal Community Space</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/06/05/2024/chatgptai-tools-informal-community-space</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Education is pleased to announce that an informal community Webex space has been created to focus directly on AI tools being used in the classroom, and is available to share, collaborate, and brainstorm on this topic. Faculty, staff, or graduate TAs who would like to join this space should &lt;a href="mailto:foderm@rpi.edu?subject=Please%20add%20me%20to%20the%20ChatGPT%2FAI%20Tools%20Informal%20Webex%20Space"&gt;email Maureen Fodera&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/06/05/2024/chatgptai-tools-informal-community-space</guid></item><item><title>Invite CCPD to Your Classroom or Club/Organization!</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/invite-ccpd-your-classroom-or-cluborganization</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to inspire and prepare students for the professional world, Rensselaer’s Center for Career Development is here to help! CCPD’s team provides tailored presentations on a range of career-related topics, and can come into your class, club, or organizations meeting to present on a topic of your choosing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/invite-ccpd-your-classroom-or-cluborganization</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity to Offer Confidential Retirement Consultation by Phone, Zoom Video Option</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f958e1e-00006125calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 4, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f958e1e-00006125calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HR to Present “Helping Families Eat Healthier” Brunch with Benefits</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/brunch-benefits-helping-families-eat-healthier</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Division of Human Resources is pleased to present its next virtual Brunch with Benefits session 11:00 a.m. to noon on Thursday, August 22. Led by Registered Dietitian Lindsey Cumoletti, August’s session will focus on “Helping Families Eat Healthier;” CDPHP representatives from will also be available to answer any questions related to the health plan. &lt;a href="https://cdphp.zoom.us/webinar/register/WN_U029L9csRfG1nb0vRUJaHQ#/registration"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; for this session today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/brunch-benefits-helping-families-eat-healthier</guid></item><item><title>Fac/Staff Webinar to Offer Tips for Incorporating Digital Story-Telling as Assignments</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-6b1d2eb5-000069facalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, August 29, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/rbe59e228c4d004c5e65953216858eed2"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Maureen Fodera of Rensselaer’s Office of Undergraduate Education as she gives a high overview of the meaning of digital story-telling, discusses its advantages and assignment practices, and also reviews the Six-Word Story, Six Unique Shots assignment concept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-6b1d2eb5-000069facalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
