<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Congressman Tonko to Announce Community Projects Investing in Higher Education in the Capital Region</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-018f-c4b0759b-000043d5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 31, 2024 1:00 PM - Congressman Paul Tonko will be joined by representatives and supporters of the three out his 15 Community Projects focused on investing in the Capital Region’s higher education institutions: RPI, UAlbany, and HVCC. The discussion will educate the Capital Region community and the media on each project’s details and impact; how the projects’ federal funding will improve the lives of Capital Region residents; and how the Congressman will champion these projects in the federal budget.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-018f-c4b0759b-000043d5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ICAD 2024 Scheduled for June 24-28</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/research/2024/icad-2024-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled for June 24-28, 2024, the International Conference on Auditory Display is a highly interdisciplinary conference with relevance to researchers, practitioners, artists, and graduate students working with sound to convey and explore information, and is unique in its specific focus on auditory displays and the range of interdisciplinary issues related to their use.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/research/2024/icad-2024-0</guid></item><item><title>RPI Athletics Announces Let’s Go Red! Golf Outing for 2024</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=9794&amp;cid=22489&amp;ecid=22489&amp;ciid=78790&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI Athletics is pleased to announce that it will host its annual Let’s Go Red! Golf Outing from 8AM to 3PM on Monday, June 3 at Normanside Country Club in Delmar, New York. You can help support RPI Athletics at this event by registering to play, becoming a sponsor, or providing auction and raffle items, so come out and support Rensselaer’s student-athletes and Athletics programs!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=9794&amp;cid=22489&amp;ecid=22489&amp;ciid=78790&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Systems Engineering &amp; Technology Management Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-349153c3-00001505calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 4, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Hosted by Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., this information session focuses on Rensselaer’s flexible, project-based, online Systems Engineering and Technology Management graduate degree that will help prepare decision-makers with broader and deeper capabilities in leading dynamic organizations. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/SETM4"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-349153c3-00001505calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Every Day Matters: A Human Approach to Generative AI</title><link>https://everydaymatters.rpi.edu/a-human-approach-to-generative-ai/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-human-approach-to-generative-ai</link><description>&lt;p&gt;At the Bicentennial Commencement, Emily Warren Roebling was awarded the first posthumous honorary doctorate in Rensselaer’s history, with actor Liz Wisan portraying her in the ceremony and at Colloquy and delivering remarks that were generated by an AI trained on her writings and historical archives. Every Day Matters asked Jim Hendler, who led the team’s generative AI work, how RPI’s AI research helped bridge the 19th and 21st centuries and how it adds to our understanding of generative AI.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://everydaymatters.rpi.edu/a-human-approach-to-generative-ai/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-human-approach-to-generative-ai</guid></item><item><title>Mueller Center Continues Summer Outdoor Program Series with Intro to Rock Climbing</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-aaaaf2af-00001a24calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 5, 2024 8:00 AM - 3:00 PM - Arch students are invited to join the Mueller Center’s trip to Little Falls, New York for an introduction to rock climbing! Registration is required, and each session has a maximum of ten participants; please &lt;a href="mailto:atkine2@rp.edu"&gt;contact Emma Atkinson&lt;/a&gt; in the Mueller Center to sign up or if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-aaaaf2af-00001a24calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Syllabus Available for Summer Term</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-available-summer-term</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer faculty should note that the HelioCampus (formerly known as AEFIS) syllabus module will be available to access for the Spring Term on April 29. Based on the requirements from the Provost’s office, faculty should have their syllabi published by June 3; HelioCampus will publish the syllabi automatically on June 10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-available-summer-term</guid></item></channel></rss>
