<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Lally Co-Terminal Info Session for Computer Science Majors — FREE PIZZA + WINGS</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/lally-co-terminal-info-session-computer-science-majors-free-pizza-wings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Oct. 23 | 6:00 PM | Lally 102 Stand out in a tough tech job market. Learn how to earn your MBA or M.S. at Lally while finishing your CS degree. Boost your résumé with business, leadership, and innovation skills that set you apart in AI, data, and software careers. We’ll cover program options, admissions steps, and how to make it work for you. Pizza + wings provided! Register Here- https://forms.gle/KUNPqVVAZo3VHjht8&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/lally-co-terminal-info-session-computer-science-majors-free-pizza-wings</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 School of Engineering Midterm Student Course Evaluations Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-9b46c654-00003336calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 10, 2025 (all day) - Fall 2025 School of Engineering (SoE) Midterm course evaluations are now open. Your feedback is very important to the Institute and the school, so please complete the SoE midterm evaluation surveys for all your courses! Evaluations will be available through Thursday, October 23, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-9b46c654-00003336calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Open house tours of rentals - Saturday 10-noon | Oct. 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-f327da46-0000721ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 24, 2025 10:00 AM - 12:00 PM - 8 rental properties will be available to tour and meet owners/leasing managers. See link for properties and contact info and stop at as many as you would like to see.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-f327da46-0000721ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>NSF GRFP Application News and Reviews | Oct. 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-06e3014a-00000d98calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 23, 2025 (all day) - Students applying to the NSF GRFP are highly encouraged to seek review of your documents from the Fellowship Advisor. NSF has changed the formatting requirements for applications and the advisor will check to make sure your documents are compliant and free of technical issues. Email them at least 2 weeks before the deadline to Betty Madigan at madige@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-06e3014a-00000d98calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MANE Department seminar series to continue with Van C. Mow Distinguished Lecture in Applied Mechanics | Oct. 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-06cf5cdb-00001a8acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 22, 2025 10:30 AM - 11:30 AM - Van C. Mow Distinguished Lecture in Applied Mechanics, Dawn Elliot, University of Delaware&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-06cf5cdb-00001a8acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HASS Family Weekend Music Showcase on Saturday October 25</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/hass-family-weekend-music-showcase</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This program features the RPI Orchestra, Concert Choir, and Wind Symphony in a musical preview of works that will be included on the Dec. 6th RPI Holiday Concert, including Mark Camphouse’s “A Movement for Rosa”, Christopher Tin’s “Baba Yetu”, and Bedrich Smetana’s “Die Moldau”. Admission is free. Showcase starts at 2:30pm in DCC 308.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/hass-family-weekend-music-showcase</guid></item><item><title>2025 RPI Graduate School Expo | Oct. 23</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-rpi-graduate-school-expo</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Register for the CCPD’s Graduate School Expo! On Thursday, October 23rd, all students are welcome to interact with graduate schools and learn about their programs. This event will be from 1-4pm in Sage Banquet Hall. Whether you’re actively applying to grad schools, just beginning to consider it, or aren’t sure if it’s the decision you’ll make, this is a great opportunity to meet with graduate school representatives (including RPI!). Learn more, register, and view attending schools in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-rpi-graduate-school-expo</guid></item><item><title>Family Weekend 2025 | Oct. 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-810f070e-000040f9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 24, 2025 8:00 AM - 9:00 AM - We’re excited to welcome families to campus for a special weekend honoring the achievements and talents of our incredible students. From dynamic performances and interactive classes to thrilling athletic events, you’ll get a firsthand look at what makes the RPI community so exceptional. Enjoy the lively atmosphere of Fall Fest, celebrate academic excellence at the Honors Convocation, and experience RPI traditions at the Grand Marshal/President…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-810f070e-000040f9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Dr. Azita Hirsa Receives the Rensselaer Alumni Association (RAA) Teaching Award</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/dr-azita-hirsa-receives-raa-teaching-award</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Industrial and Systems Engineering Department proudly celebrates Dr. Azita Hirsa, recipient of the RAA Teaching Award. Dr. Hirsa’s courses in professional development, ethics, and management of engineering and technology inspire students to connect technical excellence with integrity, purpose, and collaboration. “Students learn best when they feel supported, challenged, and seen as collaborators in our learning journey,” said Dr. Hirsa. “This recognition affirms that those efforts matter.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/dr-azita-hirsa-receives-raa-teaching-award</guid></item><item><title>2025 BioInnovation Forum: Frontiers of Biotechnology (Tuesday, October 28th)</title><link>https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-bioinnovation-forum-frontiers-biotechnology</link><description>&lt;p&gt;CBIS played a significant role in organizing the upcoming 2025 BioInnovation Forum: Frontiers of Biotechnology, and we hope you’ll join us - It’s a great opportunity for post-docs &amp;amp; early career faculty to present their work as part of the poster session! Check out the link for FREE registration.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-bioinnovation-forum-frontiers-biotechnology</guid></item><item><title>Department of Economics Fall Seminar Series Presents Dr. Gagan Ghosh on 10/22</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/department-economics-fall-seminar-series-dr-gagan-ghosh-cal-state-fullerton-1022</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Economics is excited to welcome Dr. Gagan Ghosh, who will be presenting “Product varieties, private costs and price competition” on Wednesday, October 22 at 3:30 PM in SAGE 5101. We encourage all interested members of the RPI community to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/department-economics-fall-seminar-series-dr-gagan-ghosh-cal-state-fullerton-1022</guid></item><item><title>Artist Mary Mattingly Speaks on October 22</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-mary-mattingly-proposals-commons</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Artist Mary Mattingly will discuss her recent work with an emphasis on Swale, a mobile, community-led food access initiative that transforms NYC waterways into civic spaces for environmental and economic justice. Built on a repurposed barge, Swale serves communities where it remains illegal to forage on public land, providing free access to perennial fruits, herbs, and vegetables while educating the public on sustainable food systems and land rights. West Hall 113 or Webex on Oct. 22 at 6pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-mary-mattingly-proposals-commons</guid></item><item><title>Webex vs Teams: Choosing the Right Tool for Your Campus Workflows | Oct. 24</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-vs-teams-choosing-right-tool-your-campus-workflows</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The campus community has access to both Cisco Webex and Microsoft Teams, but which is best for your needs? Join us on Friday, October 24, 2025, 10-11:30am for a practical, fast-paced session comparing the strengths of each platform. Whether you’re teaching, hosting a symposium, collaborating on a grant proposal, or streamlining your team’s communication, we’ll help you match the right tool to the task. Register at https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/r4235dc39258dd1620e7365907d91af2d&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-vs-teams-choosing-right-tool-your-campus-workflows</guid></item><item><title>Run to Remember 5k!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-01bc217a-000064b5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, October 20, 2025 12:00 AM - Sat , October 25, 2025 12:00 AM - The Run to Remember 5k–brought to the Troy community by the Jack Newkirk Squadron of Arnold Air Society–is a family friendly, community wide event aimed at supporting local veterans, as well as current college students. All are welcome to enjoy this event. This year, we are proud to be partnering with Mission 22, a non-profit organization dedicated to offering free mental health, wellness, and community support…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-01bc217a-000064b5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar – “Certifications &amp; Skill Development in Percipio”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-certifications-skill</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This course introduces the tools available in Percipio to support growth through certifications and skill benchmarks. You’ll learn how to identify relevant certifications and use benchmark assessments to measure current knowledge. Perfect for employees and supervisors alike, this session will help you navigate the platform’s upskilling features and align learning with career development objectives.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-certifications-skill</guid></item><item><title>Save The Date! Faculty and Staff Benefits Expo - November 7, 2025</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/save-date-faculty-and-staff-benefits-expo-november-7-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Empower your wellbeing and make the most of your benefits. Join us on Friday, November 7th at the East Campus Athletic Village (ECAV) from 10:30am - 2pm for the 2025 Faculty and Staff Benefits Expo—your one-stop shop for insights, resources, support and LUNCH!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/save-date-faculty-and-staff-benefits-expo-november-7-2025</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty Quick Learn Webinar: Tips for Planning Your Condensed Course | Oct. 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-f2b02644-000038bfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 30, 2025 11:00 AM - 11:30 AM - The Planning Your Condensed Course webinar is meant to assist instructors teaching in The Arch or short semester courses in planning and presenting their course material in innovative, effective, and carefully considered ways. In this webinar we will offer quick tips on best practices in condensing coursework. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-f2b02644-000038bfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
