<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>New Minor in Behavioral Data Science</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-behavioral-data-science</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new interdisciplinary minor is now available for students interested in the intersection between data science and human behavior. The Behavioral Data Science minor combines psychological science, statistics, and computational methods to analyze, predict, and influence human behavior across a wide range of real-world contexts. Minor requirements can be found in the RPI catalog. For questions, please contact the School of HASS advising hub at HASSinfo@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-behavioral-data-science</guid></item><item><title>LLMs and R: How Posit is Making it Easy: RPIrates Monthly Meeting (Weds, 12 Nov, 6p, AE217)</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/llms-and-r-how-posit-making-it-easy-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-12-nov-6p-ae217</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI R users are invited to the November 2025 meeting of RPIrates: The RPI R Users Group! Our topic for Weds, 12 Nov (6p, AE217) will be “LLMs and R: How Posit is Making it Easy!” In this session we’ll review the many ways that Posit, the creators of RStudio, is supporting data analytics that tightly integrates popular LLMs. RPIrates is led by Dr. John S. Erickson, Dir. of Research Operations of the Rensselaer IDEA and Chief Instigator of RPIrates. Pizza and salad starts at 5:30p.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/llms-and-r-how-posit-making-it-easy-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-12-nov-6p-ae217</guid></item><item><title>Interested in combining engineering or science with business? | Nov. 13</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/interested-combining-engineering-or-science-business</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for an information session on the Accelerated Eng/Sci + MBA program! Learn how you can earn both your undergraduate and graduate degrees in 5 years or less through our accelerated pathway. Discover how this program can help you stand out in today’s competitive job market by pairing technical expertise with business leadership skills. Register for our next virtual information session Thursday Nov 13 at 2:30pm here: https://apply.rpi.edu/register/?id=187e4a9d-01c4-418a-9f12-f207ef707c46&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/interested-combining-engineering-or-science-business</guid></item><item><title>DoD S.M.A.R.T. application reviews now available!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-6e94f0eb-00004ffbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 10, 2025 12:00 AM - Mon , December 1, 2025 12:00 PM - Students applying to the DoD S.M.A.R.T. Scholars program are encouraged to seek application assistance and review from the DoD on-campus support advisor. The program provides one-five years of salary and full tuition for undergraduate and graduate students with guaranteed work post-graduation. Send application drafts and/or questions to Betty Madigan madige@rpi.edu before the December 5th deadline.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-6e94f0eb-00004ffbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Simply to Go Hours of Operations Update</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/simply-go-hours-operations-update</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting Tuesday, November 11, 2025, Simply to Go at Russell Sage Dining Hall will open at 7:15 AM each morning!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/simply-go-hours-operations-update</guid></item><item><title>Mercer XLab 2025 Take It, Break It, Make It Contest</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-2025-take-it-break-it-make-it-contest</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mercer X Take It, Break It, Make It 2025 edition is here! You (and your collaborators) can take apart and reconstruct, in your own innovative way, anything that helps you learn: electronic hardware, software, theoretical models. Show your creativity and depth of knowledge by reverse-engineering and then making something new! Fill out the 2025 Take It, Break It, Make It participation form by December 20th. Your video submission is due January 12th. Email sawyes@rpi.edu for more details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-2025-take-it-break-it-make-it-contest</guid></item><item><title>Altium Designer Certification Workshop, Saturday, November 15th</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/altium-designer-certification-workshop-saturday-november-15th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mercer X Lab, in collaboration with the Future Semiconductor Transitions Program, is offering a remote Altium Designer certification course on Saturday, November 15th, 2025. The 6-8 hour long workshop begins at 10:00 a.m. EST. Click the Prepare for an Altium Workshop Mercer X Education Module to REGISTER or email sawyes@rpi.edu. Participants earn an official Altium Certificate and a Mercer XLab PCB Design Badge when completed. An optional design challenge follows the workshop!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/altium-designer-certification-workshop-saturday-november-15th</guid></item><item><title>BME Career Panel Nov. 13</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-73bc4d60-00001158calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 13, 2025 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Join BMEGC, CBIS GPA, and CCPD for a Career Panel. Representatives from Applied BioPhysics, Taconic, and the New York State Department of Health will come to deliver a short talk on their career paths and answer audience questions. Come network with local professionals and ask questions about the hiring process, their career paths, and their fields. Refreshments at 2:30, event starts at 3pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-73bc4d60-00001158calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Department of Economics Fall Seminar Series Presents Dr. Stephen Wu on 11/19</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/health-effects-urgent-care-center-entry-case-wellnow-dr-stephen-wu</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Economics is excited to welcome Dr. Stephen Wu, who will be presenting “Health Effects of Urgent Care Center Entry: The Case of WellNow” on Wednesday, November 19 at 3:30 PM in SAGE 5101. We encourage all interested members of the RPI community to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/health-effects-urgent-care-center-entry-case-wellnow-dr-stephen-wu</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents: Artists Felici Asteinza and Joey Fillastre on 11/12</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-artists-felici-asteinza-and-joey-fillastre</link><description>&lt;p&gt;MILAGROS co-founders Felici Asteinza and Joey Fillastre, along with their ever-changing cast of collaborators, create site-specific works that explore the history of place through striking arrangements of color and mark. With an exuberant style that champions the hand made and the intuitive, MILAGROS energizes public spaces with effervescent patterns that obliterate the seams between structures and highlight the unique attributes of the surrounding architecture. Join virtually at 6pm on 11/12.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-artists-felici-asteinza-and-joey-fillastre</guid></item><item><title>MMS Collaboration Software Training Series: Webex Event Training | Nov. 13</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/mms-collaboration-software-training-series-webex-event-training</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Planning a virtual event or supporting a student webinar? Join us for a practical walkthrough of Webex Events as part of the MMS Collaboration Software Training Series. Register now for this webinar presented via Webex on Thursday November 13, 2025 from 11am-12pm: https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/r4f44a1f130dd0f14e0e8989c146e99b3 Learn how to: - Schedule and brand your event - Use polls, Q&amp;amp;A, and chat tools - Access recordings and reports - Host with confidence&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/mms-collaboration-software-training-series-webex-event-training</guid></item><item><title>Procurement Services to Present Supplier Showcase on December 4</title><link>https://procurement.rpi.edu/announcements/procurement-services-host-10th-annual-supplier-showcase</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All faculty, staff, and students involved in RPI’s procurement process are invited to attend this year’s Supplier Showcase, which will be held from 11:00am to 2:00pm on Thursday, December 4 in the Alumni Sports &amp;amp; Recreation Center. Stop by to network with RPI’s key suppliers and the Procurement team, get your professional head shot taken, win exciting raffle prizes, have some fun in the photo booth, and enjoy a sparkling spread of savory and sweet treats from campus and local shops!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://procurement.rpi.edu/announcements/procurement-services-host-10th-annual-supplier-showcase</guid></item><item><title>RPI Quantum Users Group Meeting (Weds, 12 Nov, 4p, AE217)</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/qiskitsession-and-initialize-and-statevector-functions-rpi-quantum-users-group-meeting-weds</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The next meeting of the Quantum Users’ Group will be held at 4pm on Wednesday November 12 in AE 217. We will discuss Qiskit_session and the initialize and statevector functions plus topics of concern from the attendees.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/qiskitsession-and-initialize-and-statevector-functions-rpi-quantum-users-group-meeting-weds</guid></item><item><title>STS Colloquium: Everyone Communicates: Making Social Worlds and Valued People in the Present | Nov. 12</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-everyone-communicates-making-social-worlds-and-valued-people-present</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this talk, Michele Friedner (Comparative Human Development, University of Chicago) analyzes how special educators at a school for children with intellectual disabilities in India engage in collaborative sense-making projects with the children with whom they work (although there is the question of what collaboration actually means) and in the process they create create rich social worlds that are oriented towards the present and the near future. Join us 11/12 at 11:30am in Sage 5711.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-everyone-communicates-making-social-worlds-and-valued-people-present</guid></item><item><title>CANCELLED: CEE Fall Seminar Series - Dr. Grigorios Lavrentiadis Asst. Professor from the University of Buffalo | Nov. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-77dd03ab-00007a99calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Cancelled due to the weather. Wednesday, November 12, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - “A Non-Ergodic Ground Motion Model for the Groningen, Netherlands:&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-77dd03ab-00007a99calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Thank you from the Office of Admissions!</title><link>https://undergrad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/thank-you-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We just want to take a moment to say thank you to everyone across campus who helped make our fall admissions events such a success! Across the five events, we hosted 836 prospective students (a total of 2,240 visitors).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/thank-you-0</guid></item><item><title>Reflections on Waterways Symposium | Nov. 14</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-symposium-explores-art-environment-and-legacy-erie-canal</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The School of Humanities, Arts, and Social Sciences at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI), in collaboration with the Albany Symphony, the New York State Canal Corporation, and the New York Power Authority, will host a symposium titled Reflections on Waterways: Intersections of Arts, Culture, and the Environment in New York on Friday, November 14, 2025, from 9:30 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. in the Center For Biotechnology and Interdisciplinary Studies (CBIS) Auditorium at RPI. The symposium revisits…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-symposium-explores-art-environment-and-legacy-erie-canal</guid></item><item><title>New Roth 403(b) Catch-Up Rule: Fidelity Webinar | Nov. 14</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-5b1062e3-00004e20calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, November 14, 2025 11:00 AM - 11:45 AM - Starting January 1, 2026, a new rule under the SECURE 2.0 Act, will impact how certain employees can make catch-up contributions to their retirement plans. If you’re turning age 50 or older in 2026 and your total 2025 FICA wages (Box 3 on your 2025 form W-2) are over $145,000, any catch-up contributions you make in 2026 must be made as after-tax Roth contributions. Learn more by joining Fidelity’s educational webinar at https://fmr.zoom.us…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-5b1062e3-00004e20calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Leading from Anywhere” | Nov. 14</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-bf26e3c9-00003ab9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, November 14, 2025 9:00 AM - 11:30 AM - In this workshop, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership not as positional or based on title, but rather on values and actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:34:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-bf26e3c9-00003ab9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
