<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>An Internal Invitation to Sign Up for the Qiskit Global Summer School</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/internal-invitation-sign-qiskit-global-summer-school</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI will once again be sponsoring a cohort of participants in the Qiskit Global Summer School this year, with the online program scheduled to run July 15 - 26. The Qiskit Global Summer School is a two-week intensive summer program designed to empower the quantum researchers and developers of tomorrow with the know-how to explore the world of quantum computing, as well as refresh and sharpen the industry professional’s skills.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/internal-invitation-sign-qiskit-global-summer-school</guid></item><item><title>From Multimedia Services: New MyMediasite Video Editor Now Available</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-new-mymediasite-video-editor-now-available</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the Rensselaer community that the MyMediasite multimedia video system now has a new video editor with increased functionality that is immediately available to everyone with access to MyMediaite for recorded and uploaded videos. Please see the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/articles/26717262422157"&gt;ITSSC article&lt;/a&gt;, “Editing Video in MyMediasite,” for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-new-mymediasite-video-editor-now-available</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Graduate Certificate Review on June 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-3497f6b4-00002083calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 12, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for this information session highlighting the whole range of Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs. Three courses in length and able to be completed in a year or less, the certificates can add up to a customized, career-aligned master’s degree. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/certs12"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-3497f6b4-00002083calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RAF Announces Mary Ellen Mainello’s Retirement</title><link>https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/mary-ellen-mainello-retirement</link><description>&lt;p&gt;After more than 25 years of service at Rensselaer, Mary Ellen Mainello will be retiring on June 30. On behalf of the Institute, the Division of Research Administration and Finance would like to take this opportunity to thank Mary Ellen for everything that she has done for RPI, and in particular for the Research Finance division. Please join RAF in congratulating Mary Ellen and wishing her well in her future endeavors!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/mary-ellen-mainello-retirement</guid></item><item><title>ECSE/Physics Joint Seminar Scheduled for June 10</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-018f-de70e00a-0000196acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, June 10, 2024 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join Rensselaer’s ECSE and Physics departments for this joint seminar featuring speaker Boon S. Ooi, Professor, Photonics Laboratory, KAUST, who will present “Wide-Bandgap Semiconductors for Quantum Photonics Integration.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-018f-de70e00a-0000196acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Quantum Computing Users Group to Hold Organizational Meeting</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-organizational-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Future of Computing Institute announces the formation of a Quantum Computing Users Group. On Wednesday, June 12, from noon to 2 pm, there will be an organizational meeting in CII 3116. The goals are to find out about the experience and background of interested parties, evaluate what more is needed to enable the campus QC to be used effectively and efficiently, and discuss other subjects the group may find interesting. &lt;a href="mailto:morgat5@rpi.edu"&gt;RSVP to Tom Morgan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-organizational-meeting</guid></item><item><title>Appointments Now Available at COMM+D!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/01/16/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you working on a writing assignment, oral presentation, or visual design project? Whether you’re still in the initial brainstorming stages or finishing up your final revisions, the Center for Global Communication+Design can help, so &lt;a href="https://rpi.mywconline.com/"&gt;schedule an appointment&lt;/a&gt; with a member of COMM+D’s trained staff today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/01/16/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Summer 2024 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-summer-2024-course-requests</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Summer 2024 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-summer-2024-course-requests</guid></item></channel></rss>
