<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Department of Defense graduate funding programs information session to be held March 4th at noon</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-6d45de1c-000001ebcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 4, 2026 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - The National Defense Science and Engineering Graduate Fellowship provides 3 years of tuition and salary for PhD students in STEM fields; there is no service requirement! The SMART Scholarship for Service program provides 1 to 5 years of tuition and salary for undergrads, master’s and PhD Students. Scholars will work in DoD labs during summers and post graduation. &lt;a href="https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV_6L3FFwv0qCROrvE"&gt;Register for link…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-6d45de1c-000001ebcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Student Experience Excellence Awards</title><link>https://studentexperience.rpi.edu/announcements/student-experience-excellence-awards</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Student Experience Excellence Awards (formerly the Graduating Student Awards) recognize RPI students who have made exceptional contributions to our community through academic achievement, athletic accomplishment, leadership, service, and/or volunteerism. We invite students, staff, and faculty to nominate individuals who exemplify excellence and have made a meaningful impact on our campus.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studentexperience.rpi.edu/announcements/student-experience-excellence-awards</guid></item><item><title>Small Group Tutoring Options at the Success Center</title><link>https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/tutoring-appointment-options</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that you can easily book online a small group tutoring session in many of RPI’s upper-level courses? Check out the fantastic small group tutoring sessions being offered at the Success Center!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/tutoring-appointment-options</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC Tour (Registration required)</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2026/empac-tours</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Saturday / February 28, 2026 at 11:00 am EMPAC building tours take visitors behind the scenes to experience the center’s infrastructure as few do. Each one is hosted by an EMPAC staff member with a different area of expertise—so whether you attend one or all this season, there’s always something new to learn and discover. Join us! EMPAC Tours are offered at no cost and begin in the Main Lobby. Please register in advance and plan to arrive 15 minutes before tour start time. Each tour runs…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2026/empac-tours</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO requests feedback on the student laptop program and for help selecting next year’s student laptops</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-requests-feedback-student-laptop-program-and-help-selecting-next-years-student</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mobile Computing Program is asking for feedback from the community to help select the most appropriate laptop models and specifications for this coming year. Additionally, we are seeking general feedback on the program. Please take a few minutes to complete this survey which is open through March 7, 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-requests-feedback-student-laptop-program-and-help-selecting-next-years-student</guid></item><item><title>RPI Recognized Staff for Service Milestones</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-recognized-staff-service-milestones</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI recognized staff at the February 20 Men’s Ice Hockey game for service milestones reached over the past five years, during which formal service recognition has been paused. The celebration brought together over 100 honorees, joined by family and friends, for a total of 450+ attendees— a memorable evening of recognition and appreciation of over 8,500 years of combined service to the Institute.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-recognized-staff-service-milestones</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity Confidential Consultation (By Phone with Zoom Video Option)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-be560004-00000586calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 4, 2026 8:00 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits. To schedule an appointment, call 1-800-642-7131, Monday through Friday, 8:00 am to midnight, or online at https://nb.fidelity.com/public/nbpreloginnav/rpi/microsite/#/tem/meet-with-us&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-be560004-00000586calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff In Person Workshop - Beta Classroom - Teaching with Technology Preview</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c22e423-019c-5378f164-0000229bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 4, 2026 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Come see the Collaboratory space in the main library, and the exciting technologies available to you in the Beta Classroom. The beta classroom is a high technology testing space for interactive learning. The goal of the beta classroom is for faculty to pilot new or interactive technologies and pedagogical approaches that can be recommended for other classrooms on campus. This is also the February 27th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c22e423-019c-5378f164-0000229bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty &amp; Staff Appreciation Lunch - February 26, 2026</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-february-26-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for a Faculty and Staff Appreciation Lunch on Thursday, February 26, 2026, at The Commons and Russell Sage Dining Halls! As a thank you for all that you do, we’re offering a delicious all you care to eat lunch at a special price of just $6.00 plus tax. We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:31:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-february-26-2026</guid></item></channel></rss>
