<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Toys for Tots Campaign Underway through December 8</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-45cabebc-0000789ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 20, 2024 - Sun , December 8, 2024 (all day) - The 2024 holiday season marks the 77th anniversary of the Marine Corps Reserve Toys for Tots Program, and members of the campus community are invited to consider donating a new, unwrapped toy to join in a special nationwide celebration of this significant milestone!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-45cabebc-0000789ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Don’t Miss the Bicentennial Time Capsule Burial Ceremony on December 3!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-643dcf95-00005916calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, December 3, 2024 1:00 PM - In celebration of Rensselaer’s Bicentennial, all members of the campus community are welcome to attend this Time Capsule Burial Ceremony outside of the ’86 Field side of the Troy Building! The time capsule, which will include letters capturing the spirit of RPI in 2024, will commemorate the Institute’s legacy while giving future generations a snapshot of our vibrant community. Cupcakes to follow!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-643dcf95-00005916calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Webex LTI Legacy Upgraded to Webex LTI 1.3 in Blackboard</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</link><description>&lt;p&gt;MultiMedia Services wishes to inform the campus community that Webex LTI Legacy (formerly Webex Education Connector) has been upgraded in Blackboard to the new Webex LTI 1.3 connector. This is the final upgrade prior to the start of the semester, and brings in increased stability and features for utilizing Webex within a course in Blackboard. Please refer to the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/sections/360008224951"&gt;ITSSC Knowledge Base&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</guid></item><item><title>Procurement Services to Present Supplier Showcase on December 5</title><link>https://procurement.rpi.edu/announcements/procurement-services-host-9th-annual-supplier-showcase</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All faculty, staff, and students involved in Rensselaer’s procurement process are invited to attend this year’s Supplier Showcase, which will be held from 11:00am to 2:00pm on Thursday, December 5 in the Alumni Sports &amp;amp; Recreation Center. Stop by to network with Rensselaer’s key suppliers and the Procurement Services team, get your professional head shot taken, win exciting raffle prizes from the suppliers, check out the photo booth, and enjoy festive refreshments!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://procurement.rpi.edu/announcements/procurement-services-host-9th-annual-supplier-showcase</guid></item><item><title>RPI Bicentennial Holiday Concert, Victorian Stroll Kick-Off Scheduled for December 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-29592252-00006133calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, December 7, 2024 7:00 PM - Join us for this Bicentennial celebration, in partnership with the Rensselaer County Regional Chamber of Commerce, that kicks off the Troy Victorian Stroll! The Bicentennial Holiday Concert will feature performances by the Rensselaer Orchestra, Concert Choir, and Wind Symphony, and will include works by Brahms, Holst, Thorvaldsdottir, Wagner, and Borodin.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-29592252-00006133calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MIT’s Professor Mei Hong to Speak December 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-50b8a562-00006db9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, December 5, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Attend this event for an insightful presentation by Professor Mei Hong, a renowned expert in Chemistry from MIT, who will present “Deconstructing and Reconstructing Tau by Solid-State NMR” to delve into the intricate details of tau proteins and their role in neurodegenerative diseases. A meet-and-greet lunch will follow the presentation at 1pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-50b8a562-00006db9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Design Lab Showcase to be Held Wednesday, December 4</title><link>https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-will-host-their-design-showcase-wednesday-december-4-2024-dcc-great-hall</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled to take place from 2:00PM to 5:00PM on Wednesday, December 4 in the DCC Great Hall, the Design Showcase will feature students from multiple engineering disciplines — including Computer &amp;amp; Systems, Electrical, Industrial &amp;amp; Management, Materials and Mechanical Engineering — solving real-world design challenges for industry, entrepreneurs and academic/medical partners.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-will-host-their-design-showcase-wednesday-december-4-2024-dcc-great-hall</guid></item><item><title>Collegiate Store Holding Black Friday Sale Through December 2</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rensselaer-collegiate-store/11/25/2024/black-friday-sale-1125-122</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From now through Monday, December 2, shop ONLINE ONLY to enjoy the Rensselaer Collegiate Store’s annual Black Friday Sale, featuring up to 30% off clothing and gifts!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:33:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rensselaer-collegiate-store/11/25/2024/black-friday-sale-1125-122</guid></item></channel></rss>
