<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CMDIS BYOND Build Your Own Nano Device Program – Applications are Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-b391560b-00006ba7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, January 19, 2026 12:00 AM - 7:00 PM - Spring 2026 Applications Now Open for CMDIS BYOND Build Your Own Nano Device Program. The Center for Materials, Devices and Integrated Systems’, Micro and NanoFabrication Clean Room, offers a four-module certificate program for undergraduates, an exciting opportunity for those planning to pursue a graduate degree or those looking to prepare for a professional career in microelectronics, medical, and energy industries. Applications for the…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-b391560b-00006ba7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Spring 2026 Meal Plan Changes</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-2026-meal-plan-changes</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Students with residential meal plans may request a meal plan downgrade within 7 days of the semester start. For Spring 2026, the deadline is January 18, 2026. Click the link above to find out how to request the change.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-2026-meal-plan-changes</guid></item><item><title>RPI Chemical Hygiene Plan</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-chemical-hygiene-plan</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI Chemical Hygiene Plan (CHP) is annually reviewed by EHS and the new version is available to all RPI Faculty, Staff, and Students on the EHS Chemical Safety website.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-chemical-hygiene-plan</guid></item><item><title>Beyond the Classroom with Andrew Morrison ’87: Preparing for Industry, Innovation, and Impact</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/beyond-classroom-andrew-morrison-87-preparing-industry-innovation-and-impact</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sunday, February 1st, 5 p.m. - 9 p.m., Andrew Morrison, former President of the RPI Student Union and serial entrepreneur who has built multiple million-dollar companies, will offer winning strategies to the RPI community. Implement these strategies in a workshop that will help you make a professional brand, attract a dream career, or launch a business. Dinner will be served. You’ll acquire access to $25,000 in travel scholarships, secrets to securing positions, and pathways to RPI resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/beyond-classroom-andrew-morrison-87-preparing-industry-innovation-and-impact</guid></item><item><title>Campus Card Office Grand Opening</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/campus-card-office-grand-opening</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us at the Campus Card Office on Wednesday, January 21st between 11 am - 2 pm as we celebrate our move back into the Student Union Room 1502. We will have samples from Pepsi and snacks while supplies last. We look forward to seeing you!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/campus-card-office-grand-opening</guid></item><item><title>MLK Day Weekend Dining Halls and Retail Hours Of Operations</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/mlk-day-weekend-dining-halls-and-retail-hours-operations</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In observance of Martin Luther King Jr. Day, campus dining halls and retail locations will have adjusted hours during MLK Day Weekend. Please visit our website for the most up to date hours of operation at each location during this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/mlk-day-weekend-dining-halls-and-retail-hours-operations</guid></item><item><title>RPI Semiconductor CoLab Catalyst Seminar Series – Jan. 20 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-34648d62-00000e91calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, January 20, 2026 3:00 PM - 5:00 PM - The RPI Semiconductor CoLab Catalyst Seminar Series brings together faculty, researchers, and industry partners to share ideas, highlight collaborations, and advance semiconductor and microelectronics innovation. The first seminar, on January 20 at the Albany NanoTech Complex, features Ravishankar Sundararaman (RPI) and Tim Philicelli (IBM) on topological metals in two 45-min talks with a networking break. Registration is required. Follow the…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-34648d62-00000e91calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Webex Application Training Session on Friday January 23, 2026</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-application-training-session-friday-january-23-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on Friday, January 23, from 11am-12pm for a hands-on Webex Training Session, part of the MMS Collaboration Software Training series. This session focuses on the Webex application and its integration with Outlook and Blackboard, so you can efficiently schedule, launch, and manage meetings directly from the tools you use every day. Register now: https://rensselaer.webex.com/webappng/sites/rensselaer/webinar/webinarSeries/register/783d951c6ab8482e9198a7bd6075a700&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-application-training-session-friday-january-23-2026</guid></item><item><title>Faculty Staff Appreciation Lunch January 21st</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-january-21st</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to celebrate you! Please join us for a Faculty and Staff Appreciation Lunch on January 21 as a small thank-you for everything you do to support our campus community. On this special day, faculty and staff are invited to enjoy lunch for just $6 plus tax at Commons and Russell Sage Dining Halls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:58 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-january-21st</guid></item></channel></rss>
