<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Researchers Find That Frogs Can Quickly Increase Their Tolerance to Pesticides</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/16/researchers-find-frogs-can-quickly-increase-their-tolerance-pesticides</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Although there is a large body of research on pests evolving tolerances for the pesticides meant to destroy them, there have been considerably fewer studies on how non-target animals in these ecosystems may do the same. In recently-published research, Rensselaer’s Rick Relyea, Ph.D., professor of biological sciences and David M. Darrin ’40 Senior Endowed Chair, and his team have begun to address this gap in research.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/16/researchers-find-frogs-can-quickly-increase-their-tolerance-pesticides</guid></item><item><title>Former RPI Hockey Captain Named Head Coach of Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/7/16/former-rpi-captain-kirk-macdonald-named-head-coach-of-wilkes-barre-scranton-penguins.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Rensselaer men’s hockey captain Kirk MacDonald ’07 has been named head coach of the Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins of the American Hockey League (AHL). MacDonald, who was most recently the head coach of the Dubuque Fighting Saints of the United States Hockey League (USHL) the past two seasons, played from 2003-2007 with the Engineers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/7/16/former-rpi-captain-kirk-macdonald-named-head-coach-of-wilkes-barre-scranton-penguins.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Print Server Maintenance Scheduled for Evening of July 18</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/print-server-maintenance-scheduled-july-18-6pm-9pm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From approximately 6:00PM to 9:00PM on Thursday, July 18, DotCIO staff will be performing maintenance on the campus printing environment. As a result, there will be a brief outage that will affect all print jobs sent from a large number of printers around the Rensselaer campus.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/print-server-maintenance-scheduled-july-18-6pm-9pm</guid></item><item><title>Nominations Being Sought for RAA Teaching Award</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22919&amp;ecid=22919&amp;ciid=79492&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Nominations are now being accepted for the 2024 Rensselaer Alumni Association (RAA) Teaching Award, which recognizes current members of the faculty for their outstanding teaching techniques, contributions to the campus experience, and commitment to students. Nominations are due by Wednesday, July 31.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22919&amp;ecid=22919&amp;ciid=79492&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Summer Arch 2024 NYC Trip Slated for July 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90976b31-0190-a806c949-000019c0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, July 27, 2024 8:00 AM - The Class of 2026 Council and The Arch Summer Ambassadors would like to invite current Arch students to join them for a day in New York City. Space is limited and registration is required, so &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeNSWwU4gQnmtovupuP2aSdG0RELQmsew7YK4d2eYdAj8bG0g/viewform"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; soon!…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90976b31-0190-a806c949-000019c0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Virtual Summer Series Continues with Crane Currency Info Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2632</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the team at Crane Currency from 6:30PM to 7:30PM on Thursday, July 25 to learn about career paths and company culture within the organization, as well as upcoming opportunities for Arch students seeking an Away experience! Also please review the&lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/edu/jobs/8907483"&gt;Chemical Engineering R&amp;amp;D Internship or Co-Op opportunity&lt;/a&gt; posted in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2632</guid></item><item><title>Training, Resources to Assist Faculty with Adding Questions to End-of-Term Evaluations</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/07/10/2024/faculty-training-heliocampus-adding-additional-questions-summer-i</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Summer I and III end-of-term course evaluations will be open to students August 1-17, with reports available to instructors on September 13; instructors have until July 31 to add questions to their courses using HelioCampus. The Office of Undergraduate Education will offer training; self-help information is available on the &lt;a href="https://provost.rpi.edu/faculty-resources/heliocampus-formerly-aefis-assessment-tool/heliocampus-formerly-aefis-support"&gt;HelioCampus Resource Site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/07/10/2024/faculty-training-heliocampus-adding-additional-questions-summer-i</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review Scheduled for July 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4ab5324c-000059aecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 24, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MBAP24"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Participants will learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with real-world MBA experience, prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations, and engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4ab5324c-000059aecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
