<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Review Session to Discuss Programs in Analytics, Machine Learning, AI</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348c2fed-00000672calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, May 21, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for a session highlighting Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning and AI. Attendees can expect to learn how data can inform better decisions, and will review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/analytics21"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348c2fed-00000672calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work MBA for Professionals Review Scheduled for May 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348dc4f2-00000b4acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 23, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MBAP23"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Participants will learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with real-world MBA experience, prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations, and engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348dc4f2-00000b4acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HASS to Hold “DE-FENCE Part 2” Living Art Installation May 18</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-de-fence-line-becomes-territory</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Rensselaer’s School of Humanities, Arts and Social Sciences from 1pm to 4pm on Saturday, May 18 for “DE-FENCE Part 2: The Line Becomes a Territory,” as Margaretha Haughwout leads participants in the creation of DE-FENCE, a living participatory art installation at the NATURE Lab, located at 3319 6th Avenue in downtown Troy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-de-fence-line-becomes-territory</guid></item><item><title>New Master’s Degree Program Readies Students for Careers in Health Sciences, Clinical Research, Similar Fields</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/10/rpis-new-master-biomedical-engineering-data-science-readies-students-careers-health</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Department of Biomedical Engineering has established a new master’s degree program that will prepare students for careers of biomedical data science, a fast growing engineering specialty. According to Juergen Hahn, Ph.D., head of the Biomedical Engineering Department, those with expertise in biomedical data science are already in high demand, and that demand will continue to rise in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/10/rpis-new-master-biomedical-engineering-data-science-readies-students-careers-health</guid></item><item><title>Every Day Matters: Pursuing His Passions: Ben Viner</title><link>https://everydaymatters.rpi.edu/pursuing-his-passions-ben-viner/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pursuing-his-passions-ben-viner</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to getting the most out of a four-year undergraduate education, it’s hard to find anyone who packed more in than Ben Viner ’24. With a dual major in aeronautical and mechanical engineering and two minors in music performance and architectural acoustics, Viner took classes in four of RPI’s five schools, but also found time to take part in a wide range of other activities, including serving as Rensselaer’s 157th Grand Marshal. With Commencement just around the corner, Viner reflects on his time here.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://everydaymatters.rpi.edu/pursuing-his-passions-ben-viner/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pursuing-his-passions-ben-viner</guid></item><item><title>Peer Career Advisor Program Supports Students as They Navigate Internship and Job Opportunities</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/14/peer-career-advisor-program-supports-students-they-navigate-internship-and-job</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Center for Career and Professional Development introduced its new Peer Career Advisor (PCA) program during the Fall 2023 semester, culminating in a successful inaugural year in Spring 2024. This student-support initiative has provided a platform for current RPI students to foster community and offer career guidance to peers across all majors and academic levels, encompassing both undergraduate and graduate students.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/14/peer-career-advisor-program-supports-students-they-navigate-internship-and-job</guid></item><item><title>Farewell Gathering for Father Larry Rice to be Held May 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7cf7b2b6-00007297calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, May 29, 2024 12:00 PM - 2:00 PM - All are welcome to join the Office of the Provost in bidding farewell to Father Larry Rice, who is embarking on a new chapter and extending his support to another community in need after dedicating three years to Rensselaer as its Chaplain. Feel free to stop by the Russell Sage Dining Hall to help honor Father Larry’s contributions and wish him success in his future endeavors!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7cf7b2b6-00007297calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Air Force ROTC Cadets to be Commissioned Friday</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/15/rensselaer-air-force-rotc-cadets-be-commissioned-friday</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday, May 17, ten Air Force Reserve Officers’ Training Corps (AFROTC) cadets from Detachment 550 will be commissioned into the U.S. Air Force or Space Force in a ceremony at the Curtis R. Priem Experimental Media and Performing Arts Center (EMPAC). Detachment 550 serves as a host unit for cadets at Rensselaer and 22 regional cross-town colleges and universities; six out of the ten commissioning cadets are graduating from RPI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:35:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/15/rensselaer-air-force-rotc-cadets-be-commissioned-friday</guid></item></channel></rss>
