<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Counseling Center Announces Drop-in Counseling Hours for Fall 2025</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/drop-counseling-hours-fall-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI Counseling Center invites students to meet with a counselor without a formal appointment, during designated drop-in hours. There are two hours available for walk-in each day (M/F - 10 a.m. to 12 p.m.; T/W/Th - 2 to 4 p.m.). Drop-in counseling is available on a first come, first served basis on days when classes are in session. Students who cannot attend drop-in times can call (518) 276-6479 to schedule an appointment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/drop-counseling-hours-fall-2025</guid></item><item><title>Graduate Student Lunch and Learn professional Development Series | Sept. 17 - Registration Required</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-a96567bb-000044b2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 17, 2025 12:00 PM - 2:30 PM - TBD- Lunch and Learn. Hybrid event. Registration is required. - Email sanchn2@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-a96567bb-000044b2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; Haleon Info Session | Sept. 16</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-haleon-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, 9/16, Haleon (a local employer) will be on campus to discuss their student programs and opportunities for co-ops, internships, and rotational roles. The event will be held from 5:30-7:30pm. Join the CCPD and Haleon for this exciting event just for RPI students! Registration and additional details are available in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-haleon-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Join RPI’s Red &amp; White Student Organization, apply by Sept. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-cf542fec-00006c16calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Be part of RPI tradition! The &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/view/rpiredandwhite"&gt;Red &amp;amp; White Student Organization&lt;/a&gt; connects students with alumni, leads tours, and promotes school pride. Gain experience, friendships, and a chance to represent RPI. Apply by Sept. 12: https://forms.gle/14Trz9VS23FgD4iq6&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-cf542fec-00006c16calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents: Visiting Critic Lane Relyea | Sept. 10</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-visiting-critic-lane-relyea</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Visiting Critic Lane Relyea will give a lecture titled “Friendship, Community and Other Neoliberal Propaganda in Recent Art and Culture”. Lane Relyea is Associate Professor of Art Theory and Practice at Northwestern University. His essays and reviews have appeared in such magazines as Artforum, Afterall, Art in America, Flash Art, Frieze, Parkett, Modern Painters and Texte zur Kunst. Join us in the CBIS Auditorium at 5pm on Wednesday, September 10.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-visiting-critic-lane-relyea</guid></item><item><title>“R for Python (and other…) Muggles!” RPIrates Monthly Meeting (Weds, 10 Sep, 6p, AE217)</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/r-python-and-other-muggles-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-10-sep-6p-ae217</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPIrates: The RPI R Users Group kicks off the Fall 2025 term with a review of R fundamentals useful for experienced R users but especially new users who may already have done data science on platforms such as Python. In this session we’ll focus on R data structures, subsetting, control structures, functions and vectorization. RPIrates is led by Dr. John S. Erickson, Director of Research Operations with the Rensselaer FOCI and Chief Instigator of RPIrates. Pizza and salad starts at 5:30p&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/r-python-and-other-muggles-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-10-sep-6p-ae217</guid></item><item><title>Burgers on Burdett is Back!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/burgers-burdett-back</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce that a favorite among the RPI Community is back. Starting this Wednesday September 10th, Burgers on Burdett returns to the Commons Dining Hall during lunch.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/burgers-burdett-back</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC Multimedia Performance: Will Not Be Composed</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/program/curatorial/residencies/2025/we-will-not-be-composed</link><description>&lt;p&gt;October 20-24, 2025 We Will Not Be Composed is a multimedia performance created in collaboration with saxophonist and composer Stevie Manning, author and activist Soraya Chemaly, and new media artist Xuan to challenge perceptions of women’s anger in America. Manning and an ensemble of musicians build and rehearse the world premiere performance of the work utilizing the advanced spatial audio, video, and stage technologies of EMPAC Studio 1—Goodman.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/program/curatorial/residencies/2025/we-will-not-be-composed</guid></item><item><title>Reunion &amp; Homecoming 2025 | Oct. 10-12</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10242&amp;cid=23364&amp;ecid=23364&amp;ciid=83503&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for Reunion &amp;amp; Homecoming 2025: October 10-12, where we will celebrate class years ending in 0 or 5! If you’re interested in helping your class or group with planning an event or volunteering for your Reunion class gift committee, visit our “Volunteer” page on the Reunion website or contact &lt;a href="mailto:alumni@rpi.edu"&gt;alumni@rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10242&amp;cid=23364&amp;ecid=23364&amp;ciid=83503&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff In-Person Workshop: Get Wise with the Owl | Sept. 15</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-be9f4a82-00007d88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 15, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Discover how to make the most of your Meeting Owl! Whether your department already has an Owl or you’re considering one, this hands-on workshop will walk you through everything you need to know — from setup and placement to an overview of benefits and key features like 360° video, automatic speaker tracking, and pairing devices. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-be9f4a82-00007d88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar – “Assigning Learning in Percipio: A Guide for Supervisors”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-assigning-learning-percipio</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This course provides supervisors with a step-by-step overview of how to assign learning content to employees using Percipio. You’ll learn how to search for relevant courses, create and manage assignments, track completion, and support your team’s development goals. Designed to be quick and practical, this session equips you with the tools needed to guide your team’s learning journey effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-assigning-learning-percipio</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff In Person Workshop - Beta Classroom - Teaching with Technology Preview | Sept. 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-0fafb137-00001377calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 22, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Come see the Collaboratory space in the main library, and the exciting technologies available to you in the Beta Classroom. The beta classroom is a high technology testing space for interactive learning. The goal of the beta classroom is for faculty to pilot new or interactive technologies and pedagogical approaches that can be recommended for other classrooms on campus. This is also the educational space of the Teaching and Learning…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-0fafb137-00001377calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Please join us for the next talk in the Quantum Vision Lecture Series | Sept. 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-14ee2827-00000779calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 11, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - This session will feature a distinguished leader in quantum computing who will share their vision for the future of the field. The talk will explore innovative strategies for advancing quantum research and discuss opportunities to leverage RPI’s intellectual and infrastructure strengths to enhance our position at the forefront of this rapidly evolving domain. The presentation will last approximately 30 minutes, followed by 30 minutes of…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-14ee2827-00000779calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Summer Course Evaluation Dates and Instructor Training Opportunities</title><link>https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/summer-student-course-evaluations-training-dates-adding-questions-and-reviewing</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Review Summer I, II, and III course evaluation dates and instructor training opportunities available for HelioCampus course surveys.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/summer-student-course-evaluations-training-dates-adding-questions-and-reviewing</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Connect Through Conversations” Part 1</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-connect-through</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Much of a leader’s work is accomplished through daily conversations with team members and others. These interactions, especially the tough ones, often involve intensely personal feelings (on both sides) that have an impact on the practical outcome of the conversation and the personal connection between the leader and the person. Part 1 of 2.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-connect-through</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review with Rensselaer at Work | Sept. 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f9eb1a-00004568calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 11, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join Rensselaer Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register below to receive login details to join this virtual event&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f9eb1a-00004568calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-2</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience a “day in the life” of a Supervisor. In addition, the importance of managing employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team capacity will be explored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-2</guid></item></channel></rss>
