<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>NSBE/SHPE 47th Annual Career Fair | Sept. 25</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-30244570-000031f3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 25, 2025 10:00 AM - Fri , September 26, 2025 1:00 PM - Still unsure about your plans after graduation or what you’ll be doing this summer? Visit the NSBE/SHPE Annual Career Fair and explore opportunities with over 100 companies ready to meet you! September 25th 10 am - 4 pm and September 26th 10 am - 1 pm&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-30244570-000031f3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; Unity House of Troy Info Session | Sept. 30</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-unity-house-troy-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The CCPD will be hosting an info session with Unity House of Troy on Tuesday, September 30th! If you’re interested in helping those in need and seeing the resilience of a community in action, Unity House offer opportunities in the form of employment, volunteer roles, and internships. Come learn more about available opportunities and the valuable work that Unity House does for the community! Registration and details are available in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-unity-house-troy-info-session</guid></item><item><title>NEW: Burgers by the Bridge – Thursday Nights Just Got Better!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/new-burgers-bridge-thursday-nights-just-got-better</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Craving something grill-worthy? Swing by Burgers by the Bridge at Russell Sage Dining Hall every Thursday night at Dinner for a stacked burger special that’ll hit the spot.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/new-burgers-bridge-thursday-nights-just-got-better</guid></item><item><title>Order of the Engineer Registration | Sept. 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-7249ac29-00006140calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 23, 2025 9:00 AM - 4:00 PM - The Order of the Engineer is open to all senior and graduate engineering students. The Order is a national organization that fosters a spirit of pride and responsibility in the engineering profession. The ceremony will be held October 15th at 6:00 PM. You must attend to be inducted and receive your ring. To register, https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSey-EadwWdy79LqItirOHymANzIu8tYSu8ahXu1eTuNqm7McA/viewform?usp=header Ring sizing and…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-7249ac29-00006140calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>GE Vernova Site Visit | Oc.t 8</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ge-vernova-site-visit</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, October 8th, the CCPD will be hosting a site visit to GE Vernova’s Schenectady office! Come learn about opportunities and life at GE Vernova and get a glimpse of what this location has to offer. Registration is available in Handshake, but spots are limited–register today! Transportation provided by the CCPD.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ge-vernova-site-visit</guid></item><item><title>Stephanie Boluk and Patrick LeMieux: Hands Free: A History of Accessible Alt Ctrls |Sept. 23</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/stephanie-boluk-and-patrick-lemieux-hands-free-history-accessible-alt-ctrls</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This presentation begins with a brisk survey of the history of hands-free video game interfaces before comparing and contrasting two devices that articulate two different design philosophies: the NES Hands Free and the Octopad. Rather than thinking about accessibility as a single-player problem, these controllers engage the social, political, and environmental aspects of video games to change the way we play. Join us on September 23 at 4:30pm on Webex.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/stephanie-boluk-and-patrick-lemieux-hands-free-history-accessible-alt-ctrls</guid></item><item><title>EARN YOUR Mercer X Skills Badges</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/earn-your-mercer-xlab-skills-badges</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mercer XLab is now offering a chance to earn limited edition Fall 2025 Skills Badges! To improve your Mercer X Skill Set there are three levels to obtain: Level 1 is your learning, Level 2 is applying your learning to a project, and Level 3, the gold standard, is teaching someone else! We offer the opportunity to earn PCB Pro (printing PCB prototypes), PCB Designer, Hot Worker (soldering), Spice-EE (Spice simulation), Instrument Wiz, and IC Designer skills. Earn yours before they run out!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/earn-your-mercer-xlab-skills-badges</guid></item><item><title>National Hazing Prevention Week | Sept. 22-26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-4f0acc1f-00001e6fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 22, 2025 - Fri , September 26, 2025 (all day) - RPI Won’t Stand By! September 22nd - September 26th is National Hazing Prevention Week. Multiple areas of campus will be hosting events to build community, uplift healthy groups, and raise awareness to prevent hazing. Stop by one or more of our events! For more information, contact Lauryn Maleski or Mel Daley.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-4f0acc1f-00001e6fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>The Food Pantry is looking for volunteers</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-71975cd3-00003a3fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 23, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - Have you considered volunteering at the Pantry? The pantry is open 9 hours a week and shifts are 1 hour in length. A very easy way to support students. contact Graham Knowles for more details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-71975cd3-00003a3fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Cable Television Outage in Specific Campus Buildings</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the campus about an issue affecting CATV services in several buildings: Sage, Troy, Ricketts, and 87Gym. Our service provider has identify the issue–an underground cable–and will implement repairs as soon as possible. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause and appreciate patience as we work toward a resolution. New information will be provided as soon as it becomes available. Thank you for your understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings</guid></item><item><title>Mainstreaming Mental Well-being: A Training Series for Faculty and Staff</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/mainstreaming-mental-well-being-training-series-faculty-and-staff</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mainstreaming Mental Wellbeing (MMWB) Taskforce envisions an RPI community in which mental health and well-being are central tenets, both in and out of the classroom, and where all community members are challenged and supported to learn, grow, and develop. This training series will give you concrete knowledge, skills, and resources to play an active role in supporting student wellbeing at RPI.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/mainstreaming-mental-well-being-training-series-faculty-and-staff</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff Quick Learn Webinar - Creating Basic Pivot Tables with Excel for Windows | Oct. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-53028bb4-0000350acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 3, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Do you work with data in Excel? Are you always manipulating the content with filters and sorting? If so, taking a look at Pivot Tables in Excel could be beneficial. This workshops will focus on using Pivot Tables in Excel to summarize, filter and group data. Basic functions will be applied as well as a quick look at charts. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-53028bb4-0000350acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty &amp; Staff Appreciation Lunch on September 24th</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-september-24th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We’re celebrating you! As a token of our appreciation, all faculty and staff are invited to enjoy lunch at Commons or Russell Sage Dining Halls for just $6 on September 24th!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-september-24th</guid></item></channel></rss>
