<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Information Session Scheduled for June 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-3493d0f0-00001b8ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, June 7, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., will review the online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates, and participants will learn how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/general7"&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-3493d0f0-00001b8ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>American Music Festival to be Held June 7-8</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/american-music-festival-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Presented by Albany Symphony Orchestra and scheduled to be held throughout Troy June 7-8, this festival will feature composer workshops and rehearsal readings, post-concert musical mingling at Evelyn’s Cafe, recitals, Dogs of Desire on Friday, the culminating Festival concert on Saturday, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/american-music-festival-2024</guid></item><item><title>How Should Brands Respond to Positive Online Reviews?</title><link>https://retailwire.com/discussion/how-should-brands-respond-to-positive-online-reviews/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;While businesses are widely encouraged to respond to negative online reviews, a new study finds responding to positive online reviews is more of a “minefield,” and some should be ignored. Researchers at Rensselaer and Baruch College’s Zicklin School of Business analyzed ten years of online reviews of hotels from Trip Advisor, and found the type of response widely depends on the critique.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://retailwire.com/discussion/how-should-brands-respond-to-positive-online-reviews/</guid></item><item><title>Quantum Computing Users Group Organizational Meeting</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-organizational-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Future of Computing Institute announces the formation of a Quantum Computing Users Group. On Wednesday, June 12th, from noon to 2 pm, there will be an organizational meeting in CII 3116. The goals are to find out about the experience and background of interested parties, evaluate what more is needed to enable the campus QC to be used effectively and efficiently and discuss other subjects that the group may find interesting. RSVP: Tom Morgan, morgat5@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-organizational-meeting</guid></item><item><title>Virtual Housing Fairs Continue June 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-7210cfa4-00004a2bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, June 7, 2024 9:00 AM - 10:30 AM - The Off-Campus Commons is pleased to host this virtual housing fair to give students a chance to learn more about off-campus housing, meet the RPI staff who can assist, and interact with several property owners who cater to RPI students. Feel free to &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/UVEntWpZnc"&gt;join the Discord Server&lt;/a&gt; any time during the event….&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-7210cfa4-00004a2bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Continues Virtual Summer Series with Tokyo Electron Info Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2629</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 6:30PM to 7:30PM on Thursday, June 20, the team at Tokyo Electron U.S. Holdings, Inc. (TEL) will discuss the organization’s career paths and company culture, as well as upcoming opportunities for Arch students seeking an Away experience! Interested students can review the &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/edu/jobs/89383858883745"&gt;Process Engineer Intern&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/edu/jobs/8883745"&gt;Process Engineer Co-op&lt;/a&gt; opportunities posted in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2629</guid></item><item><title>Registration Now Open for NSF GRFP Bootcamp</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-e3f5ea9d-0000399acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 5, 2024 8:00 AM - First-year graduate students, juniors and seniors are encouraged to &lt;a href="https://rpi.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_2mm8LJCSHc895QO"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; for this virtual program to develop strong applications to the National Science Foundation Graduate Research Fellowship Program, which begins June 24 and provides three years of salary and tuition while students earn their graduate degree. U.S. citizenship or permanent residency is required.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-e3f5ea9d-0000399acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Training, Resources to Aid Instructors in Reviewing Spring Course Results</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/05/16/2024/spring-2024-course-evaluation-results-training-heliocampus</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Spring 2024 student course evaluation results will be available to instructors on May 28, 2024; on May 30 and June 10, the Office of Undergraduate Education will offer live webinar training for instructors and TAs on running those results. Those who cannot attend a live session or prefer to review on their own may refer to the &lt;a href="https://provost.rpi.edu/faculty-resources/heliocampus-formerly-aefis-assessment-tool/heliocampus-formerly-aefis-support"&gt;HelioCampus Resource Site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/05/16/2024/spring-2024-course-evaluation-results-training-heliocampus</guid></item></channel></rss>
