<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:35:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Griffis Business Park Tour &amp; Luncheon | July 16 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0196-f32b60f6-0000563acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 16, 2025 9:00 AM - 5:00 PM - Join us for the 2025 Griffiss Business Park Student Tour on July 16 in Rome NY. This full day experience includes visits to leading tech and research organizations such as the Air Force Research Lab and Innovare Advancement Center. Students will also have the opportunity to connect with RPI alumni over a networking lunch at NYSTEC. Registration is required by June 15. Transportation is provided.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:35:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0196-f32b60f6-0000563acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Graduate Summer Lunch &amp; Learn-The Art of Scientific Presentations | July 16 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0196-c5a8e0e6-00001112calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 16, 2025 11:30 AM - 1:00 PM - Dr. Jacob Shelley-In “The Making of a Scientist” (1953), Anne Roe said, “Nothing in science has any value to society if it is not communicated…”. In this presentation, based on a long-running series of seminars and short courses, suggestions will be offered on how to prepare for, present, and benefit from scientific lectures, be they in a classroom environment, technical conference, local seminar, job interview, or short course. Registration…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:35:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0196-c5a8e0e6-00001112calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Mechanical Engineering Review on July 16</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-79621b30-00006c86calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 16, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work faculty on a 30-minute information session covering Rensselaer’s online, project-based Master of Engineering program in Mechanical Engineering. Experienced engineers are asked to take on larger and more complex tasks as they progress in their careers, and this program provides the necessary breadth and depth, no matter where one’s career takes them. Please RSVP to attend this event&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:35:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-79621b30-00006c86calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Campus Cleanout Days Scheduled this Summer</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/campus-cleanout-days</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Environmental Health &amp;amp; Safety (EHS) and Environmental &amp;amp; Site Services (E&amp;amp;SS) are partnering with the campus community to encourage cleanouts of cluttered storage areas, offices, shops, and labs. Take advantage of these free events to prepare your spaces for the upcoming fall semester!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:35:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/campus-cleanout-days</guid></item><item><title>Walkway Between JEC and The Greene Building Under Construction Beginning Monday, July 14th</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/walkway-between-jec-and-greene-building-under-construction-beginning-monday-july-14th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Beginning Monday, July 14, 2025, the elevated walkway between the JEC and Greene buildings will undergo necessary repairs to its west side. Construction is expected to continue through Friday, August 16th. During this period, the walkway will be closed to all pedestrian traffic. Please note that this project will also impact the second-floor entrance into the Greene Building, which serves as the ADA-accessible entry. In coordination with the contractor, a portion of the ramp and walkway will…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:35:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/walkway-between-jec-and-greene-building-under-construction-beginning-monday-july-14th</guid></item><item><title>Workshop Series: Building Your Toolkit to Support Graduate Students | July 16</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-c77fd1d5-0000523bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 16, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM - Join Student Experience staff for two interactive workshops to enhance your toolkit for supporting graduate students at RPI. Learn tips and tricks to help you as a professional and life-long learner. Workshop One: Regulate to Relate: Navigating Burnout to Support Ourselves and Those We Mentor This interactive session explores the neuroscience of burnout through a compassionate, embodied lens.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:35:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-c77fd1d5-0000523bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar- “RPI MAX: Setting Goals and Reviewing Results”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-rpi-max-setting-goals-and</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: This seminar will establish the positive effect of transforming the traditional role of planner and evaluator solely from the people-leader to a shared responsibility between leader and direct report. This shift builds collective ownership and allows the leader to focus on coaching and developing throughout the performance cycle. Leaders will experience how to develop and use effective SMART goals to help them, and their employees track progress and accurately evaluate outcomes. In…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:35:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-rpi-max-setting-goals-and</guid></item></channel></rss>
