<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Book Your Appointment with COMM+D Online!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/01/03/2025/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you working on a writing assignment, oral presentation, or visual design project? Whether you’re at the beginning brainstorming stages or finishing up your final revisions, the Center for Global Communication+Design (Comm+D) can help, so be sure to schedule an appointment with a member of the Center’s trained staff!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/01/03/2025/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</guid></item><item><title>Spring Graduate Lunch and Learn Series- Post-degree work authorizations | April 9 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-98adf2d8-000055bdcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 9, 2025 12:00 PM - 2:30 PM - Join International Services and speakers from NZP Law Group to learn about post-degree work on Optional Practical Training (OPT) and STEM OPT, &amp;amp; immigration options after the F-1 visa. ISSS will provide information about OPT and STEM OPT and NPZ will share the options to consider beyond the F-1 visa. Seating is limited. Lunch will be served from 12-12:30.REGISTRATION IS REQUIRED. To Register email Noelle Sanchez (sanchn2@rpi.edu)Location: The Ellsworth Room in the Union.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-98adf2d8-000055bdcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Demystifying the Civil Service Merit System: Careers in Public Service | April 8</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/demystifying-civil-service-merit-system-careers-public-service-april-8</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on Tuesday, April 8th, 2025 at 5:30 pm - 6:30 pm in Low 3112 as the CCPD hosts Adam Rossi, Capital Region CCG Specialist from the New York State Department of Civil Service who will present a workshop on career and internship opportunities in New York State and how to apply.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/demystifying-civil-service-merit-system-careers-public-service-april-8</guid></item><item><title>2025 ECAC Esports Spring Showdown | April 4–6</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2025/2025-ecac-spring-showdown</link><description>&lt;p&gt;April 4–6, 2025 | The ECAC Esports Spring Showdown will bring collegiate gaming teams from around the country to the university’s Curtis R. Priem Experimental and Performing Arts Center. The teams will compete in several esports titles, including Rocket League and Overwatch. Bringing in over 125 schools and 800 student teams, the event is reportedly expected to draw in thousands of participants and spectators to Troy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2025/2025-ecac-spring-showdown</guid></item><item><title>How Many Student Support Resources Are You Using?</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/how-many-student-support-resources-are-you-using</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you explored our comprehensive advising model? Have you taken full advantage of the Center for Career and Professional Development and the Center for Global Communication + Design? What about I-PERSIST and the Student Success Labs? Did you know our median course evaluation for overall instructor rating is above 4/5? There’s so much more to discover! Dive into Standard 3 of RPI’s Self-Study for Middle States Accreditation, a team led by Dr. Sibel Adali and Dr. Tracy Sullivan.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/how-many-student-support-resources-are-you-using</guid></item><item><title>Math Sciences Department - Class of ’27 Lecture Series | April 8 &amp; April 9</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-b49dd46c-00001efccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, April 8, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - The Class of ’27 Lecture Series, established in 1960 to honor the first chair of the Math Sciences Department, holds two special lectures annually. Lecture I, on April 8, will present “Eigenmatrix for Unstructured Sparse Recovery”. Lecture II, on April 9, features “NRandomness in phase estimation and Heisenberg-limited Hamiltonian learning”, by speaker Lexing Ying from Stanford University.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-b49dd46c-00001efccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Thank you from the Office of Admissions!</title><link>https://undergrad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/thank-you</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Admissions would like to thank all students, faculty, and staff who volunteered at the Accepted Student Celebration on March 22. Seeing everyone come together to support our yield efforts was very appreciated by all, especially accepted students and their families. We look forward to doing it again on April 12! If you have any questions or want to learn more about helping out, please email Arianna Livshits at paluma3@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/thank-you</guid></item><item><title>APRIL Mercer X Clubhouse Workshops and Seminars</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/april-mercer-x-clubhouse-workshops-and-seminars</link><description>&lt;p&gt;April Mercer X Clubhouse Workshops are ready to bring in the Spring! Are you interested in PCB Design (4/2), ROS Programming (4/9), Learning from Microelectronic Experts at a Mini-Colloquium (4/18), a Research Fair while enjoying your favorite ICE CREAM (4/24), and more? Please visit the Mercer X Lab, 6th floor JEC, to learn about every workshop or event open to all RPI students in April!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/april-mercer-x-clubhouse-workshops-and-seminars</guid></item><item><title>Teaching &amp; Learning Collaboratory In-Person Spring Event - Learning Today: Neuroscience, Digital Technologies, and Distraction | May 13</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/04/01/2025/teaching-learning-collaboratory-person-spring-event-learning</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Education and the Teaching and Learning Collaboratory are pleased to announce our spring guest speaker, James M. Lang, who will talk on Learning Today: Neuroscience, Digital Technologies, and Distraction on May 13th from 11 - 12:45pm. Please review session details. Registration required by May 5th. We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/04/01/2025/teaching-learning-collaboratory-person-spring-event-learning</guid></item><item><title>Administration Division Announces Dave Ira’s Retirement</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/administration/04/02/2025/administration-division-announces-dave-ira%E2%80%99s-retirement</link><description>&lt;p&gt;After 21 years of service at Rensselaer, Dave Ira will be retiring on May 2, 2025. Dave joined Rensselaer in 2004 as Associate Director of Physical Plant. He stepped in as Acting Director in March 2022 and was promoted to the Director’s position in August 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/administration/04/02/2025/administration-division-announces-dave-ira%E2%80%99s-retirement</guid></item></channel></rss>
