<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CCPD &amp; NY Independent System Operator Info Session | Oct. 21</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-ny-independent-system-operator-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, October 21st, join the CCPD and NY Independent System Operator to discover how NYISO helps keep New York’s power grid reliable and efficient, as well as how you can gain hands-on experience in areas like engineering, IT, economics, and more. Meet the NYISO team, ask questions, and learn about their co-op opportunities. Registration and additional details are available in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-ny-independent-system-operator-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 School of Engineering Midterm Student Course Evaluations Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-9b46c654-00003336calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 10, 2025 (all day) - Fall 2025 School of Engineering (SoE) Midterm course evaluations are now open. Your feedback is very important to the Institute and the school, so please complete the SoE midterm evaluation surveys for all your courses! Evaluations will be available through Thursday, October 23, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-9b46c654-00003336calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Prepare for the second round of exams</title><link>https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/exam-prep-calc-i-and-ii-iea-cs-i-and-data-structures</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Prepare for upcoming exams in Calculus I, II, IEA, CSCI 1 and Data Structures with the Student Success Center. Drop in sessions available October 14-16 and 19-23. Enjoy our signature cookie - the Puck on 10/22 (for first 100 attendees)! IPERSIST office hours available throughout the week.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/exam-prep-calc-i-and-ii-iea-cs-i-and-data-structures</guid></item><item><title>Reduce and Reuse: Introducing the Chemical ReUse Program</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/reduce-and-reuse-introducing-chemical-reuse-program</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI is committed to reducing chemical waste and promoting responsible resource management across campus. To advance these goals, Environmental Health &amp;amp; Safety (EHS) is launching a Chemical ReUse Program, a new initiative that helps laboratories share surplus chemicals and reduce disposal needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/reduce-and-reuse-introducing-chemical-reuse-program</guid></item><item><title>Get Your Message on Campus Screens - Learn How! | Oct. 16</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/get-your-message-campus-screens-learn-how</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Jim Evans, Director of Multi Media Services, on Thursday October 16th from 11am-12pm for a hands-on webinar about Carousel Digital Signage, RPI’s campus-wide signage system. Whether you’re promoting an event, sharing a campus update, or spotlighting a team achievement, this training will help you get your message on screens across RPI. Open to RPI campus community only. Register online at https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/rf01c7b66cceead46ccb48bd624c388dc&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/get-your-message-campus-screens-learn-how</guid></item><item><title>Fall Farmers Market October 16th at the Student Union Patio</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-farmers-market-october-16th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Pumpkin spice up your week with cozy vibes, local finds, and mouthwatering eats at the Fall Farmers Market from 11 am - 2 pm!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-farmers-market-october-16th</guid></item><item><title>Dr. Azita Hirsa Receives the Rensselaer Alumni Association (RAA) Teaching Award</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/dr-azita-hirsa-receives-raa-teaching-award</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Industrial and Systems Engineering Department proudly celebrates Dr. Azita Hirsa, recipient of the RAA Teaching Award. Dr. Hirsa’s courses in professional development, ethics, and management of engineering and technology inspire students to connect technical excellence with integrity, purpose, and collaboration. “Students learn best when they feel supported, challenged, and seen as collaborators in our learning journey,” said Dr. Hirsa. “This recognition affirms that those efforts matter.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/dr-azita-hirsa-receives-raa-teaching-award</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Colloquia: Bogdan Arsintescu - Research to product: 15 Years of Building Graph Systems | Oct. 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-e7b350d0-00003a8dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, October 20, 2025 10:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Bogdan Arsintescu is a knowledge graph and graph systems expert who thrives in greenfield innovation projects. He recently started a structured data project in the AI Knowledge team that is part of Microsoft CoreAI. In Microsoft Fabric he focused on ontology and graph systems, building scale-out graph systems for analytics and operational workloads (a project he incubated and spearheaded while originally at LinkedIn) as an architect and…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-e7b350d0-00003a8dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff In-Person Workshop: Get Wise with the Owl | Oct. 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-a054b73f-00002137calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 22, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Discover how to make the most of your Meeting Owl! Whether your department already has an Owl or you’re considering one, this hands-on workshop will walk you through everything you need to know — from setup and placement to an overview of benefits and key features like 360° video, automatic speaker tracking, and pairing devices. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-a054b73f-00002137calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>2025 Pillar of Rensselaer Award</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-pillar-rensselaer-award</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We are now welcoming nominations for the 2025 Pillar of Rensselaer award!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:32:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-pillar-rensselaer-award</guid></item></channel></rss>
