<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:31:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Administration Division: Roof Replacements Scheduled for Summer Months</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/administration/06/06/2024/roof-replacements-materials-research-center-mrc-empire-state-hall-esh-and</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All members of the campus community should note that roof replacements are scheduled for the Materials Research Center (MRC), Empire State Hall (ESH), and the west wing of the Jonsson Rowland Science Center (JRSC). Construction will begin on Monday, June 17 and be completed by Friday, August 9, with tentative daily work hours set for 6:00AM to 2:30PM, Monday through Friday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/administration/06/06/2024/roof-replacements-materials-research-center-mrc-empire-state-hall-esh-and</guid></item><item><title>ICAD 2024 Scheduled for June 24-28</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/research/2024/icad-2024-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled for June 24-28, 2024, the International Conference on Auditory Display is a highly interdisciplinary conference with relevance to researchers, practitioners, artists, and graduate students working with sound to convey and explore information, and is unique in its specific focus on auditory displays and the range of interdisciplinary issues related to their use.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/research/2024/icad-2024-0</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Researchers Upend Theory About the Formation of the Milky Way Galaxy</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/06/06/rensselaer-researchers-upend-theory-about-formation-milky-way-galaxy</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Heidi Jo Newberg, Ph.D., a professor of astronomy at Rensselaer; Tom Donlon, Ph.D., a visiting researcher at Rensselaer and a postdoctoral researcher at the University of Alabama; and their team have recently published research that reveals a shocking discovery about the history of our universe: the Milky Way Galaxy’s last major collision occurred billions of years later than previously thought.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/06/06/rensselaer-researchers-upend-theory-about-formation-milky-way-galaxy</guid></item><item><title>Former RPI Hockey Captain Helps Florida Everblades Win ECHL Kelly Cup</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/6/10/former-rpi-captain-will-reilly-helps-florida-everblades-win-echl-kelly-cup.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Rensselaer men’s hockey captain Will Reilly ‘20 and the Florida Everglades claimed the ECHL Kelly Cup this past weekend with a 4-1 series victory against the Kansas City Mavericks. Reilly played a key role in the Everblades’ 4-3 overtime victory in game five, as he provided the assist on Matt Weldman’s series-winning score with 3:38 elapsed in the extra period.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/6/10/former-rpi-captain-will-reilly-helps-florida-everblades-win-echl-kelly-cup.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer in the News: Computer scientist discusses Apple’s entrance into the AI space</title><link>https://spectrumlocalnews.com/nys/capital-region/news/2024/06/11/ai-expert-apple-intelligence-privacy-concerns</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jim Hendler, who leads Rensselaer’s Future of Computing Research and has studied artificial intelligence for years, is featured in a segment which recently appeared on the Spectrum News 1 local news channel.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://spectrumlocalnews.com/nys/capital-region/news/2024/06/11/ai-expert-apple-intelligence-privacy-concerns</guid></item><item><title>Study Abroad Applications Now Being Accepted for Spring 2025</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of International Programs’ &lt;a href="https://rpi-sa.terradotta.com/index.cfm?FuseAction=Abroad.Home"&gt;application portal&lt;/a&gt; is now open to undergraduate students who wish to apply for spring 2025 study abroad. Deadlines, contact info, and application guidelines are available via the &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025"&gt;International Programs website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review Scheduled for June 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-34a36fe0-00002c7ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, June 20, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MBAP20"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Participants will learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with real-world MBA experience, prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations, and engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential….&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-34a36fe0-00002c7ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
