<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>DotCIO Announces Change to Single Sign-On Process, Effective May 22</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/change-single-sign-process-effective-05222024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;To improve security, DotCIO is releasing a change to the single sign-on process that will become effective as of Wednesday, May 22, 2024. Under this updated process, the initial login page will only prompt users to enter their Username and then click Login; the next page will ask for their password, and to click Login a second time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/change-single-sign-process-effective-05222024</guid></item><item><title>ICAD 2024 Scheduled for June 24-28</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/research/2024/icad-2024-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled for June 24-28, 2024, the International Conference on Auditory Display is a highly interdisciplinary conference with relevance to researchers, practitioners, artists, and graduate students working with sound to convey and explore information, and is unique in its specific focus on auditory displays and the range of interdisciplinary issues related to their use.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/research/2024/icad-2024-0</guid></item><item><title>Don’t Miss the 26th Annual RPI Football Golf Tournament!</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=9806&amp;cid=22506&amp;ecid=22506&amp;ciid=78792&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mark your calendar for this year’s RPI Football Golf Outing, which is scheduled to be held on May 17 at Western Turnpike Golf Course in Guilderland, New York; check-in is at 8AM, with a shotgun start at 9AM. The outing provides a great opportunity for our current and former players to celebrate the past, enjoy the present, and look ahead to the future, and this is your chance to help both the golf outing and Rensselaer’s football program reach new heights!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=9806&amp;cid=22506&amp;ecid=22506&amp;ciid=78792&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Every Day Matters: The Support to Explore: Erin Thomas</title><link>https://everydaymatters.rpi.edu/the-support-to-explore-erin-thomas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-support-to-explore-erin-thomas</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Like the rest of the undergraduate Class of 2024, Erin Thomas will receive her bachelor’s degree from Rensselaer on May 18. Thomas, a biological neuroscience major, has chosen to attend a post-baccalaureate program at the National Institutes of Health before applying to graduate programs in neuroscience. It was the combination of a rigorous, wide-ranging curriculum and the opportunity to do advanced research that drew her to RPI in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://everydaymatters.rpi.edu/the-support-to-explore-erin-thomas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-support-to-explore-erin-thomas</guid></item><item><title>From Multimedia Services: New MyMediasite Video Editor Now Available</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-new-mymediasite-video-editor-now-available</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the Rensselaer community that the MyMediasite multimedia video system now has a new video editor with increased functionality that is immediately available to everyone with access to MyMediaite for recorded and uploaded videos. Please see the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/articles/26717262422157"&gt;ITSSC article&lt;/a&gt;, “Editing Video in MyMediasite,” for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-new-mymediasite-video-editor-now-available</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Naval ROTC Midshipmen to be Commissioned Friday</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/15/rensselaer-naval-rotc-midshipmen-be-commissioned-friday</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday, May 17, 11 prospective Rensselaer graduates will be commissioned as Ensigns in the U.S. Navy. The Naval Reserve Officers’ Training Corps (NROTC) program was established at Rensselaer in October 1941, and is charged with developing young men and women morally, mentally, and physically for the rigors of service as officers in the U.S. Navy and Marine Corps.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/15/rensselaer-naval-rotc-midshipmen-be-commissioned-friday</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Summer 2024 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-summer-2024-course-requests</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Summer 2024 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-summer-2024-course-requests</guid></item><item><title>TIAA Holding Confidential In-Person Retirement Counseling Sessions May 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8bd40c40-018c-4b40ee32-00002cc6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 23, 2024 9:00 AM - 4:00 PM - A TIAA Financial Consultant will be available for one-on-one consultations on a broad range of retirement topics. Attend this upcoming event to help you become better informed and more confident about Rensselaer’s retirement plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8bd40c40-018c-4b40ee32-00002cc6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
