<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Host Mechanical Engineering Review on September 18</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7fb7cd8-00004a43calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 18, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work faculty on a 30-minute information session covering Rensselaer’s online, project-based Master of Engineering program in Mechanical Engineering. Experienced engineers are asked to take on larger and more complex tasks as they progress in their careers, and this program provides the necessary breadth and depth, no matter where one’s career takes them. Please RSVP to attend&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7fb7cd8-00004a43calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ID Cards Required to Access Meal Plans in Dining Hall</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/id-cards-required-dining-hall-access</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We hope your semester is off to a great start! Please be reminded that starting immediately, all students with an active meal plan must present their valid student ID card to access meals in the dining halls. This policy helps ensure efficient service and accurate meal tracking.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/id-cards-required-dining-hall-access</guid></item><item><title>2025-26 Student Advisory Council (SAC) - Application deadline September 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d825c46-00002640calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, September 24, 2025 8:00 AM - 7:00 PM - Applications are now open for the 2025–26 Student Advisory Council (SAC)! Hosted by Vice Provosts Dr. Rob Hradsky and Dr. Matt Oehlschlaeger, the SAC connects students with campus leadership to shape academics, student life, and RPI culture. Meetings are biweekly on Fridays, 12–1:30 PM. Apply by Sept. 24 to make your voice heard and create positive change. Questions? Contact Quadir “Q” Webster at webstq@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d825c46-00002640calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Students, Faculty and Staff with Windows 10 on personal computers not managed by RPI</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/students-faculty-and-staff-windows-10-personal-computers-not-managed-rpi</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Windows 10 support ends on October 14th, 2025. This means that as of this date, Windows 10 systems will cease to be eligible for support including important security patches. Without appropriate mitigation, Windows 10 systems and your data will be at significant risk. Additionally, they will be non-compliant with multiple RPI security policies and may be denied access to the campus network to reduce risk and maintain a secure cybersecurity posture. Click in for recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/students-faculty-and-staff-windows-10-personal-computers-not-managed-rpi</guid></item><item><title>Apple Back-to-School Promotion (6/25-9/30)</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/apple-back-school-promotion</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Apple Back-to-School Promotion is back! Running from June 25 until September 30, 2025, the Rensselaer community can enjoy FREE Apple AirPods 4 Active Noise Cancelling (ANC) with the purchase of an eligible iMac or MacBook -or- FREE Apple Pencil Pro with the purchase of an eligible iPad Air or iPad Pro. Check out rensselaerstore.com to see what eligible devices are available. When you add an eligible device to your cart, you must also add the FREE item to your cart for the promotion to be…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/apple-back-school-promotion</guid></item><item><title>GE Vernova Site Visit | Oc.t 8</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ge-vernova-site-visit</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, October 8th, the CCPD will be hosting a site visit to GE Vernova’s Schenectady office! Come learn about opportunities and life at GE Vernova and get a glimpse of what this location has to offer. Registration is available in Handshake, but spots are limited–register today! Transportation provided by the CCPD.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ge-vernova-site-visit</guid></item><item><title>Department of Chemistry Fall 2025 Seminar Series | Sept. 16</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-391ac9fa-00007cd2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 16, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Mrinal Shekhar, Senior Computational Chemist at Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard, will speak on “Bridging Thermodynamics, Kinetics, and Structure: Synergistic Machine Learning and Simulation in Drug Discovery”.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-391ac9fa-00007cd2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>EARN YOUR Mercer X Skills Badges</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/earn-your-mercer-xlab-skills-badges</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mercer XLab is now offering a chance to earn limited edition Fall 2025 Skills Badges! To improve your Mercer X Skill Set there are three levels to obtain: Level 1 is your learning, Level 2 is applying your learning to a project, and Level 3, the gold standard, is teaching someone else! We offer the opportunity to earn PCB Pro (printing PCB prototypes), PCB Designer, Hot Worker (soldering), Spice-EE (Spice simulation), Instrument Wiz, and IC Designer skills. Earn yours before they run out!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/earn-your-mercer-xlab-skills-badges</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO announces Retirement of EZ-Snapshot Service</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-announces-retirement-ez-snapshot-service</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This notice is to announce the retirement of the EZ-Snapshot service effective Monday, November 3rd, 2025. Sometimes referred to as EZ-Backup, the service was created in 2006 using enterprise-class tape backup technology and was used to backup departmental, research and individual servers and workstations. It has fallen out of use in the past several years, having been replaced by a modern disk-based backup solution.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-announces-retirement-ez-snapshot-service</guid></item><item><title>Symposium on Surface Science and Catalysis | Sept. 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d85feba-00002e81calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 19, 2025 12:00 PM - 5:00 PM - The Symposium on Surface Science and Catalysis will feature a series of talks and discussions highlighting recent advances in the field, starting with lunch at 12:00. Feel free to come and go as your schedule allows—everyone is welcome to drop in for any portion of the event. However, if you plan to join us for lunch, RSVP to Bonnie Carson (carsob@rpi.edu) by Wednesday, September 17th. More detailed information is included in the event URL…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d85feba-00002e81calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Summer 2025 End of Term Student Course Evaluations: Reviewing Evaluation Results (Training for Instructors and TAs) Webinar | Sept. 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-108084af-00004072calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 17, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - This webinar is for instructors and TA’s that would like to understand or have a refresher of the various ways to review their student course evaluations in HelioCampus.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-108084af-00004072calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Registration Deadline for the 2nd annual Finance Conference</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-1111aa50-00005cc3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 22, 2025 12:00 AM - Tue , September 23, 2025 1:00 AM - RPI’s Division of Finance is excited to announce the 2nd annual Finance Conference on October 1, 2025. Come explore a curated lineup of interactive sessions designed to advance your professional skills and deepen your understanding of critical topics in higher education. From finance and data to leadership and IA, there’s something for every learner. The registration deadline is September 22, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-1111aa50-00005cc3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff Webinar - Strategies on Flipping Your Classroom | Sept. 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-29d9c2b4-0000679acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 24, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:00 PM - This session will discuss the practice of moving traditional in-class lectures onto the web by creating engaging, media-rich content that student’s access before, during, or after class. Class time is refocused, allowing students to work on tasks and problems that apply the concepts they studied independently. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-29d9c2b4-0000679acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff: Maximize Your Dental Benefits – Virtual MetLife Session</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-maximize-your-dental-benefits-virtual-metlife-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Faculty and Staff are invited to participate in a virtual dialogue with MetLife Dental Plan representatives, designed to help ensure you have an exceptional member experience. On Wednesday, September 17 from 11:00 am to 12 noon attendees will receive: An overview of RPI’s dental program A tutorial on how to find an in-network provider and use the online member portal An opportunity to engage directly with MetLife representatives and members of the Division of Human Resources team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-maximize-your-dental-benefits-virtual-metlife-session</guid></item></channel></rss>
