<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>OGE Online Dissertation and Thesis Preparation Workshop to be held February 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-28252791-000011b3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 19, 2025 2:30 PM - 4:00 PM - Learn the basics of correct thesis organization and format, appropriate paper attribution and reference citation styles—plus a review of the most commonly found mistakes and ways to avoid them. This workshop is for any student who will be writing an MS thesis or PhD dissertation. Bring your questions! &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScNtXJPWg-dh0rCgpqjNsUPsCvTo84qzvfDgVDOPzSs1Z0ryg/viewform?usp=header"&gt;Register here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-28252791-000011b3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>McKinney Creative Writing Workshop to be Held 2/21</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-creative-writing-workshop-writing-social-change-d-colin</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Have a story that could inspire others? Ready to raise your voice in solidarity with your community? Want to share your experiences with environmental or social activism? Get help composing or revising an essay, poem, or story for submission to the McKinney Writing for Social Change Contest with author and activist D. Colin on 2/21 at 12pm in the Fischbach Conference Room, on the second floor of the Folsom Library.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-creative-writing-workshop-writing-social-change-d-colin</guid></item><item><title>Game Development Club Presents Valentine’s Day Game Jam</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/game-development-club-presents-valentines-day-gamejam</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Love is in the air! Join the RPI Game Development Club on February 14 at 6 p.m. in Sage 2411 for a Valentine’s Themed Game Jam, and make a Multiplayer Game in 48 hours to play with the special people in your life! Overnight breaks begin at 10:00 PM on both Friday and Saturday nights and doors re-opening at 8:00 AM each morning. This event is open to RPI students of all majors and all levels of experience! Please contact club president, Aiden Crossfield (crossa2@rpi.edu) for more information and sign up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/game-development-club-presents-valentines-day-gamejam</guid></item><item><title>Tesla x RPI Application Workshop, Tech Talk, Networking to be Held February 19 at 2:00 pm</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/tesla-x-rpi-application-workshop-tech-talk-networking-be-held-february-19-2-pm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Tesla will host a session that will provide guidance on the resume-building and application process to help RPI students stand out! Immediately following the Tech Talk, Tesla will transition to a networking event in the DCC Great Hall where students can speak one-to-one with engineering managers. Seating is limited, so &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/login"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/tesla-x-rpi-application-workshop-tech-talk-networking-be-held-february-19-2-pm</guid></item><item><title>Systems Engineering &amp; Technology Management Review Scheduled for February 13</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-98993a62-00001760calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Thursday, February 13, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Hosted by Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., this session focuses on Rensselaer’s flexible, project-based, online Systems Engineering and Technology Management graduate degree that will help prepare decision-makers with broader and deeper capabilities in leading dynamic organizations. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/SETM13"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-98993a62-00001760calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Analytics, Machine Learning and AI Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-989a6e48-00001c3bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, February 19, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., on a 30-minute information session highlighting Rensselaer online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning &amp;amp; AI. Expect to learn how data can inform better decisions and review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/analytics19"&gt;Please register if you plan to attend.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-989a6e48-00001c3bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Cognitive Science Colloquium Scheduled for February 12th</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cognitive-science-colloquium-scheduled-february-12th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join the Cognitive Science Department at noon on 2/12 for a presentation titled “HARMONIC: Cognitive and Control Collaboration in Human-Robotic Teams” by Dr. Sanjay Oruganti, Research Scientist in the Language-Endowed Intelligent Agents (LEIA) Lab at RPI’s Cognitive Science Department (Carnegie 113).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cognitive-science-colloquium-scheduled-february-12th</guid></item><item><title>“Whose Data Is It Anyway?” Celebrate #LoveData25</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/whose-data-it-anyway-celebrate-lovedata25</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI Libraries celebrates Love Data Week 2025, an international data event held annually in February. This year’s theme, “Whose Data Is It Anyway?”, explores data ownership, provenance, and data collection. Libraries worldwide are hosting events with workshops, talks, and games. Love Data Week aims to raise awareness about data literacy and responsible data use. Find out more about International Love Data Week.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/whose-data-it-anyway-celebrate-lovedata25</guid></item><item><title>Upcoming Rensselaer Faculty and Staff Teaching and Learning Opportunities for Spring 2025</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/12/18/2024/upcoming-rensselaer-faculty-and-staff-teaching-and-learning</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Teaching and Learning Collaboratory has just announced the upcoming trainings for Rensselaer faculty and staff for the Spring 2025 term. Please be sure to visit the training page link below for a listing of sessions, dates, times, format, and a link to register. Link to trainings: &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory/#Workshops"&gt;Teaching and Learning Collaboratory Workshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/12/18/2024/upcoming-rensselaer-faculty-and-staff-teaching-and-learning</guid></item><item><title>HR to Hold Professional Development Workshop, “Leading from Anywhere”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: At Rensselaer, we maintain that “leadership” involves a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. In this workshop, scheduled to be held from 9am to 11am on February 20, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership not as positional or based on title, but rather on values and actions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere</guid></item><item><title>As of 02/12/2025, RPI managed computers will lock after 15 minutes of inactivity</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/02122025-rpi-managed-computers-will-lock-after-15-minutes-inactivity</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting 02/12/2025, RPI managed computers will lock after an activity time out of 15 minutes. Devices unused for 15 minutes will be locked requiring your login password to unlock. This measure complies with data privacy regulations to prevent unauthorized access to sensitive information if an individual leaves their computer unattended, ensuring that only the authorized individual can access the system by requiring a password to log back in after the inactivity period.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/02122025-rpi-managed-computers-will-lock-after-15-minutes-inactivity</guid></item><item><title>Have YOU Joined the Teaching and Learning Newsflash List Yet?</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/12/03/2024/have-you-joined-teaching-and-learning-newsflash-list-yet</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A list for faculty interested in instructional technologies, pedagogy, and innovative tools for classroom engagement, the Teaching and Learning e-Newsflash has been created to support faculty who wish to try new technologies and strategies for learning. Subscribers will also be notified about any on-campus teaching and learning workshops/events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:32:30 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/12/03/2024/have-you-joined-teaching-and-learning-newsflash-list-yet</guid></item></channel></rss>
