<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>The McKinney Student Writing Contest Is Now Open!</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-mckinney-writing-contest-open</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2025 McKinney Writing Contest is open, and both undergraduate and graduate students are invited to &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/mckinney-writing-contest/submission"&gt;submit&lt;/a&gt; entries in a wide range of categories to win cash prizes! Entries are due by midnight on March 11, 2025. Please see the &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/mckinney"&gt;McKinney Writing Contest page&lt;/a&gt; for more information, or &lt;a href="mailto:McKinney@rpi.edu"&gt;email the contest committee&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-mckinney-writing-contest-open</guid></item><item><title>OIP Schedules Study Abroad Welcome Back and Info Session</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/01/02/2025/study-abroad-welcome-back-and-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 4:00PM to 5:00PM on Wednesday, January 8 in the CBIS Bruggeman Room, all undergraduates — and particularly students who would like to study abroad in summer/fall 2025 — are encouraged to join the Office of International Programs as they welcome fall Study Abroad students back to campus to hear about their experiences, as well as learn about study abroad opportunities, application processes, and deadlines. Cookies and cocoa will be provided!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/01/02/2025/study-abroad-welcome-back-and-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Ballinger Named Fellow of the National Academy of Inventors</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/12/19/clint-ballinger-named-fellow-national-academy-inventors</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Clint Ballinger, Ph.D., professor of practice in Rensselaer’s Department of Mechanical, Aerospace, and Nuclear Engineering, is among 170 inventors elected by the National Academy of Inventors (NAI) to its 2024 Class of Fellows.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/12/19/clint-ballinger-named-fellow-national-academy-inventors</guid></item><item><title>MSE Seminar to be Held January 8</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-27cfa0a2-00002a01calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, January 8, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Dr. Jim Schuck, of the Department of Mechanical Engineering at Columbia University, will present “Strain-localized excitons and quantum nonlinear van der Waals photonics in 2D semiconductors.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-27cfa0a2-00002a01calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“The Thacher Computing Instrument: The Supercomputer of the 19th Century” to be Topic of RPIrates Monthly Meeting</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/thacher-computing-instrument-supercomputer-19th-century-rpirates-computing-history-talk-weds</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In celebration of Rensselaer 200, RPIrates: The RPI Users Group, will kick off 2025 at 6:00PM on January 8 in Amos Eaton 217 with a special RPIrates Computing History Talk about the famous Thacher Computing Instrument, invented by RPI graduate Edwin Thacher (1863); Dr. John Erickson will discuss the instrument’s history, explain its theory of operation and demonstrate its use.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/thacher-computing-instrument-supercomputer-19th-century-rpirates-computing-history-talk-weds</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Spring 2025 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-spring-2025-course-requests-please-read</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Spring 2025 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-spring-2025-course-requests-please-read</guid></item><item><title>“Developing Your Leadership Presence” Topic of HR Professional Development Seminar</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-developing-your-leadership</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: Scheduled to be held from 8:00AM to noon on Wednesday, January 15, 2025, this seminar is designed to help leaders improve their ability to authentically influence and connect with others. Discussion topics include the relationship between personal presence and ability to influence people and situations, a recognition of how specific behaviors increase or decrease an influential presence and steps to authentically interact with others in a more influential manner.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-developing-your-leadership</guid></item><item><title>Training Webinar to Focus on Reviewing Fall End-of-Term Student Course Evaluations</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0193-e4bc234c-0000609bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, January 7, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - This webinar is for instructors and TAs who would like to better understand — or get a refresher course in — the various ways they can review their student course evaluations in HelioCampus.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0193-e4bc234c-0000609bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HR to Hold Professional Development Seminar, “Developing Your Leadership Presence”</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-0cff9034-00007b1bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, January 15, 2025 8:00 AM - 12:00 PM - This seminar is designed to help leaders improve their ability to authentically influence and connect with others by striking a balance between strength and warmth. Discussion topics include the relationship between personal presence and ability to influence people and situations, how specific behaviors increase or decrease an influential presence, and steps to authentically interact with others in a more influential manner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-0cff9034-00007b1bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
