<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>RPI Libraries is accepting student applications for evening and weekend shifts!</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-accepting-student-applications-evening-and-weekend-shifts</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Shifts start in January 2026. Review the available shifts in the full announcement and indicate your availability in the online application.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-accepting-student-applications-evening-and-weekend-shifts</guid></item><item><title>Do you want to Inspire the next generation of Engineers?</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-832cc5c3-00007b62calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Attention, Freshmen and Sophomores! Applications are now open for the Engineering Ambassadors! This group has a passion for K-12 Educational Outreach and works with local schools to promote STEM exploration, making engineering more accessible to a younger audience. Please visit the link to our application. Applications close at midnight on January 23, 2026. Contact Recruitment Coordinator, Katie Titus with questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-832cc5c3-00007b62calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CMDIS Annual Research Symposium Abstract Deadline Announcement</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019b-1465069b-0000037bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, December 13, 2025 12:00 AM - Sun , January 4, 2026 11:55 PM - The Center for Materials, Devices and Integrated Systems (CMDIS) Annual Research Symposium will take place on Friday, February 6, 2026, at the Heffner Alumni House. Abstract submissions for talks, posters, and Art-in-Science are due Sunday, January 4, 2026, at 11:59 PM. Contributions across microelectronics, materials, energy, sustainability, modeling, manufacturing, robotics, and control are welcome. Details and…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019b-1465069b-0000037bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Campus Card Office Returning to the Student Union</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/campus-card-office-moving-student-union-january-12-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to share that the Campus Card Office is coming back to the heart of campus! After several years at 2144 Burdett Ave., we’ll be relocating to the Student Union starting January 12, 2026, making it even easier for you to connect with us where campus life happens.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/campus-card-office-moving-student-union-january-12-2026</guid></item><item><title>Information Security – Phishing Awareness during the Holiday Break</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/information-security-phishing-awareness-during-holiday-break</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Our Information Security team has observed a recurring trend during the holiday season: cybercriminals often target organizations and college campuses with phishing attacks. These emails may contain suspicious links, malicious attachments, or fraudulent websites designed to steal login credentials. Falling victim to such attacks can compromise your device or RCS account, potentially leading to data loss, system instability, and serious security vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/information-security-phishing-awareness-during-holiday-break</guid></item><item><title>Fall Parking Permits to expire on 12/22/2025</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-parking-permits-expire-12222025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please note that any Fall semester only parking permits will expire on 12/22/2025. Spring semester only permits will be available starting on 12/23/2025. If you purchased a full year permit, no further action is needed. Continue to park as normal.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-parking-permits-expire-12222025</guid></item><item><title>Apply Now to RPI’s Collegiate Science &amp; Technology Entry Program!</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/apply-now-rpis-collegiate-science-technology-entry-program</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Collegiate Science &amp;amp; Technology Entry Program (CSTEP) is excited to announce that applications for the Spring semester are now open! CSTEP is an academic enrichment program designed to support New York State residents who are economically disadvantaged and pursuing careers in STEM or health-related fields. Don’t miss this chance to elevate your academic and professional journey-apply today by visiting here and reach out to InclusiveExcellence@rpi.edu with any questions!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/apply-now-rpis-collegiate-science-technology-entry-program</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff Quick Learn Webinar: Best Practices for Dealing with Student Absences</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019b-23aad5af-00001abecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, January 7, 2026 2:00 PM - 2:30 PM - In this workshop we will offe some best practice strategies for dealing with student absences. Maureen Fodera (Office of Undergraduate Education) will be presenting this workshop. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019b-23aad5af-00001abecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Spring 2026 Syllabus Available - Complete by January 26, 2026</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-spring-2026-syllabus-available-complete-january-26-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The HelioCampus syllabus module is now available for faculty to access for the spring. Based on the requirements from the Provost’s office, faculty should have their syllabi published in HelioCampus by January 26, 2026. HelioCampus will publish all syllabi automatically on February 2, 2026. Please review post to register for one of the two training sessions that will be offered in January 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-spring-2026-syllabus-available-complete-january-26-2026</guid></item></channel></rss>
