<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Women’s Soccer Set to Host Prospect Day on September 22</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/8/12/womens-soccer-set-to-host-prospect-day-on-september-22.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI Women’s Soccer will be hosting a prospect day on Sunday, September 22 from 10am to 3:00pm at East Campus Athletic Village. Prospective student-athletes from the Classes of 2025, 2026, 2027, and 2028 who are interested in competing at the collegiate level are welcome to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/8/12/womens-soccer-set-to-host-prospect-day-on-september-22.aspx</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Announces September 24 Resume Review/Tabling Session with RPI Alumni</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2695</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Anytime between 1:00PM and 3:00PM on Tuesday, September 24 in the 15th Street welcome lobby of the Rensselaer Union, students are welcome to stop by to connect with Gore associates who graduated from RPI and have their resume reviewed in between classes! Company associates will also offer career advice, share their experiences from post graduation, and highlight what it’s like to work in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2695</guid></item><item><title>First Game Jam of the Year Starting September 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/september-game-jam-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Game Dev Club is hosting its first Game Jam of the year starting on Friday, September 20 at 5pm in Sage 2411! Kick off the fall and join us once again (or for the first time!) for a 48-hour jam, with overnight breaks beginning at 10:00 PM both Friday and Saturday nights and doors opening again at 8:00 AM each morning. Teams will be formed to design your own game from scratch. Students of all years, areas of study, and experience levels are welcome to participate!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/september-game-jam-0</guid></item><item><title>Student Health Center Posts Mpox Update for Fall 2024</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/mpox-update-fall-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mpox is a viral illness that can be spread between people or between people and certain animals, and generally causes mild flu-like symptoms and a rash. On August 14, the World Health Organization declared the mpox outbreak as a public health emergency of international concern in the Democratic Republic of the Congo and neighboring countries. Although the current risk to Rensselaer is very low, the campus should be aware of the disease and note what can be done to prevent an outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/mpox-update-fall-2024</guid></item><item><title>RPI students take day off to celebrate the Ferris wheel — and other inspirational alums’ work</title><link>https://www.timesunion.com/education/article/rpi-students-take-day-celebrate-ferris-wheel-19760947.php</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer might be known for nose-to-the-grindstone expectations and hard classes, but on September 13, students and other campus community members took a day off to celebrate the Ferris wheel as part of RPI’s 200th anniversary. The ride was erected in honor of George Ferris, an 1881 RPI graduate who designed and built the first Ferris wheel for the 1893 World Fair in Chicago. On September 14, RPI opened the event to the public, offering free food and Ferris wheel rides to all attendees.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.timesunion.com/education/article/rpi-students-take-day-celebrate-ferris-wheel-19760947.php</guid></item><item><title>“Leaders in Action” Conversation to be Held with Trustee Thomas G. Capek ‘86</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23152&amp;ecid=23152&amp;ciid=80367&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From noon to 2:00 PM on Thursday, September 26, the RPI community is invited to join Professor Azita Hirsa and Trustee Thomas Capek ’86, senior vice president and chief engineer at Corning Incorporated, in the CBIS auditorium as he speaks as part of the Department of Industrial and Systems Engineering’s “Leaders in Action” series and discuss the evolution of his engineering career and leadership in the 21st century.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23152&amp;ecid=23152&amp;ciid=80367&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Systems Engineering and Technology Management Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8fefbac8-00005755calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 25, 2024 6:00 PM - 6:30 PM - Hosted by Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., this information session focuses on Rensselaer’s flexible, project-based, online Systems Engineering and Technology Management graduate degree that will help prepare decision-makers with broader and deeper capabilities in leading dynamic organizations. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/SETM25"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8fefbac8-00005755calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Multimedia Services Announces Reauthentication Requirement for Webex</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-announces-reauthentication-requirement-webex</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting on Monday, September 23, all Webex applications (desktop or mobile) will require reauthentication every 30 days. Please allow extra time when launching the application to confirm that it is properly authenticated prior to any meeting. This will improve security and ensure the software is updated.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-announces-reauthentication-requirement-webex</guid></item><item><title>Retirement Reception for Paul Martin to be Held September 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-e1a138a7-00001371calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 20, 2024 2:00 PM - 4:00 PM - After more than 40 years of service at Rensselaer, Paul Martin will be retiring. The campus community is welcome to attend this reception being held in Paul’s honor, and to join the Administration Division in thanking Paul for his service to the Institute and wishing him well in his retirement.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-e1a138a7-00001371calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Women’s Tennis Competes in Empire Cup at Skidmore</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/15/womens-tennis-competes-in-empire-cup-at-skidmore.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend of September 14-15, the Rensselaer women’s tennis team participated in the Empire Cup on the Skidmore campus, and went on to find success in doubles play throughout the two-day event, with the Engineers winning eight out of ten doubles matches.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/15/womens-tennis-competes-in-empire-cup-at-skidmore.aspx</guid></item><item><title>HR Professional Development Workshop, “Leading Virtually,” to be Held September 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-999afcb9-00007e2fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 26, 2024 9:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Virtual and remote work creates both challenges and opportunities to work as a cohesive team focused on achieving results. This seminar explores the fundamentals of Rensselaer’s Flexible Work Program, teaches leaders how to communicate more effectively in a virtual environment and focus their team by keeping team members and their goals visible and in sight, and how to enhance trust among members separated by time and/or distance.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-999afcb9-00007e2fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Fac/Staff Quick Learn Webinar, “Considering Brave Spaces vs. Safe Spaces in Discussions,” to be Held September 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-d77d6a6e-000051d9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 24, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - In this workshop, Maureen Fodera of the Office of Undergraduate Education will look at the strategies around building brave spaces versus safe spaces, and what that means in situations when in a learning environment with a group of peers discussing challenging topics. Be sure to &lt;a href="https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/ra1747a7b03fe78c3c1473cd22a444f27"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you’d like to participate!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-d77d6a6e-000051d9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>TIAA Confidential In-Person Retirement Counseling Sessions to be Held October 1</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6fb44d84-00006c0acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 1, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - A TIAA Financial Consultant will be available for one-on-one consultations on a broad range of retirement topics. Attend this upcoming event to help you become better informed and more confident about Rensselaer’s retirement plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 12:34:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6fb44d84-00006c0acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
