<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:33:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Hosts Graduate Certificate Review on July 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-c121b1fc-00001ca3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, July 22, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., in a 30-minute information session highlighting the whole range of Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs. These certificates are three courses in length, developing targeted ability groups, and can be completed in as little as seven months. Please register if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:33:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-c121b1fc-00001ca3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Am I Enough of Me: Theatrical Production and Research Project</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2025/am-i-enough-me-theatrical-production-and-research-project</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Thursday / July 24, 2025 at 6:00 pm Am I Enough of Me concerns individuality and timing. This theatrical performance tells the story of what can happen when our dreams are put on hold. Three college graduates must choose between their passion projects and a dystopian corporate future. Their choice is explored through multiple mediums including musical theater, augmented reality, AI video, audience interaction, and art song. Presented by Communication and Media Department Performance Cliff Watson&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:33:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2025/am-i-enough-me-theatrical-production-and-research-project</guid></item><item><title>Webinars to be Included in Webex Suite</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinars-be-included-webex-suite-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Webex Suite meeting platform will include Webinars as of July 31, 2025. All Webinars, including those scheduled prior to this date but running after July 31, will be run on the new platform. In order to utilize the new experience, the installed Webex App must be version 45.4 or newer. If you need assistance to update your Webex App, please submit a support request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:33:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinars-be-included-webex-suite-0</guid></item></channel></rss>
