<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>RAA to Sponsor “College Discovery” Webinar September 11</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10016&amp;cid=22964&amp;ecid=22964&amp;ciid=79674&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with RPI’s Offices of Alumni Engagement and Enrollment Management, the Rensselaer Alumni Association will present a “College Discovery” webinar from 7:00PM to 8:30PM on Wednesday, September 11, covering a range of important topics for alumni who are preparing their children for the college selection, recruitment, and admissions process.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10016&amp;cid=22964&amp;ecid=22964&amp;ciid=79674&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Updated Laboratory Safety Course Available in Percipio</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/updated-laboratory-safety-course-available-percipio</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Environmental Health &amp;amp; Safety (EHS), in collaboration with Human Resources, has updated Rensselaer’s laboratory safety course, which is an important part of Rensselaer’s overall safety program and provides the campus community with resources for conducting laboratory activities in a safe and efficient manner. Students, faculty and staff who work in laboratory and research spaces are required to take Rensselaer’s Laboratory Safety Series, which is now available in Percipio.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/updated-laboratory-safety-course-available-percipio</guid></item><item><title>Information Session for 2025 Project RFP: Quantum Computing Track 4 to be Held August 16</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/information-session-2025-project-rfp-quantum-computing-track-4</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 1:00PM to 3:00PM on Friday, August 16, RPI and IBM representatives will discuss details of the Track 4 RFP and answer questions regarding the scope and process for this call. &lt;a href="https://tinyurl.com/52ety7v3"&gt;Registration&lt;/a&gt; is required to participate; please &lt;a href="mailto:fontak@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Kathy Fontaine&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/information-session-2025-project-rfp-quantum-computing-track-4</guid></item><item><title>Multimedia Services Announces Mediasite Capture Now Available to Faculty, Staff</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-announces-mediasite-capture-now-available-faculty-staff</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services is pleased to announce that Mediasite Capture is now available to staff and faculty through MyMediasite. Capture allows recording of video through a browser without installing any additional software. Please refer to &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/articles/24815238635277-Creating-Content-Recording-Video-Using-Mediasite-Capture"&gt;ITSSC&lt;/a&gt; for more information on Mediasite Capture.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-announces-mediasite-capture-now-available-faculty-staff</guid></item><item><title>Invite CCPD to Your Classroom or Club/Organization!</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/invite-ccpd-your-classroom-or-cluborganization</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to inspire and prepare students for the professional world, Rensselaer’s Center for Career Development is here to help! CCPD’s team provides tailored presentations on a range of career-related topics, and can come into your class, club, or organizations meeting to present on a topic of your choosing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/invite-ccpd-your-classroom-or-cluborganization</guid></item><item><title>Fac/Staff Quick Learn Webinar to Offer Tips for Engaging Students</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-4ceefed6-000077d6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, August 21, 2024 11:00 AM - 11:30 AM - Assigning reading assignments and micro video lectures prior to class are great ways for students to gather initial knowledge. &lt;a href="https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/ra96fe508834470c479bd9391dd04b69c"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Maureen Fodera, of the Office of Undergraduate Education, as she offers tips on how instructors can use these means to engage and motivate students and help them extract important details/understandings….&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-4ceefed6-000077d6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
