<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>NSF GRFP Bootcamp scheduled to run August 4th through 25th</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0193-92eddcd8-000012e1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, August 4, 2025 12:00 AM - Mon , August 25, 2025 12:00 AM - Participants complete online modules on their own time. Develop strong application materials for this 3 year fellowship which provides a salary and tuition for graduate school. Feedback on documents available for all applicants. For more information email madige@rpi.edu. Register for the Bootcamp https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV_85M3eKII9idFy5M&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0193-92eddcd8-000012e1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Multiple Paving Projects, July 16th - August 6th</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/multiple-paving-projects-july-16th-august-6th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please be advised that the Site Services Department will be overseeing multiple paving projects within the coming weeks. We will be repaving sidewalks in the following areas: Around the Rensselaer Student Union, West Lot, Albright Lot, all sidewalks surrounding Albright, Cook Drive from the circle in front of the Houston Field House to the intersection of Sunset Avenue and sidewalks between the buildings in Stacwyck.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/multiple-paving-projects-july-16th-august-6th</guid></item><item><title>Single Course Enrollment Options with Rensselaer at Work this Fall Term | Aug. 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-37b18fc5-000045eccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, August 7, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., will host this Rensselaer at Work information session reviewing the online graduate programs for working professionals and provide course enrollment options to make an immediate impact on one’s work. Participants can also explore courses for developing valuable skills that benefit employee and employer alike. Please register to attend&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-37b18fc5-000045eccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Apple Back-to-School Promotion (6/25-9/30)</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/apple-back-school-promotion</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Apple Back-to-School Promotion is back! Running from June 25 until September 30, 2025, the Rensselaer community can enjoy FREE Apple AirPods 4 Active Noise Cancelling (ANC) with the purchase of an eligible iMac or MacBook -or- FREE Apple Pencil Pro with the purchase of an eligible iPad Air or iPad Pro. Check out rensselaerstore.com to see what eligible devices are available. When you add an eligible device to your cart, you must also add the FREE item to your cart for the promotion to be…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/apple-back-school-promotion</guid></item><item><title>2025-2026 Parking Permits Available August 1st</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-2026-parking-permits-available</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Parking and Transportation Department is pleased to announce that the 2025-2026 parking permits are now available for purchase.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-2026-parking-permits-available</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Leading from Anywhere” | Aug. 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-19775290-00006e0fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, August 5, 2025 9:00 AM - 11:30 AM - At Rensselaer, we maintain that “leadership” involves a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. Whether it be leading a particular project or initiative, assisting others in overcoming obstacles and capitalizing on opportunities, or catalyzing co-creation with colleagues. In this workshop, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership not as…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-19775290-00006e0fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Fall 2025 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-fall-2025-course-requests</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Fall 2025 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-fall-2025-course-requests</guid></item></channel></rss>
