<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 12:35:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Info Session on Analytics, Machine Learning, AI</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-349b99c1-00002737calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 18, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for a session highlighting Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning and AI. Attendees can expect to learn how data can inform better decisions, and will review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/analytics18"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 12:35:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-349b99c1-00002737calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Summer 2024 Session II Student Course Evaluations Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-03500370-00004fa6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, June 17, 2024 (all day) - Course evaluations are now open for the Summer II 2024 semester. Your feedback is very important to the Institute, the five schools, and their departments, so please be sure to complete evaluation surveys for all your courses! Evaluations will be available through Saturday, June 29.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 12:35:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-03500370-00004fa6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Announces RPI Capital Region Careers Networking Night</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2627</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re eager to explore internship, co-op and job opportunities in the Capital Region area, look no further! Just put together your best business casual attire and then get ready to join the Center for Career and Professional Development in the Russell Sage Dining Hall from 6PM to 8PM on Wednesday, June 26 for an engaging evening of networking with esteemed local employers representing various industries.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 12:35:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2627</guid></item><item><title>“Personal Financial Management” to be Topic of Summer Professional Development Seminar</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8e7b22eb-018e-c32738c5-000074a1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 25, 2024 2:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Please join Professor Johan Maharjan, Lally School of Management, as he presents insight into personal financial management. Please note that this is a hybrid event; limited in-person seating is available at CBIS Bruggeman conference room, or participants may join via Webex.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 12:35:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8e7b22eb-018e-c32738c5-000074a1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Campus Summer Shuttle Service to Continue for City Station Residents</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/06/13/2024/campus-summer-shuttle-service</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Parking and Transportation will be continuing shuttle service to Rensselaer students living at the City Station residences for the summer, with shuttle service to run from 10AM to 10PM Monday through Saturday, and from noon to 8PM on Sunday. The City Station shuttle bus stop is located in front of City Station East.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 12:35:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/06/13/2024/campus-summer-shuttle-service</guid></item></channel></rss>
