<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>The Title IX Office Issues a Call for Student Participation in their Sexual Misconduct Awareness and Prevention Survey</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/sexual-misconduct-awareness-and-prevention-survey-underway</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Your Voice Matters – please check your RPI email for an invitation to respond to the Sexual Misconduct Awareness and Prevention Survey. Your participation in this confidential survey will assist us in our ability to protect and support students at RPI. All matriculated students on the Troy campus, who are over age 18, are encouraged to participate. We want to hear from you. The survey link is found in your RPI email.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/sexual-misconduct-awareness-and-prevention-survey-underway</guid></item><item><title>Constellation Energy Virtual Info Session to be Held November 12</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/constellation-energy-virtual-info-session-be-held-november-12</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 5:30PM to 6:30PM EST on Tuesday, November 12, Constellation will host an information session for Rensselaer undergraduate students to discuss their initiatives and commitment to sustainability, the evolving energy industry, and what a career path at Constellation would look like! There will also be time for Q&amp;amp;A, networking, and one-on-one chats to answer your questions and get to know you better.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/constellation-energy-virtual-info-session-be-held-november-12</guid></item><item><title>Global Virtual Career Fair to be Held for LGBTQ+ Students, Recent Graduates</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/global-virtual-career-fair-lgbtq-students-and-recent-graduates</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: November 13, 2024, 12:00 - 3:00 pm - Rensselaer is a proud sponsor of this year’s #WorkFair, a global virtual career fair for LGBTQ+ students and recent graduates in Europe, Asia, and the Americas. This free event will feature opportunities to attend virtual panels and workshops, engage in live chats with recruiters, and book interviews. &lt;a href="https://workfair.vfairs.com/#"&gt;Please visit the WorkFair website for more information and to register&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/global-virtual-career-fair-lgbtq-students-and-recent-graduates</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Peer Career Advisors to Host “Major Mixer” November 14</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/major-mixer-hosted-ccpd-peer-career-advisors-be-held-november-14</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD’s Peer Career Advisors from 6pm to 8pm on Thursday, November 14 in the second-floor banquet hall in Russell Sage Dining Hall for a night of mingling and mixing with students across majors at RPI! Students will discuss their majors, experiences at RPI, and careers while enjoying a casual night with free food.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/major-mixer-hosted-ccpd-peer-career-advisors-be-held-november-14</guid></item><item><title>iEAR to Present Talk by Francois-Joseph Lapointe on November 6</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-talk-francois-joseph-lapointe</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As part of HASS’ Art, Science &amp;amp; Religion series, join iEAR from 5:00PM to 6:30PM on Wednesday, November 6 in the CBIS Auditorium for a talk by Francois-Joseph Lapointe, who will discuss how the transmission of the microbiome at birth plays a crucial role in shaping an individual’s health and development, representing a dynamic interplay between maternal and neonatal microbial communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-talk-francois-joseph-lapointe</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Schedules November 8 Information Session</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9b03988d-00002abccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, November 8, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/general8"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates, and describes how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9b03988d-00002abccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC to Present American Premiere of Marina Rosenfeld’s μ (mu)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-96af8242-00004b3fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, November 8, 2024 7:00 PM - All are invited to a performance and video installation by Marina Rosenfeld as she makes the American premiere of her EMPAC-commissioned work “μ (mu)”. Titled after the mathematical term for friction or touch and inspired by the artist’s longstanding interest in turntablism, the work takes place along the surface of a dubplate at the moment of inscription.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-96af8242-00004b3fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Mercer XLab Now Accepting Printed Circuit Board Designs to Prototype Projects</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-now-accepting-printed-circuit-board-designs-prototype-projects</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have a PCB design for a personal project, course project, or research project that you’d like to print out and test within 24 hours before sending it out for manufacturing? The Mercer XLab’s LPKF S104 Milling System, CONTAC S4 Copper Plating System, and Multipress S4 allow them to print multilayer boards, so please &lt;a href="mailto:MercerXLab@rpi.edu"&gt;email the lab&lt;/a&gt; to get the request form and help make the lab’s prototyping process more efficient by giving them a chance to print your board!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-now-accepting-printed-circuit-board-designs-prototype-projects</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of the Veterans Day Remembrance Event!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-dd48cbd5-00000954calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 11, 2024 10:45 AM - 1:00 PM - All are welcome to join event host Air Force ROTC, Detachment 550, for a Veterans Day remembrance event at the Louis Rubin Memorial Approach to celebrate RPI veterans past and present. A reception, hosted by the Office of the Registrar, will follow at EMPAC’s Evelyn’s Cafe.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-dd48cbd5-00000954calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>United Way to Host Annual Thanksgiving Feast November 21</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-681c9a5c-00000af3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 21, 2024 11:30 AM - 2:00 PM - The campus community is welcome to come to Russell Sage Dining Hall to enjoy a Thanksgiving feast featuring roast turkey, ham, and all the trimmings for just $15! Vegan and gluten-free options will also be available. Reservations are required, and payment by cash, check, or departmental charge must be received by November 13. Take-out meals will also be available upon request, but no walk-ins will be accepted.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-681c9a5c-00000af3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Meet and Greet” Lunch, Presentation to Feature Columbia University Professor Dr. Adam Brickman</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-f77d96f3-00005374calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 7, 2024 12:00 PM - &lt;a href="mailto:felchg@rpi.edu"&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; to attend this meet-and-greet lunch with Columbia University Professor of Neuropsychology, Dr. Adam Brickman, who, following lunch, will present a talk titled “Is there a role of cerebrovascular disease in our conceptualization of Alzheimer’s Disease?” at 3PM in the Bruggeman Room. Everyone is highly encouraged to attend both the lunch and presentation to make the most of this unique learning experience!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-f77d96f3-00005374calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Enjoy the Festival of Lights at RPI Diwali Night 2024!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-fce34798-00001512calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, November 9, 2024 5:00 PM - 10:00 PM - &lt;a href="https://shorturl.at/zzlb6"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join the Graduate Indian Students Association for an evening of vibrant performances, lively music, dance, a cultural fashion show, a delicious Indian buffet, and much more!…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-fce34798-00001512calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Quantum Computing Users Group Monthly Meeting Scheduled for November 13</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-monthly-meeting-1</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join students and colleagues interested in quantum computing, or those currently working on the subject, at noon on Wednesday, November 13 in Amos Eaton 214. If you are interested in presenting, please &lt;a href="mailto:morgat5@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Tom Morgan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-monthly-meeting-1</guid></item><item><title>2024 United Way Pledge Campaign Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-a04d1e4c-00001f38calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 18, 2024 12:00 AM - Mon , December 16, 2024 12:00 AM - The United Way of the Greater Capital Region works to advance the common good by focusing on basic needs, family support and financial stability, and Rensselaer has long been an active and proud partner in helping to create long-lasting systemic change toward a better tomorrow. Once again, Rensselaer’s United Way volunteers call upon the generosity of the campus community to help address societal challenges.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-a04d1e4c-00001f38calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>TIAA to Offer Confidential In-Person Retirement Counseling November 13</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6fb72d28-00006e56calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 13, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - A TIAA Financial Consultant will be available for one-on-one consultations on a broad range of retirement topics. Attend this upcoming event to help you become better informed and more confident about Rensselaer’s retirement plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6fb72d28-00006e56calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
