<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CCPD Virtual Info Session with Crane Currency Rescheduled for August 8</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2632</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In an event originally scheduled for July 25, students are invited to join the team at Crane Currency from 6:30PM to 7:30PM on Thursday, August 8 to learn about career paths and company culture within the organization, as well as upcoming opportunities for Arch students seeking an Away experience. Also review the&lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/edu/jobs/8907483"&gt;Chemical Engineering R&amp;amp;D Internship or Co-Op opportunity&lt;/a&gt; posted in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2632</guid></item><item><title>Study Abroad Applications Now Being Accepted for Spring 2025</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of International Programs’ &lt;a href="https://rpi-sa.terradotta.com/index.cfm?FuseAction=Abroad.Home"&gt;application portal&lt;/a&gt; is now open to undergraduate students who wish to apply for spring 2025 study abroad. Deadlines, contact info, and application guidelines are available via the &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025"&gt;International Programs website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</guid></item><item><title>RPI Libraries Join PALCI Consortium</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-has-joined-palci-consortium-replaces-connectny-services</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer Libraries are pleased to announce that they have recently joined the Partnership for Academic Library Collaboration and Innovation, or PALCI. With this membership, which replaces the Libraries’ previous ConnectNY services, Rensselaer students, faculty, and researchers will gain access to and benefit from PALCI’s extensive resource-sharing network, which includes academic and research libraries and a vast collection of over 46 million items shared by member institutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-has-joined-palci-consortium-replaces-connectny-services</guid></item><item><title>Updated Laboratory Safety Course Available in Percipio</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/updated-laboratory-safety-course-available-percipio</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Environmental Health &amp;amp; Safety (EHS), in collaboration with Human Resources, has updated Rensselaer’s laboratory safety course, which is an important part of Rensselaer’s overall safety program and provides the campus community with resources for conducting laboratory activities in a safe and efficient manner. Students, faculty and staff who work in laboratory and research spaces are required to take Rensselaer’s Laboratory Safety Series, which is now available in Percipio.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/updated-laboratory-safety-course-available-percipio</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of the Incoming RPI Student Sendoff!</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22878&amp;ecid=22878&amp;ciid=79412&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 1PM to 3PM on Sunday, August 11 at Pat’s Barn in the Rensselaer Technology Park, come join the RPI Alumni Chapter of Hudson Mohawk to meet and welcome local first-year students from the Class of 2028! It’s a great way to enjoy food and refreshments while making connections, sharing stories, and networking with our newest class. The cost is $10 per person; all local current and incoming RPI students area are invited free of charge courtesy of the Hudson Mohawk Chapter alumni.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22878&amp;ecid=22878&amp;ciid=79412&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Joint ECSE/COGS Seminar to be Held August 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0190-ff0e72e7-00002b8fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, August 5, 2024 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Join ECSE and COGS for a seminar titled “Transforming General-Purpose Robots into Trusted Teammates with HARMONIC,” with Dr. Sanjay Oruganti, Post-doctoral Researcher in the Language-Endowed Intelligent Agents (LEIA) Lab in Rensselaer’s Cognitive Science Department.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0190-ff0e72e7-00002b8fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Information Session for 2025 Project RFP: IBM-RPI Future of Computing Research Collaboration (FCRC)</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/information-session-2025-project-rfp</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When: Thursday, August 8, 2024, 1:00 pm – 2:00 pm Where: https://rensselaer.webex.com/meet/fontak Meeting number: 737 518 548 RPI and IBM representatives will be discussing details of the RFP and answering questions regarding the scope and process for this call. Be sure to register (https://forms.gle/gVJtDB6woSGqtsMx8) if you’d like to participate! Contact: Kathy Fontaine, fontak@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/information-session-2025-project-rfp</guid></item><item><title>CCPD to Hold URP/Handshake Faculty Training Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/urphandshake-faculty-training-session-august-16th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday, August 16, from 9:30AM to 11:00AM in DCC 209, CCPD will host an interactive opportunity for faculty members to learn how to use Handshake for posting undergraduate research positions. Participants will learn about Handshake, set up an employer profile, and prepare to post their first job. Light snacks will be provided. Space is limited, so interested faculty should &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/form/urp-handshake-training-8-16"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/urphandshake-faculty-training-session-august-16th</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity to Offer Confidential In-Person Retirement Consultation Sessions August 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f855c60-00005898calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, August 19, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f855c60-00005898calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
