<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:32:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>DotCIO Announces Change to Single Sign-On Process, Effective May 22</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/change-single-sign-process-effective-05222024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;To improve security, DotCIO is releasing a change to the single sign-on process that will become effective as of Wednesday, May 22, 2024. Under this updated process, the initial login page will only prompt users to enter their Username and then click Login; the next page will ask for their password, and to click Login a second time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:32:20 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/change-single-sign-process-effective-05222024</guid></item><item><title>RPI Athletics Announces Let’s Go Red! Golf Outing for 2024</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=9794&amp;cid=22489&amp;ecid=22489&amp;ciid=78790&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI Athletics is pleased to announce that it will host its annual Let’s Go Red! Golf Outing from 8AM to 3PM on Monday, June 3 at Normanside Country Club in Delmar, New York. You can help support RPI Athletics at this event by registering to play, becoming a sponsor, or providing auction and raffle items, so come out and support Rensselaer’s student-athletes and Athletics programs!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:32:20 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=9794&amp;cid=22489&amp;ecid=22489&amp;ciid=78790&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work MBA for Professionals Review Scheduled for May 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348dc4f2-00000b4acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 23, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MBAP23"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Participants will learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with real-world MBA experience, prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations, and engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:32:20 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-348dc4f2-00000b4acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Handbook of Student Rights and Responsibilities Now Available</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/dean-students/05/20/2024/rensselaer-handbook-student-rights-and-responsibilities-summer-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://rpi.box.com/s/itdt9diqmjkfj2luqhe8irxf99f9pntu"&gt;Rensselaer Handbook of Student Rights and Responsibilities&lt;/a&gt; reflects the values, beliefs, and expectations we have as a community of scholars. It is the responsibility of each Rensselaer student to understand and comply with the rules and regulations set forth in the Handbook, as well as with the requirements set forth in other Institute policies and rules.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:32:20 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/dean-students/05/20/2024/rensselaer-handbook-student-rights-and-responsibilities-summer-2024</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity to Offer Confidential Retirement Consultation by Phone, Zoom Video Option</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8db2d34d-018e-101a53d7-0000459dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, June 3, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:32:20 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8db2d34d-018e-101a53d7-0000459dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
