<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:32:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar – “Certifications &amp; Skill Development in Percipio”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-certifications-skill-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;“Certifications &amp;amp; Skill Development in Percipio” This course introduces the tools available in Percipio to support growth through certifications and skill benchmarks. You’ll learn how to identify relevant certifications and use benchmark assessments to measure current knowledge. Perfect for employees and supervisors alike, this session will help you navigate the platform’s upskilling features and align learning with career development objectives.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:32:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-certifications-skill-0</guid></item><item><title>Spring 2026 RPI Faculty and Staff Teaching and Learning Workshops/Webinars Schedule Available</title><link>https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-2026-rpi-faculty-and-staff-teaching-and-learning-workshopswebinars-schedule</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Teaching and Learning Collaboratory has just announced the upcoming trainings for RPI faculty and staff for the Spring 2026 term. Please be sure to visit the training page link below for a listing of sessions, dates, times, and links to register! Visit the Teaching and Learning Collaboratory Workshop page for further details and to register.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:32:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-2026-rpi-faculty-and-staff-teaching-and-learning-workshopswebinars-schedule</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff Quick Learn Webinar: Best Practices for Dealing with Student Absences</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019b-23aad5af-00001abecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, January 7, 2026 2:00 PM - 2:30 PM - In this workshop we will offe some best practice strategies for dealing with student absences. Maureen Fodera (Office of Undergraduate Education) will be presenting this workshop. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:32:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019b-23aad5af-00001abecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
