<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Title IX Office Issues Call for Student Participation in Sexual Misconduct Awareness and Prevention Survey</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/sexual-misconduct-awareness-and-prevention-survey-underway</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Your Voice Matters! Please check your RPI email for an invitation to respond to the Sexual Misconduct Awareness and Prevention Survey. Your participation in this confidential survey will assist us in our ability to protect and support students at RPI. All matriculated students on the Troy campus, who are over age 18, are encouraged to participate. We want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/sexual-misconduct-awareness-and-prevention-survey-underway</guid></item><item><title>Therapy Dog Group Sessions to Continue November 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-5c4e86e1-00007765calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 20, 2024 5:00 PM - 6:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://linktr.ee/therapydoggroup"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join other students in the Mueller Center classroom to relax, de-stress, and pet some furry friends! If you have any questions or would like more information, please contact Emma Atkinson in the Mueller Center.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-5c4e86e1-00007765calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Second Economics Virtual Info Session to Be Held November 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/economics-virtual-info-sessions</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for an online info session on our PhD in Applied Econ and Policy and MS in Econ programs on Wed, Nov 20th, at 10:00 AM. Learn about the program structures and focus areas, ideal applicants for each program, and funding opportunities. Registration is required to receive the Zoom link.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/economics-virtual-info-sessions</guid></item><item><title>RPI Student Work Featured in Dezeen</title><link>https://www.arch.rpi.edu/2024/11/rpi-student-work-featured-in-dezeen/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Ten RPI student architecture projects have been featured in the online magazine Dezeen as part of their Dezeen School Shows, with featured projects including work from each year of the five-year B. Arch. programs at Rensselaer. The school show is a partnership between Dezeen and Rensselaer.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.arch.rpi.edu/2024/11/rpi-student-work-featured-in-dezeen/</guid></item><item><title>Procurement Services to Present Supplier Showcase on December 5</title><link>https://procurement.rpi.edu/announcements/procurement-services-host-9th-annual-supplier-showcase</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All faculty, staff, and students involved in Rensselaer’s procurement process are invited to attend this year’s Supplier Showcase, which will be held from 11:00am to 2:00pm on Thursday, December 5 in the Alumni Sports &amp;amp; Recreation Center. Stop by to network with Rensselaer’s key suppliers and the Procurement Services team, get your professional head shot taken, win exciting raffle prizes from the suppliers, check out the photo booth, and enjoy festive refreshments!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://procurement.rpi.edu/announcements/procurement-services-host-9th-annual-supplier-showcase</guid></item><item><title>GrantForward Training Webinar Scheduled for November 18</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-1d19bfa5-00007abccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 18, 2024 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/wAUvVqgsggzBLDEm8"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to attend the Office for Research’s one-hour webinar with GrantForward, the funding search and recommendation service to which all Rensselaer faculty, staff, and students are currently subscribed and have access. It’s a great introduction for new GrantForward users or a refresher for existing ones!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-1d19bfa5-00007abccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Event to Introduce Partnership between RPI and Albany Medical College Bioinformatics Core</title><link>https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/partnership-between-rpi-and-amc-bioinformatics-core</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us and Ramon Bossardi Ramos, PhD., Director of the Bioinformatics Core at Albany Medical College, at 2:00PM on Monday, November 18 in CBIS Bruggeman as Dr. Ramos introduces AMC’s newest research core and how it can enhance research across many disciplines at RPI. AMC and RPI are exploring a partnership that would allow researchers at either institution to use the RPI Genomics Core and the AMC Bioinformatics Core with internal rates.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/partnership-between-rpi-and-amc-bioinformatics-core</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO updates plotting instructions and print refund process</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-updates-plotting-instructions-and-print-refund-process</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO has updated instructions for printing to the plotters. The documentation is more concise and simpler to follow, which will improve the outcome of the final product. With much testing, following the updated instructions has increased the success rate of plotting. Additionally, the Adobe applications have been updated on the computers in the VCC lobby. Please click in this announcement for links to detailed Plotting and Print Refund documentation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-updates-plotting-instructions-and-print-refund-process</guid></item><item><title>Webex LTI Legacy Upgraded to Webex LTI 1.3 in Blackboard</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</link><description>&lt;p&gt;MultiMedia Services wishes to inform the campus community that Webex LTI Legacy (formerly Webex Education Connector) has been upgraded in Blackboard to the new Webex LTI 1.3 connector. This is the final upgrade prior to the start of the semester, and brings in increased stability and features for utilizing Webex within a course in Blackboard. Please refer to the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/sections/360008224951"&gt;ITSSC Knowledge Base&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity to Offer Confidential Retirement Consultation by Phone, Zoom Video Option</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f97806c-000062cbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 25, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f97806c-000062cbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Benelogic Service Outage Scheduled for November 17</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/benelogic-scheduled-service-outage</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Benelogic system maintenance has been scheduled to take place between midnight and 4:00AM ET on Sunday, November 17, and all portals will be offline during this time. After the maintenance is complete, users should be able to resume access and complete open enrollment, which ends on November 18, 2024. If you have any questions or concerns, please &lt;a href="mailto:degrol@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Lizette Degro&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/benelogic-scheduled-service-outage</guid></item><item><title>November 15 Grad Program Info Session Specifically for RPI Employees</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0193-1c159e14-00003ec2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, November 15, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/RPI15"&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work’s informational webinar just for Rensselaer employees to review RPI’s part-time, online graduate programs in engineering, analytics, leadership, and technical change management. Attendees will hear about the project-based model, learning through iteration, and how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0193-1c159e14-00003ec2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>2024 United Way Pledge Campaign Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-a04d1e4c-00001f38calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 18, 2024 12:00 AM - Mon , December 16, 2024 12:00 AM - The United Way of the Greater Capital Region works to advance the common good by focusing on basic needs, family support and financial stability, and Rensselaer has long been an active and proud partner in helping to create long-lasting systemic change toward a better tomorrow. Once again, Rensselaer’s United Way volunteers call upon the generosity of the campus community to help address societal challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-a04d1e4c-00001f38calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
