<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Book Your Appointment with COMM+D Online!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/01/03/2025/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you working on a writing assignment, oral presentation, or visual design project? Whether you’re at the beginning brainstorming stages or finishing up your final revisions, the Center for Global Communication+Design (Comm+D) can help, so be sure to schedule an appointment with a member of the Center’s trained staff!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/01/03/2025/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</guid></item><item><title>Counseling Center Announces Walk-in Hours for Spring 2025</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/walk-counseling-hours-spring-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Counseling Center invites students to meet with a counselor without a formal appointment during designated walk-in hours! Two walk-in hours are available each day: from 10am to noon on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays, and from 2:00pm to 4:00pm Tuesdays and Thursdays. Walk-in counseling is also available on a first-come, first-served basis on days when classes are in session; students who cannot attend the walk-in times can call (518) 276-6479 to schedule an appointment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/walk-counseling-hours-spring-2025</guid></item><item><title>Off-Campus Housing and Resource Fair Scheduled for February 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0193-d4f1466f-00006f50calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 12, 2025 2:00 PM - 5:00 PM - If you’re looking for an apartment next year, stop by and meet with representatives of local rental properties to discuss the many housing options available near campus!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0193-d4f1466f-00006f50calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Join the CCPD for Career Fair Info Sessions on February 11</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/join-ccpd-career-fair-info-sessions</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 5pm to 8pm on Tuesday, February 11, students are invited to attend 45-minute info sessions with select career fair employers in the Union before the fair! Please see the &lt;a href="https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/join-ccpd-career-fair-info-sessions"&gt;CCPD Spring 2025 Career Fair Info Sessions&lt;/a&gt; collection in Handshake for more info; please note that space is limited, and all sessions are on a first-come, first-served basis.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/join-ccpd-career-fair-info-sessions</guid></item><item><title>Information Session with Amphenol - February 6</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-bf68b7f6-0000570dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Thursday, February 6, 2025 5:00 PM - 6:15 PM - Join SWE for an information session with Amphenol! Food (pizza), will be provided!! RSVP at the form below to get a headcount on who is attending!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-bf68b7f6-0000570dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>McKinney Keynote: Creative Writing Craft Talk Slated for April 8</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-keynote-creative-writing-craft-talk</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us on Tues, 4/8 at 2PM in EMPAC Studio Beta for a craft talk by award-winning novelist and McKinney keynote speaker, Lan Samantha Chang. Chang is the winner of an Anisfield-Wolf Book Award for Fiction and a PEN Open Book Award. She’s received fellowships from the National Endowment for the Arts, the Guggenheim Foundation, and an award from the American Academy of Arts and Letters. Chang will be discussing the craft of fiction and her writing process. Registration is not required.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-keynote-creative-writing-craft-talk</guid></item><item><title>Lean Green Belt Certification Scheduled for February 21 - 23</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/lean-green-belt-certification-22125-22325</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Industrial &amp;amp; Systems Eng. Dept. and IISE student chapter, along with Institute of Industrial and Systems Engineers (IISE) Headquarters, will present a short course on Lean Green Belt Certification from February 22-23 on the Rensselaer campus, taught by Dr. Asian Ghosh. Register by February 7 to receive a discounted rate; the last day to register for the course is February 17.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/lean-green-belt-certification-22125-22325</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Leading from Anywhere”</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-0d09abd2-00000107calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Thursday, February 20, 2025 9:00 AM - 11:00 AM - At Rensselaer, we maintain that “leadership” involves a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. In this workshop, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership not as positional or based on title, but rather on values and actions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-0d09abd2-00000107calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Info Session for Summer 2025 IBM Visiting Student Opportunities</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/info-session-summer-2025-ibm-visiting-student-opportunities</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, February 7, 2025, 2:30 PM - 4:30 PM - The RPI-IBM Future of Computing Research Collaboration (FCRC) is seeking applicants for paid externship opportunities at IBM this summer. Each Visiting Student will work directly with IBM Researchers to accomplish specific research tasks as defined in the project expectations. &lt;a href="https://idea.rpi.edu/media/info-session-summer-2025-ibm-visiting-student-opportunities"&gt;Visit link for more information.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/info-session-summer-2025-ibm-visiting-student-opportunities</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Informational Webinar Scheduled for February 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-9897f5d4-00001281calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, February 11, 2025 5:00 PM - 5:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MBAP11"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D. as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Participants will learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with real-world MBA experience, prepare to lead dynamic and innovative organizations, and engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-9897f5d4-00001281calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff Webinar - Flipping Your Classroom - February 18</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-d25db551-00000663calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, February 18, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - This session will discuss the practice of moving traditional in-class lectures onto the web by creating engaging, media-rich content that student’s access before, during, or after class. Class time is refocused, allowing students to work on tasks and problems that apply the concepts they studied independently. &lt;a href="https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/r33008272ef92cf10ca02d01bc1a67154"&gt;Please register&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-d25db551-00000663calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
