<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>2026 Silicon Valley Career Immersion Trip- Applications Open Now!</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-silicon-valley-career-immersion-trip-applications-open-now</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Ready to see where engineering and innovation meet? RPI’s School of Engineering and Center for Career &amp;amp; Professional Development invite applications for the 2026 Silicon Valley Career Immersion Trip, a five-day experience exploring the tech capital of the world. Join a select group of students to: · Explore world-class innovators like Apple, Google, Microsoft, and PayPal (among others) through site visits and alumni events. · Connect with RPI alumni shaping the future of technology. · Gain…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-silicon-valley-career-immersion-trip-applications-open-now</guid></item><item><title>Dining Halls Point of Sale System Upgrade Coming Soon</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/dining-halls-point-sale-system-upgrade-coming-soon</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Dining will soon be implementing an update to our POS (point of sale) systems across all dining halls. This enhancement will improve our ability to identify meal plan holders during entry by displaying the RPI ID photo for cashiers, resulting in a faster transaction process.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/dining-halls-point-sale-system-upgrade-coming-soon</guid></item><item><title>LLMs and R: How Posit is Making it Easy: RPIrates Monthly Meeting (Weds, 12 Nov, 6p, AE217)</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/llms-and-r-how-posit-making-it-easy-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-12-nov-6p-ae217</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI R users are invited to the November 2025 meeting of RPIrates: The RPI R Users Group! Our topic for Weds, 12 Nov (6p, AE217) will be “LLMs and R: How Posit is Making it Easy!” In this session we’ll review the many ways that Posit, the creators of RStudio, is supporting data analytics that tightly integrates popular LLMs. RPIrates is led by Dr. John S. Erickson, Dir. of Research Operations of the Rensselaer IDEA and Chief Instigator of RPIrates. Pizza and salad starts at 5:30p.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/llms-and-r-how-posit-making-it-easy-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-12-nov-6p-ae217</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; Abbott Info Session | Nov. 11</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-abbott-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come learn about Abbott’s Clinical Associates program and discover a career in electrophysiology! Meet with a representative from Abbott on Tuesday, November 11th from 6-7pm–details and registration can be found in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-abbott-info-session</guid></item><item><title>CEE Fall Seminar Series - Dr. Grigorios Lavrentiadis Asst. Professor from the University of Buffalo | Nov. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-77dd03ab-00007a99calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 12, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - “A Non-Ergodic Ground Motion Model for the Groningen, Netherlands: Merging Physics-Based Simulations and Empirical Observations”. We present a new non-ergodic ground motion model (GMM) for the Groningen natural gas field in the Netherlands, aimed at improving the region’s seismic hazard characterization. Non-ergodic GMMs offer the ability to reduce aleatory variability, which often controls the seismic hazard, especially at longer return…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-77dd03ab-00007a99calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty Spotlight on Research &amp; Impact webinar series-Miki Amitay | Nov. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-08376e3f-00005abdcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 12, 2025 2:00 PM - 2:30 PM - Vehicles That Feel What if we could change the shape of a vehicle—without moving parts—just by controlling how air flows around it? Prof. Amitay will introduce active flow control, a new technology that uses tiny devices to manage airflow and improve how vehicles perform. This approach can reduce drag, save fuel, and even replace traditional control surfaces like flaps or rudder. It is a simple idea with powerful potential for the future of…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-08376e3f-00005abdcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Colloquia: Ali Tajer “Causal Representation Learning” | Nov. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-153fd099-00006de3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 12, 2025 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Ali Tajer received a B.Sc. and an M.Sc. degree in Electrical Engineering from Sharif University of Technology, an M.A. in Statistics, and a Ph.D. in Electrical Engineering from Columbia University. During 2010-2012, he was a Postdoctoral Research Associate at Princeton University. He is currently a Professor of Electrical, Computer, and Systems Engineering at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-153fd099-00006de3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ECSE Master Practitioner Seminar: “Advantages and Disadvantages of Silicon Carbide Semiconductors for Power Electronic Systems” | Nov. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d681cc1-00001dd9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 12, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join us for an ECSE Master Practitioner Seminar: “Advantages and Disadvantages of Silicon Carbide Semiconductors for Power Electronic Systems” with Dr. Michael Schutten. Abstract and speaker bio can be found at the event URL.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d681cc1-00001dd9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MSE Seminar: Dr. Arthi Jayaraman | Nov. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-4a4fec88-0000311acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 12, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Machine learning based analyses and interpretation of structural characterization data from soft materials Arthi Jayaraman Departments of Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering and Materials Science and Engineering University of Delaware – Newark&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-4a4fec88-0000311acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>25th Sydney Archer Lecture in Organic &amp; Medicinal Chemistry | Nov. 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-551390c6-00003f38calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 11, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Arthur Taveras, Chief Executive Officer &amp;amp; Entrepreneur of Transform Therapeutics in Boston, MA, will speak about “An RPI Graduate’s Journey: Navigating Opportunities &amp;amp; Risks in Biotech”.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-551390c6-00003f38calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents: Artists Felici Asteinza and Joey Fillastre on 11/12</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-artists-felici-asteinza-and-joey-fillastre</link><description>&lt;p&gt;MILAGROS co-founders Felici Asteinza and Joey Fillastre, along with their ever-changing cast of collaborators, create site-specific works that explore the history of place through striking arrangements of color and mark. With an exuberant style that champions the hand made and the intuitive, MILAGROS energizes public spaces with effervescent patterns that obliterate the seams between structures and highlight the unique attributes of the surrounding architecture. Join virtually at 6pm on 11/12.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-artists-felici-asteinza-and-joey-fillastre</guid></item><item><title>MMS Collaboration Software Training Series: Webex Event Training | Nov. 13</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/mms-collaboration-software-training-series-webex-event-training</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Planning a virtual event or supporting a student webinar? Join us for a practical walkthrough of Webex Events as part of the MMS Collaboration Software Training Series. Register now for this webinar presented via Webex on Thursday November 13, 2025 from 11am-12pm: https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/r4f44a1f130dd0f14e0e8989c146e99b3 Learn how to: - Schedule and brand your event - Use polls, Q&amp;amp;A, and chat tools - Access recordings and reports - Host with confidence&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/mms-collaboration-software-training-series-webex-event-training</guid></item><item><title>Physics, Applied Physics and Astronomy Colloquium: Professor Julian Georg, Senior Lecturer, Department of Physics, Applied Physics, and Astronomy, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute | Nov. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-5b0a85ef-00004a83calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 12, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Title: “The Expansion of the Universe Explained for Everyone”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-5b0a85ef-00004a83calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI Quantum Users Group Meeting (Weds, 12 Nov, 4p, AE217)</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/qiskitsession-and-initialize-and-statevector-functions-rpi-quantum-users-group-meeting-weds</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The next meeting of the Quantum Users’ Group will be held at 4pm on Wednesday November 12 in AE 217. We will discuss Qiskit_session and the initialize and statevector functions plus topics of concern from the attendees.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/qiskitsession-and-initialize-and-statevector-functions-rpi-quantum-users-group-meeting-weds</guid></item><item><title>RPI Grad ISA Diwali Night | Nov. 15 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-5f4b7885-00002be3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, November 15, 2025 5:30 PM - 9:30 PM - The RPI Graduate Indian Students Association invites you to a Diwali celebration with beautiful performances and a sumptuous Indian buffet on November 15th, 2025, at Academy Hall Auditorium at 5:30 pm (EST). Join us for an evening filled with dance, music, fashion show, games, and get a chance to win exciting prizes! This Diwali is as much yours as it is ours, and we need your support in this grand celebration. We have a nominal registration…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-5f4b7885-00002be3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Medical Ethics in a Time of Crisis Roundtable | Nov. 11</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/medical-ethics-time-crisis</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Liz Bowen (Bioethics &amp;amp; Humanities, SUNY Upstate Medical Center), Johanna Crane (Alden March Bioethics Institute), Michele Friedner (Comparative Human Development, University of Chicago), and Matthew Wolf-Meyer (Science and Technology Studies, RPI) for a conversation about medical ethics from 2pm-3:30pm in Sage 5510.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/medical-ethics-time-crisis</guid></item><item><title>STS Colloquium: Everyone Communicates: Making Social Worlds and Valued People in the Present | Nov. 12</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-everyone-communicates-making-social-worlds-and-valued-people-present</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this talk, Michele Friedner (Comparative Human Development, University of Chicago) analyzes how special educators at a school for children with intellectual disabilities in India engage in collaborative sense-making projects with the children with whom they work (although there is the question of what collaboration actually means) and in the process they create create rich social worlds that are oriented towards the present and the near future. Join us 11/12 at 11:30am in Sage 5711.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-everyone-communicates-making-social-worlds-and-valued-people-present</guid></item><item><title>Supporting Student Well-being: A Training for Faculty and Staff | Nov. 12 (Please register)</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/mainstreaming-mental-well-being-training-series-faculty-and-staff</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Students’ mental health directly affects classroom engagement, learning, and success outside the classroom. Join us for an interactive workshop designed to help faculty and staff confidently support students who may be struggling with mental health concerns. You will learn practical tools to recognize signs of distress, respond effectively, and connect students to the right resources. Lunch is provided!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/mainstreaming-mental-well-being-training-series-faculty-and-staff</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Leading from Anywhere”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere-111425</link><description>&lt;p&gt;At Rensselaer, we maintain that “leadership” involves a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. Whether it be leading a particular project or initiative, assisting others in overcoming obstacles and capitalizing on opportunities, or catalyzing co-creation with colleagues, Rensselaer community members model leadership every day. In this workshop, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere-111425</guid></item></channel></rss>
