<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>MANE Graduate Programs Information Sessions Announced</title><link>https://mane.rpi.edu/announcements/mane-accelerated-graduate-programs-information-sessions</link><description>&lt;p&gt;ACCELERATED MASTER’S(CO-TERMINAL), BS-PHD, and M.Eng., M.S. &amp;amp; Ph.D.TRADITIONAL Did you know that you could be paid to earn a PhD? Or, that you could receive a scholarship toward a Master’s degree? Attend an information session to learn about the exciting research opportunities, program requirements, funding options &amp;amp; application processes to MANE’s graduate programs. Thursday, September 18th: 10:00–11:00 a.m. in JEC-3117 Monday, September 29th: 2:00-3:00 p.m. in JEC-3117 Wednesday, October 15th…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mane.rpi.edu/announcements/mane-accelerated-graduate-programs-information-sessions</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents! “Turn the Light Around”: 16mm Plant Processed Performance and Films by Le Ratoire | Sept. 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-turn-light-around-16mm-plant-processed-performance-and-films-le-ratoire</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us September 20 at 7pm at The Sanctuary for Independent Media for screenings of 16mm plant-processed performance films, presented by Katherine Bauer and Joyce Lainé, members of the film collective Le Ratoire and Atelier MTK. The image sin each film emerge before our eyes through the process of a developer composed of plants, ashes, and water. The screening will be followed by Q&amp;amp;A. This event is co-sponsored by iEAR Presents and The Sanctuary for Independent Media.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-turn-light-around-16mm-plant-processed-performance-and-films-le-ratoire</guid></item><item><title>Industrial &amp; Systems Engineering- Co-Terminal/Accelerated Master’s Programs Information Session | Sept. 24</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/industrial-and-systems-engineering</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Co-Terminal/Accelerated Master’s Program Information Session All interested students are welcome! Learn about the ISE master’s programs: Industrial and Management Engineering (IME) Systems Engineering and Technology Management (SETM) September 24, 2025 1-2pm ET SCAN TO JOIN&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/industrial-and-systems-engineering</guid></item><item><title>MANE Department Seminar 9/17- Youho Lee</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-5576bbcd-000064d5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 17, 2025 10:30 AM - 11:30 AM - “Comprehensive Evaluation of Cr-Coated Accident-Tolerant Fuel Cladding in Large PWRs and Implications for advanced SMR applications”, Youho Lee, Associate Professor, Seoul National University&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-5576bbcd-000064d5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 Lecture Series</title><link>https://www.arch.rpi.edu/2025/09/fall-2025-lecture-series/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Architecture is pleased to announce its full lecture series for spring 2025. All events start 5:00pm at EMPAC Theater unless otherwise noted. Admission is free. Søren Pihlmann / pihlmann architects Adding Less, Changing More – When Form Features Constraint Wednesday, September 10 Wednesday, September 24 Sharon Johnston / Johnston Marklee Architecture &amp;amp; the City: Extremes &amp;amp; In-Betweens Frank Pitts ’75 Lecture Monday, September 29 J. Alfonso Quiñones / BAAQ 20 years under the…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.arch.rpi.edu/2025/09/fall-2025-lecture-series/</guid></item><item><title>Stephanie Boluk and Patrick LeMieux: Hands Free: A History of Accessible Alt Ctrls |Sept. 23</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/stephanie-boluk-and-patrick-lemieux-hands-free-history-accessible-alt-ctrls</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This presentation begins with a brisk survey of the history of hands-free video game interfaces before comparing and contrasting two devices that articulate two different design philosophies: the NES Hands Free and the Octopad. Rather than thinking about accessibility as a single-player problem, these controllers engage the social, political, and environmental aspects of video games to change the way we play. Join us on September 23 at 4:30pm on Webex.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/stephanie-boluk-and-patrick-lemieux-hands-free-history-accessible-alt-ctrls</guid></item><item><title>Closure of Sage Avenue Roadway and Sidewalk Beginning September 22</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/closure-sage-avenue-roadway-and-sidewalk-beginning-september-22</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Beginning Monday, September 22, 2025, RPI Facilities Management will begin a project to replace leaking steam pipes along the north sidewalk in front of E Dorm and across the roadway at the Sage Avenue campus entrance. As a result, the north sidewalk and entrance to the academic campus off Sage Avenue will be closed and will remain closed for approximately five to six weeks. Additionally, Sage Avenue will be closed between the crosswalk at Troy Building and the crosswalk on the east side of E…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/closure-sage-avenue-roadway-and-sidewalk-beginning-september-22</guid></item><item><title>CBE Seminar Series - Dr. Michael S. Ziegler | Sept. 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-3e1e8a44-00005998calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 17, 2025 9:30 AM - 10:30 AM - CBE Seminar Series continues with Dr. Micah Ziegler, Assistant Professor from Georgia Institute of Technology. Dr. Ziegler’s seminar titled “Data-informed modeling to accelerate the improvement of sustainable energy and chemical technologies” is opened to all. Refreshments will be available in Ricketts Coonley Lounge (120) at 9:00 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-3e1e8a44-00005998calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents! Le Ratoire Plant Processing Workshop | Sept. 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-le-ratoire-plant-processing-workshop</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, Le Ratoire artist collective will work with participants to learn how to make black &amp;amp; white film/photo developer using just local plants, ashes, and water. No industrial products, nothing from the store! We will go over the techniques of photograms (also known as rayograms) and phytography, two ways of exposing and making images on photo paper without needing to use a camera. Join us September 20 at 2pm at the NATURE Lab at the Sanctuary for Independent Media.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-le-ratoire-plant-processing-workshop</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff: Maximize Your Dental Benefits – Virtual MetLife Session | Sept/ 17</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-maximize-your-dental-benefits-virtual-metlife-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Faculty and Staff are invited to participate in a virtual dialogue with MetLife Dental Plan representatives, designed to help ensure you have an exceptional member experience. On Wednesday, September 17 from 11:00 am to 12 noon attendees will receive: An overview of RPI’s dental program A tutorial on how to find an in-network provider and use the online member portal An opportunity to engage directly with MetLife representatives and members of the Division of Human Resources team&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-maximize-your-dental-benefits-virtual-metlife-session</guid></item><item><title>SoE Fall 2025 Midterm Course Surveys: Adding Additional Questions to a Course Section (Instructor Training) | Sept. 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-349c50d6-000063facalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 29, 2025 1:30 PM - 2:00 PM - Learn how to add additional questions to your School of Engineering Midterm. The institute has standard defined questions for the SoE midterm, but if you wanted to add a few questions on top of what is already defined this training is for you. Please click the link in the See section to register.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:33:28 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-349c50d6-000063facalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
