<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:33:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Surfing the Manifold: Adventures in Latent Space with David Rokeby | June 4</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/surfing-manifold-adventures-latent-space-david-rokeby</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As they learn, AI systems build rich and nuanced fields of possibilities, often called latent spaces. At BMO Lab we love to make this latent space tangible and explorable. Director of the BMO Lab, David Rokeby, will do live demonstrations of a few of the systems the lab has been developing, and there will be a chance for attendees to interact with them themselves. Join us on June 4 from 4-6pm in the CBIS Auditorium.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:33:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/surfing-manifold-adventures-latent-space-david-rokeby</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Hosts Systems Engineering Information Session on June 6</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-96ac81ec-0196-d442c843-00004918calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, June 6, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - This 30-minute information session is hosted by Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., and will focus on Rensselaer’s Systems Engineering and Technology Management graduate degree. The degree is digitally delivered, flexible, and project-based to prepare decision-makers with broader and deeper capabilities in leading dynamic organizations. The session will highlight program details and how you can select graduate certificates relevant to your work to complete…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:33:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-96ac81ec-0196-d442c843-00004918calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>No Pressure, Just Pride: LGBTQ+ Mixer | June 18</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/no-pressure-just-pride-lgbtq-mixer-june-18</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Celebrate Pride Month with the CCPD! On Wednesday, June 18th from 5-7pm, students, faculty, and staff who identify as LGBTQ+ or allies are invited to a low-stakes mixer in Sage Banquet Hall. Participants will get to know each other in a relaxed environment and learn about resources on- and off-campus. Hors d’oeuvres and refreshments will be served and the CCPD’s Clothing Closet will be available. Come as you are and join us for a night of community and joy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:33:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/no-pressure-just-pride-lgbtq-mixer-june-18</guid></item><item><title>Qiskit Global Summer School Open Enrollment</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/qiskit-global-summer-school-open-enrollment</link><description>&lt;p&gt;IBM Announced Open Enrollment for Qiskit Global Summer School 2025. QGSS25 is an excellent opportunity to learn about quantum computing, either out of personal interest or to prepare for future course work. Click in for schedule and enrollment information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:33:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/qiskit-global-summer-school-open-enrollment</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience several “Supervisory Simulations” with colleagues. In addition, the importance of coaching employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team capacity will be explored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:33:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-0</guid></item></channel></rss>
