<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Tesla x RPI Application Workshop, Tech Talk, Networking to be Held February 19 at 2:00 pm</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/tesla-x-rpi-application-workshop-tech-talk-networking-be-held-february-19-2-pm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Tesla will host a session that will provide guidance on the resume-building and application process to help RPI students stand out! Immediately following the Tech Talk, Tesla will transition to a networking event in the DCC Great Hall where students can speak one-to-one with engineering managers. Seating is limited, so &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/login"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/tesla-x-rpi-application-workshop-tech-talk-networking-be-held-february-19-2-pm</guid></item><item><title>How to Stay Involved with RPI as an Alum</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-d7b74424-00001a0bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, February 19, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join our info session to learn how to stay involved as an alum. You will learn about the Office of Alumni Engagement, how to be an alumnus, alumni benefits, athletics &amp;amp; affinity groups, post graduation checklist, and more!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-d7b74424-00001a0bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Game Development Club Presents Valentine’s Day Game Jam</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/game-development-club-presents-valentines-day-gamejam</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Love is in the air! Join the RPI Game Development Club on February 14 at 6 p.m. in Sage 2411 for a Valentine’s Themed Game Jam, and make a Multiplayer Game in 48 hours to play with the special people in your life! Overnight breaks begin at 10:00 PM on both Friday and Saturday nights and doors re-opening at 8:00 AM each morning. Open to all RPI students! Contact Aiden Crossfield (crossa2@rpi.edu) to sign up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/game-development-club-presents-valentines-day-gamejam</guid></item><item><title>Math Colloquium: Karl Pierce (Flatiron Institute) - February 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-b2eb7479-00006292calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 19, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - This Mathematical Sciences Colloquium will feature a presentation titled “On the Utilization of Matrix-Free Tensor Decompositions in the Approximation of Accurate Tensor Algorithms” by Dr. Karl Pierce, Postdoctoral Research Fellow at the Flatiron Institute’s Center for Computational Quantum Physics.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-b2eb7479-00006292calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CEE Seminar Speaker - Dr. Marc Edwards - University of Virginia Tech - February 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-ad950f59-000026c2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 19, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - “The Politicization of American Science: Lessons from the Aftermath of the Flint Water Crisis”. After the declaration of the Flint Federal Emergency in January 2015, opportunists came to Flint from academia, Hollywood and the media to exploit the tragedy for their own benefit. Flint residents were lied to repeatedly. Some academics claimed…. Further information at the seminar. Meeting number (access code): 2863 861 9814 Meeting password: 4AKqVPhd3Q7&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-ad950f59-000026c2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Industrial and Systems Engineering Spring Colloquium</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/industrial-and-systems-engineering-spring-colloquium-feb-26</link><description>&lt;p&gt;February 26, 2025 11:00 AM - 11:50 AM - Professor Bopaya Bidanda from the Department of Industrial Engineering at the University of Pittsburgh will present a talk on “Innovation &amp;amp; AI: Balancing Efficiency, Sustainability and Developing Emerging Roles for IE, and Implications for IE Education.” Held in the DCC 324 , followed by a reception until 12:45. Everyone is welcome.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/industrial-and-systems-engineering-spring-colloquium-feb-26</guid></item><item><title>Lean Green Belt Certification: February 21 - Febrary 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-ae46a88e-0000487fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, February 21, 2025 4:00 PM - Sun , February 23, 2025 6:00 PM - The Industrial &amp;amp; Systems Engineering Dept. and IISE student chapter, along with Institute of Industrial and Systems Engineers (IISE) Headquarters, present a short course on Lean Green Belt. Taught by Dr. Asish Ghosh. Register by 2/7/2025 to receive a discounted rate. Last day to register for the course is 2/17/2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-ae46a88e-0000487fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Dining Welcomes New Catering Director</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/auxiliary-services/02/03/2025/rensselaer-dining-announces-their-new-catering-director</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Dining is excited to announce Rebecca Hanesack as the new Director of Catering at RPI, bringing 25 years of hospitality experience to the role. During her studies at Siena College, Rebecca began her career in hospitality. Involved in nearly every operational and administrative support role, she gained a comprehensive understanding of the industry from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/auxiliary-services/02/03/2025/rensselaer-dining-announces-their-new-catering-director</guid></item><item><title>Being &amp; Becoming: Quartet led by trumpeter Peter Evans - Corrected Date: February 21</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-d739223c-00007edbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, February 21, 2025 7:00 PM - All are invited! Being &amp;amp; Becoming, the quartet led by trumpeter Peter Evans, gives a standing-room-only concert featuring some of the most forward-thinking young musicians in Jazz and Contemporary music. Experience Being &amp;amp; Becoming live in the immersive EMPAC Studio 2 venue, with charged lighting design by Azumi O E heightening the alchemic creation and recreation of musical worlds onstage. Limited capacity. $5 in advance for RPI community.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-d739223c-00007edbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>No ALAC Drop-In Tutoring on February 17th – Resumes February 18th</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/advising-learning-assistance/02/10/2025/no-alac-drop-tutoring-february-17th-%E2%80%93-resumes-february-18th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;ALAC drop-in tutoring will not be available on Monday, February 17th, due to the holiday. Tutoring will resume on Tuesday, February 18th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/advising-learning-assistance/02/10/2025/no-alac-drop-tutoring-february-17th-%E2%80%93-resumes-february-18th</guid></item><item><title>“Whose Data Is It Anyway?” Celebrate #LoveData25</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/whose-data-it-anyway-celebrate-lovedata25</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI Libraries celebrates Love Data Week 2025, an international data event held annually in February. This year’s theme, “Whose Data Is It Anyway?”, explores data ownership, provenance, and data collection. Libraries worldwide are hosting events with workshops, talks, and games. Love Data Week aims to raise awareness about data literacy and responsible data use. Find out more about International Love Data Week.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/whose-data-it-anyway-celebrate-lovedata25</guid></item><item><title>Spring Lunch and Learn Series: Helping Students Learn</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-lunch-and-learn-helping-students-learn</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Faculty are invited to a spring Lunch and Learn Series on Helping Students Learn. This is a 3-part series on research-based teaching theories and methods. The first session will be on February 26 with a focus on Accessing Prior Knowledge—Preparing Students to Learn New Material. Registration is limited. The series is sponsored by the MANE Department and funded by the National Science Foundation grant # 2235345, NSF IUSE/PFE:RED A&amp;amp;I Curriculum integration through collaborative teaching and mentoring: adapting an integrated system for engineering formation&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-lunch-and-learn-helping-students-learn</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO anounces a new employee request form for technology needs</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-anounces-new-employee-request-form-technology-needs</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO has released a new employee request form for technology needs available in their IT Services and Support Center (ITSSC) request system. This form is a centralized request for technology needs for new hires, including transferring from a different Division, such as computer/laptop, software, network and shared resources access, printers, and phone requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-anounces-new-employee-request-form-technology-needs</guid></item></channel></rss>
