<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Free Flu Shot Clinic to be Held for Students October 30</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/free-flu-shots-ecav-103024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Student Health Center will be holding a free flu shot clinic on Wednesday, October 30 from 9:00 AM until 3:30 PM at the East Campus Athletic Village (ECAV).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/free-flu-shots-ecav-103024</guid></item><item><title>RPIrates Monthly Meeting: “Linux Shell Expansion for R Dummies”</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/linux-shell-extensions-r-dummies</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stepping into the Land of Linux is unavoidable for serious data analysts, and a mastery of the command line is a definite superpower for R users. Shell expansion enables Linux users to generate complex commands and manipulate data efficiently. In this discussion we’ll use the echo command explore various types of expansions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/linux-shell-extensions-r-dummies</guid></item><item><title>Graduate “Lunch and Learn” Event to Highlight Personal Financial Management</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-97e010bd-00002106calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 6, 2024 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM - During this session, Professor Johan Maharjan will present insight into personal financial management, discuss the core areas of managing personal finance, and offer strategies for budgeting, tackling debt, using credit cards, saving for retirement, and much more. Limited seating for this hybrid event will be available in the CBIS Bruggeman Room, or participants can attend via Webex. Lunch will be served from 11-11:30 AM.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-97e010bd-00002106calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>H2M architects + RPI Student Meet &amp; Greet to be held November 6</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/h2m-architects-engineers-presents-rpi-student-meet-greet</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join H2M at their Troy office right on River Street with food, non-alcoholic drinks and refreshment and music. This is a casual opportunity for RPI students to come meet professionals across architecture, engineering, construction and environmental sciences from a local employer. H2M is open to full-time seekers and interns in multiple areas.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/h2m-architects-engineers-presents-rpi-student-meet-greet</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Posts Reminder Regarding Compliance with Campus Email Policy</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-posts-reminder-regarding-compliance-campus-email-policy</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Members of DotCIO’s IT Security team wish to remind all members of the Rensselaer community that Institute policy states that email accounts obtained through third parties may not be used in conducting the business of the Institute, and that ensuring &lt;a href="https://dotcio.rpi.edu/it-security/compliance-rensselaer-email-policy"&gt;compliance with the Rensselaer email policy&lt;/a&gt; is crucial.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-posts-reminder-regarding-compliance-campus-email-policy</guid></item><item><title>“Allyship in Action” Panel Event to be Held October 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-c0a048b3-00001006calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 30, 2024 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - All Rensselaer students, staff, faculty, and alumni are invited to take part in this virtual Webex event to hear from a panel of lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender, and queer (LGBTQ+) individuals from the Rensselaer community as they discuss the meaning and importance of allyship, and how to help create safe and supportive communities for LGBTQ+ individuals.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-c0a048b3-00001006calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Find Out What “The Buzz” is All About!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/10/28/2024/fall-2024-uged-buzz</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Undergraduate Education is excited to announce the Fall 2024 &lt;a href="https://rpi.app.box.com/s/ym9u6zvsnkqymo3dbphj4mdikygnlhrh"&gt;UGED Buzz newsletter&lt;/a&gt;, which highlights happenings from spring/summer 2024. UGED will publish a newsletter each fall and spring term so everyone in the campus community can hear about the exciting initiatives that are going on within the department!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/10/28/2024/fall-2024-uged-buzz</guid></item><item><title>Mercer X Affiliated Club Interest Meeting, Friday, November 1st, 8-9 pm, Mercer XLab Clubhouse</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-x-affiliated-club-interest-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a part of a student club that could use an electronic makerspace as a second home? Does your club want to learn and share best practices with others? Do you need a space for workshops? Does your club want to improve its recruitment and retention? Join us Friday, November 1st, 8 pm in the Mercer XLab and Mercer X Lab Clubhouse on the 6th floor of the JEC to learn about what the Clubhouse offers and what we will ask of you! The Mercer X Clubhouse was created by students like you, for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-x-affiliated-club-interest-meeting</guid></item><item><title>Mercer XLab NOW ACCEPTING Printed Circuit Board Designs to Prototype Projects</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-now-accepting-printed-circuit-board-designs-prototype-projects</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have a PCB design for a personal project, course project, or research project that you’d like to print out and test within 24 hours BEFORE sending it out for manufacturing? Our LPKF S104 Milling System, CONTAC S4 Copper Plating System, and Multipress S4 enable us to print multilayer boards. Please help us make the Mercer XLab prototyping process efficient by giving us a chance to print your board! We need practice! Email MercerXLab@rpi.edu to get the request form.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-now-accepting-printed-circuit-board-designs-prototype-projects</guid></item><item><title>HR Posts 2024 New York State Election Information Regarding Time Off to Vote</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/new-york-state-election-law-ss-3-110-posting-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;With Election Day right around the corner, Rensselaer’s Division of Human Resources has some timely reminders for all faculty and staff who are registered to vote.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/new-york-state-election-law-ss-3-110-posting-2024</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Systems Engineering &amp; Technology Management Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9afec06e-000020f1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 31, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Hosted by Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., this information session focuses on Rensselaer’s flexible, project-based, online Systems Engineering and Technology Management graduate degree that will help prepare decision-makers with broader and deeper capabilities in leading dynamic organizations. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/SETM31"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9afec06e-000020f1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Don’t Miss “I Dream” in Concert on November 1!</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/i-dream-concert</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, November 1, 2024 at 7:00 pm – In partnership with RPI, the Musical Dramatic Arts Foundation is proud to present a concert version of the musical “I Dream,” which tells the story of the final 36 hours of Martin Luther King Jr.’s life as seen through the eyes of his closest friend, Ralph Abernathy, as the Civil Rights leaders grappled with justice, identity, and the burden of leadership. &lt;a href="https://www.rpi.edu/bicentennial/i-dream"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://tickets.empac.rpi.edu/TheatreManager/1/online?performance=525"&gt;Buy tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/i-dream-concert</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of Black Families Technology Awareness Day</title><link>https://bftad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/be-part-black-families-technology-awareness-day-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled for Saturday, February 1, Black Families Technology Awareness Day 2025 is designed to excite and engage K-12 students and their parents or guardians in science, technology, engineering, the arts and mathematics! Program proposals are being sought for the event and submissions are due by November 1; campus community members are invited to register through December 5 to volunteer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 12:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bftad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/be-part-black-families-technology-awareness-day-2025</guid></item></channel></rss>
