<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer Student to Explore Whether Jupiter Moon Can Support Life</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/13/rensselaer-student-explore-whether-jupiter-moon-can-support-life</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Brianna Casey ’26 is one of 40 undergraduate students nationwide to be selected for NASA’s Europa Inspiring Clipper: Opportunities for Next-Generation Scientists, or ICONS, internship program. The program, which supports the Europa Clipper mission with the goal of determining whether Jupiter’s moon, Europa, has “conditions suitable to support life,” and matches students with mentors for ten weeks to conduct research.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/13/rensselaer-student-explore-whether-jupiter-moon-can-support-life</guid></item><item><title>RPI in the News: An AI-assisted commencement and blending art with tech</title><link>https://www.wamc.org/show/the-best-of-our-knowledge/2024-05-13/an-ai-assisted-commencement-and-blending-art-with-tech</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In the first segment in this episode of WAMC’s “The Best of Our Knowledge” radio program, host Lucas Willard and Jim Hendler, Director of the Future of Computing Institute at Rensselaer, discuss how Rensselaer’s bicentennial Commencement ceremony will feature special guest Emily Warren Roebling, brought to life with the help of artificial intelligence technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wamc.org/show/the-best-of-our-knowledge/2024-05-13/an-ai-assisted-commencement-and-blending-art-with-tech</guid></item><item><title>7th Annual Lavender Graduation to be Held May 16</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-0baf5a9d-000043e7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 16, 2024 3:00 PM - 4:30 PM - All are invited to join the Rensselaer LGBTQ+ Task Force to celebrate the accomplishments of our LGBTQ+ graduates! The event will feature guest speaker Ray Lutzky ’02, PhD ’14, VP of Strategic Partnerships at Element451. Graduating students, please &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/lavgradreg"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend; &lt;a href="mailto:LGBTQTaskForce@rpi.edu"&gt;contact the LGBTQ TaskForce&lt;/a&gt; if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-0baf5a9d-000043e7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HASS to Hold “DE-FENCE Part 2” Living Art Installation May 18</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-de-fence-line-becomes-territory</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Rensselaer’s School of Humanities, Arts and Social Sciences from 1pm to 4pm on Saturday, May 18 for “DE-FENCE Part 2: The Line Becomes a Territory,” as Margaretha Haughwout leads participants in the creation of DE-FENCE, a living participatory art installation at the NATURE Lab, located at 3319 6th Avenue in downtown Troy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-de-fence-line-becomes-territory</guid></item><item><title>Every Day Matters: Optimism for the Future: Kamilia Nicolas</title><link>https://everydaymatters.rpi.edu/optimism-for-the-future-kamilia-nicolas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=optimism-for-the-future-kamilia-nicolas</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Kamilia Nicolas ’24 thrives in high-pressure environments. A senior at Rensselaer, Nicolas was class president when she entered college in the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic, managing to lead the freshmen and work with the university administration through the then unknown territory. She also flourished as an intern in the New Jersey Assembly and the New York City Council. But planning the Capital Region’s first-ever Youth Climate Career Summit has been her most challenging opportunity to date.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://everydaymatters.rpi.edu/optimism-for-the-future-kamilia-nicolas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=optimism-for-the-future-kamilia-nicolas</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Syllabus Available for Summer Term</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-available-summer-term</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer faculty should note that the HelioCampus (formerly known as AEFIS) syllabus module will be available to access for the Spring Term on April 29. Based on the requirements from the Provost’s office, faculty should have their syllabi published by June 3; HelioCampus will publish the syllabi automatically on June 10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:31:43 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-available-summer-term</guid></item></channel></rss>
