<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CRCC Internship Fair to be Held November 14</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/crcc-internship-fair-1114</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Still searching for a spring or summer internship? Planning to stay local? CRCC is hosting its 8th annual Internship Fair, which will be held from noon until 3:00PM on Thursday, November 14 and is open to RPI students of all majors. Employers will be hiring from various industries, so be sure to &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/career_fairs/51876/student_preview?token=7H0BANe2OiVNCWIazjvKAUd7XSp25qBOztiyxWsUfBZ9Fi6s2JqaXA"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/crcc-internship-fair-1114</guid></item><item><title>Warning about Text Message (Smishing) Scams</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/warning-about-text-message-smishing-scams</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This is to alert you about a rise in smishing scams pretending to be from RPI leadership. These fake messages (smishing) might look like they are from President Schmidt or other officials, trying to trick you into giving away personal or RPI related information. Stay vigilant! If you get a suspicious message do not click any links, share personal information or even respond and report it to your mobile carrier.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/warning-about-text-message-smishing-scams</guid></item><item><title>Mercer X Affiliated Club Interest Meeting, Friday, November 1st, 8-9 pm, Mercer XLab Clubhouse</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-x-affiliated-club-interest-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a part of a student club that could use an electronic makerspace as a second home? Does your club want to learn and share best practices with others? Do you need a space for workshops? Does your club want to improve its recruitment and retention? Join us Friday, November 1st, 8 pm in the Mercer XLab and Mercer X Lab Clubhouse on the 6th floor of the JEC to learn about what the Clubhouse offers and what we will ask of you! The Mercer X Clubhouse was created by students like you, for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-x-affiliated-club-interest-meeting</guid></item><item><title>Arnold Air Society to Host Fall Festival</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-d9c477d6-00006a5acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, November 1, 2024 5:00 PM - 8:00 PM - The Arnold Air Society will be hosting a Fall Festival Cornhole and Spike ball tournament at the ’86 Field, with the winner of this competition receiving a $100.00 cash prize! Admission is free, and all are welcome to attend this autumnal celebration.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-d9c477d6-00006a5acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Time Regained” Musical Performance to Highlight Oliveros-Riley Partnership</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/time-regained</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, November 6, 2024 at 4:00 pm – Showcasing the musical partnership of Pauline Oliveros and Terry Riley through the lens of time-delay techniques, this concert features the world premiere performance of Oliveros’s “The C(s) for Once (1966),” followed by Riley’s Keyboard Study #1 (1964), a piano solo that Oliveros dedicated to Riley, and other works.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/time-regained</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of Black Families Technology Awareness Day 2025!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/pre-college-initiatives/09/19/2024/be-part-black-families-technology-awareness-day-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled for Saturday, February 1, Black Families Technology Awareness Day 2025 is designed to excite and engage K-12 students and their parents or guardians in science, technology, engineering, the arts and mathematics! Program proposals are being sought for the event and submissions are due by November 1; campus community members are invited to register through December 5 to volunteer. Please see the &lt;a href="https://bftad.admissions.rpi.edu/"&gt;BFTAD website&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/pre-college-initiatives/09/19/2024/be-part-black-families-technology-awareness-day-2025</guid></item><item><title>October is Cybersecurity Awareness Month!</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/october-cybersecurity-awareness-month</link><description>&lt;p&gt;To help all members of the campus community enhance their cybersecurity knowledge, brush up on best practices and stay informed about the latest campus cybersecurity threats, DotCIO has worked with Rensselaer’s Division of Human Resources to curate a number of training resources in Percipio.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/october-cybersecurity-awareness-month</guid></item><item><title>Inventor, Student Programs Leader, Hockey Player, and Naval Admiral Inducted into Rensselaer’s Alumni Hall of Fame</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/10/29/inventor-student-programs-leader-hockey-player-and-naval-admiral-inducted-rensselaers</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Four distinguished alumni were inducted into the Rensselaer Alumni Association. Frederick J. Kahn is an LCD technology pioneer and adviser to emerging businesses. Eddie Ade Knowles was a Rensselaer educator, dean, and student programs leader, as well as a musician and civil rights advocate. Adam Oates was a member of the Rensselaer’s 1985 National Championship hockey team and an NHL Star. Ronald J. Zlatoper was a decorated Navy admiral and pilot, as well as a Rensselaer Trustee.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/10/29/inventor-student-programs-leader-hockey-player-and-naval-admiral-inducted-rensselaers</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review to be Held November 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9b024a15-000025e4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 5, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MBAP5"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Participants will learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with real-world MBA experience, prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations, and engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9b024a15-000025e4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HR to Hold “Discovering and Leveraging Your Talents” Professional Development Workshop</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-57dc5824-000038c6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 11, 2024 1:00 PM - 3:00 PM - Are you interested in learning more about options available to advance your career at Rensselaer? In this workshop, participants will learn about the Institute’s current job family structure and how positions are placed within it, join an active discussion about the tools that are available to assist in advancing one’s career, and hear from current employees about their experiences and suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:36:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-57dc5824-000038c6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
