<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:31:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Don’t Forget This Week’s Center of Gravity!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-87e1b54b-00001364calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 12, 2024 4:00 PM - 10:00 PM - The Center of Gravity is your one-stop for personal, academic and well-being success this summer! Activities include novelty food and snacks, academic support from peer tutors and course TAs, away semester searches with the CCPD, wellness and well-being activities, water coloring, Legos, book clubs and more, so be sure to visit weekly!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:31:36 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-87e1b54b-00001364calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Info Session on Analytics, Machine Learning, AI</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-349b99c1-00002737calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 18, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for a session highlighting Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning and AI. Attendees can expect to learn how data can inform better decisions, and will review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/analytics18"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:31:36 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-349b99c1-00002737calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Researcher Sheds New Light on Circadian Rhythms</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/06/04/rensselaer-researcher-sheds-new-light-circadian-rhythms</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Circadian clocks, which drive circadian rhythms, are entwined with many essential systems in living things, including humans, and because of this, disruptions to our circadian clocks are linked to higher disease rates in humans. Rensselaer’s Jennifer Hurley, Ph.D., Richard Baruch M.D. Career Development Chair and Associate Department Head of Biological Sciences, has dedicated her career to understanding the mechanisms that allow our circadian clocks to keep time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:31:36 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/06/04/rensselaer-researcher-sheds-new-light-circadian-rhythms</guid></item><item><title>Deep-Dive Presentation of Recent Advances in HPC-Quantum Integration to be Held June 14</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/collaborative-effort-ibm-quantum-hpc-quantum-integration</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 10AM to 11m on Friday, June 14, the Future of Computing Institute at Rensselaer is pleased to announce a collaborative effort with IBM Quantum for HPC-Quantum integration, and invites you to join this deep-dive presentation of recent advances in HPC-Quantum integration. The goal is to identify subject-matter experts at RPI in HPC and Quantum Computing and their applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:31:36 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/collaborative-effort-ibm-quantum-hpc-quantum-integration</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Announces RPI Capital Region Careers Networking Night</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2627</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re eager to explore internship, co-op and job opportunities in the Capital Region area, look no further! Just put together your best business casual attire and then get ready to join the Center for Career and Professional Development in the Russell Sage Dining Hall from 6PM to 8PM on Wednesday, June 26 for an engaging evening of networking with esteemed local employers representing various industries.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:31:36 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2627</guid></item><item><title>SoS to Host Thacher Park Field Trip</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7de523a7-00002c2ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 25, 2024 10:00 AM - 4:00 PM - All Arch students are welcome to join the School of Science for an academic field trip to Thacher Park. Please &lt;a href="mailto:getwrk@rpi.edu"&gt;contact the School of Science&lt;/a&gt; to sign up!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:31:36 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7de523a7-00002c2ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
