<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Good News, Students! Dining Halls Now Open for Late Lunch</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/dining-halls-now-open-late-lunch</link><description>&lt;p&gt;You asked, we listened! Starting August 24th, Commons and Russell Sage dining halls will remain open for lunch later to better fit your schedules.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/dining-halls-now-open-late-lunch</guid></item><item><title>Four Sign Celebratory Form for Men’s Basketball Class of 2029</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2025/8/21/four-sign-celebratory-form-for-mens-basketball-class-of-2029.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;TROY, NY - The Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI) men’s basketball team, led by 11th year head coach Mark Gilbride, will welcome four freshmen to campus this fall. Noah Daniel, Kellen Driscoll, Zach Hart and Payne Wood all recently signed Division III Celebratory Forms in honor of their intentions to attend RPI and join the men’s basketball program.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2025/8/21/four-sign-celebratory-form-for-mens-basketball-class-of-2029.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 Shuttle Service</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-2025-shuttle-service</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Parking and Transportation Department would like to inform the RPI community that shuttle service for the fall semester will begin on August 25th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-2025-shuttle-service</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC Multimedia Performance: Will Not Be Composed</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/program/curatorial/residencies/2025/we-will-not-be-composed</link><description>&lt;p&gt;October 20-24, 2025 We Will Not Be Composed is a multimedia performance created in collaboration with saxophonist and composer Stevie Manning, author and activist Soraya Chemaly, and new media artist Xuan to challenge perceptions of women’s anger in America. Manning and an ensemble of musicians build and rehearse the world premiere performance of the work utilizing the advanced spatial audio, video, and stage technologies of EMPAC Studio 1—Goodman.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/program/curatorial/residencies/2025/we-will-not-be-composed</guid></item><item><title>RPI Women’s Soccer Pre-Game Tailgate, East Campus Athletic Village</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10790&amp;cid=24373&amp;ecid=24373&amp;ciid=83502&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: 8/29/2025 1:00 PM to 3:30 PM We’re excited to kick off the 2025 season with a Pre-Game Tailgate and hope you’ll join us for a fun and casual afternoon before rooting on RPIWS as we take on Suffolk University! Current and former families, alumnae, and friends of RPIWS are invited! This is a great chance to meet new families, reconnect with old, and celebrate the start of another exciting season. We’ll have food, games, music, and plenty of team spirit. Let’s Go Red!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10790&amp;cid=24373&amp;ecid=24373&amp;ciid=83502&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Change in Faculty/Staff Meal Plan Option</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/change-facultystaff-meal-plan-option</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As part of our ongoing efforts to streamline services, changes in meal pricing and offering greater flexibility, we will transition fully to the Community RAD (Rensselaer Account Dollars) system at the start of the Fall 2025 Semester as the primary dining option for faculty and staff. For more information or to set up your Community RAD account, please visit the Campus Card Website, or contact the Campus Card Office at 518-276-6670 or email at campuscard@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/change-facultystaff-meal-plan-option</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff Quick Learn Webinar: Best Practices for Dealing with Student Absences | Aug. 25</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-82c55900-00001984calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, August 25, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - In this workshop we will offe some best practice strategies for dealing with student absences. Maureen Fodera (Office of Undergraduate Education) will be presenting this workshop. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-82c55900-00001984calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Connect Through Conversations” Part 1</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-connect-through</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Much of a leader’s work is accomplished through daily conversations with team members and others. These interactions, especially the tough ones, often involve intensely personal feelings (on both sides) that have an impact on the practical outcome of the conversation and the personal connection between the leader and the person. Part 1 of 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:32:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-connect-through</guid></item></channel></rss>
