<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Loss of Oxygen in Lakes and Oceans a Major Threat to Ecosystems, Society, and Planet</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/15/loss-oxygen-lakes-and-oceans-major-threat-ecosystems-society-and-planet</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Oxygen is a fundamental requirement of life, and the loss of oxygen in water, referred to as aquatic deoxygenation, is a threat to life at all levels. In fact, in research recently published in Nature Ecology and Evolution, Rensselaer’s Associate Professor Kevin Rose, Ph.D. and his collaborators describe how ongoing deoxygenation presents a major threat to the stability of the planet as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/15/loss-oxygen-lakes-and-oceans-major-threat-ecosystems-society-and-planet</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Researcher Draws Insights from COVID-19 to Inform Improved Health Care in Times of Crisis</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/18/rensselaer-researcher-draws-insights-covid-19-inform-improved-health-care-times-crisis</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Among the many challenges COVID-19 presented, disruptions in health care were among the most impactful; the large-scale pandemic resulted in millions of hospitalizations and deaths in the United States alone, and also affected many routine medical services. In research recently published in Nature Medicine, Rensselaer’s Jianxi Gao, Ph.D., associate professor of computer science, and his team measured our health care system’s resilience and adaptability to disruptions caused by COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/18/rensselaer-researcher-draws-insights-covid-19-inform-improved-health-care-times-crisis</guid></item><item><title>RPI hosts NORDTECH summit addressing microchip worker shortage</title><link>https://www.news10.com/top-stories/rpi-summit-addressing-microchip-worker-shortage/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re into the humanities, you may be wondering what microchips — aka semiconductors — do. They’re the basic building blocks for modern technologies like ATMs, planes, and AI, and there’s a worker shortage in that industry, so RPI is trying to bridge that gap through a NORDTECH program.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.news10.com/top-stories/rpi-summit-addressing-microchip-worker-shortage/</guid></item><item><title>“Leaders in Action” Conversation to be Held with Trustee Dr. John Capek</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-dd63d2bc-00002f02calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, August 1, 2024 4:00 PM - 6:00 PM - During this session, hosted by Prof. Azita Hirsa, Trustee John Capek B.S. ’83, M.E. ’84, M.E. ’85, MBA ’87, Ph.D. ’88, retired Executive Vice President at Abbott Ventures, a global healthcare company, will discuss the intersection of business, entrepreneurship, and science and engineering. Participants will have the opportunity to ask questions related to the topic. Refreshments will be served following the session.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-dd63d2bc-00002f02calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Joint ECSE/CBIS Seminar on Life Science Automation Scheduled for July 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0190-e5500128-00001be3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, July 29, 2024 10:30 AM - 11:30 AM - Professors Kerstin Thurow and Heidi Fleischer — from the Center for Life Science Automation (Celisca) at the University of Rostock, Germany — will jointly present a seminar focusing on life science automation research in Celisca.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0190-e5500128-00001be3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Study Abroad Applications Now Being Accepted for Spring 2025</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of International Programs’ &lt;a href="https://rpi-sa.terradotta.com/index.cfm?FuseAction=Abroad.Home"&gt;application portal&lt;/a&gt; is now open to undergraduate students who wish to apply for spring 2025 study abroad. Deadlines, contact info, and application guidelines are available via the &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025"&gt;International Programs website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</guid></item><item><title>Summer Outdoor Program Series Continues with Day Hike at Moxham Mountain</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-aab672e5-00002818calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 31, 2024 8:00 AM - 3:00 PM - Students are invited to join this daytime hiking trip on Moxham Mountain, located near the town of Minerva, New York! The trip, which is approximately five miles round-trip and should take about three hours, is limited to ten participants and registration is required; please look for information and registration on the Muller Center’s Instagram page, or &lt;a href="mailto:weinew2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Will Weinert&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-aab672e5-00002818calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Student Fall ’24/Spring ’25 Parking Permits Available as of August 1</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/07/17/2024/student-parking-permits-upcoming-fall-24spring-25</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Student parking permits for the Fall ’24/Spring ’25 semesters will be available for sale beginning Thursday, August 1. Please note that first-year students are not allowed to have a vehicle on campus, and all other students must &lt;a href="https://rpi.aimsparking.com/"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; and have a valid permit before parking on campus. For additional information, please contact the Parking office by phone at (518) 276-6616 or via &lt;a href="mailto:parking@rpi.edu"&gt;email&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/07/17/2024/student-parking-permits-upcoming-fall-24spring-25</guid></item><item><title>OUE Announces ChatGPT/AI Tools Informal Community Space</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/06/05/2024/chatgptai-tools-informal-community-space</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Education is pleased to announce that an informal community Webex space has been created to focus directly on AI tools being used in the classroom, and is available to share, collaborate, and brainstorm on this topic. Faculty, staff, or graduate TAs who would like to join this space should &lt;a href="mailto:foderm@rpi.edu?subject=Please%20add%20me%20to%20the%20ChatGPT%2FAI%20Tools%20Informal%20Webex%20Space"&gt;email Maureen Fodera&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/06/05/2024/chatgptai-tools-informal-community-space</guid></item></channel></rss>
