<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Join Velan Studios - An Introduction to Tech Art in the Games Industry! | April 1st, 2025</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/join-velan-studios-introduction-tech-art-games-industry</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Velan Studios for an engaging session with their developers as they introduce the exciting world of Technical Art in the games industry. Learn how tech artists bridge the gap between art and engineering, bringing creative visions to life. Whether you’re an artist, programmer, or are simply passionate about games, this conversation will shed light on the role of Tech Art at Velan Studios. Register and learn more in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/join-velan-studios-introduction-tech-art-games-industry</guid></item><item><title>An introduction to Human Spaceflight | March 25</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-a9fa44b9-0000158ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, March 25, 2025 1:30 AM - 3:00 AM - Join us for “An introduction to human spaceflight” Rick Mastracchio ’87 MS ELEC NASA astronaut class of 1996. Veteran of three Space Shuttle missions STS-106, STS-118 and STS-131, a Russian Soyuz mission TMA-11M, two ISS Expeditions 38, 39 and nine spacewalks. He has logged &amp;gt;227 days in space. Rick is currently the senior director of business development for Northrop Grumman. The presentation will be followed by a extended Questions and Answer session.Where: CBIS Auditorium&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-a9fa44b9-0000158ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Apartment Hunting Workshop | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-b90c7a22-00005a5bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 26, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:00 PM - Red &amp;amp; White invites Juniors, Seniors, and Graduate Students to come learn about apartment hunting in a new city from local realtor Kareem Jandall! The event will be held on Wednesday, March 26th from 2-3pm in the Heffner Alumni House Great Hall Kareem is the President for the Women’s Council of Realtors, owns her own real estate business, and is a Senior Real Estate Specialist.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-b90c7a22-00005a5bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Semiconductor Careers Summit to be held on March 26 at 3PM!</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/semiconductor-careers-summit-be-held-march-26-3pm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD and select employers for a day focused on semiconductor careers! The events begin with an industry overview at 3:15pm in EMPAC and will continue through 8pm, featuring a panel, raffles, and networking. &lt;a href="https://app.joinhandshake.com/career_fairs/2c876680-3e29-4218-81e7-138407f7c5bb/student_preview"&gt;Log into Handshake for more details&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/semiconductor-careers-summit-be-held-march-26-3pm</guid></item><item><title>Nutrition Workshop | March 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-428df490-000078c6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, March 27, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:00 PM in the Mueller Center Classroom - Fuel your body and mind at our Nutrition Workshops! Learn practical tips for healthy eating, meal prepping, and making nutritious choices. Open to all—empower yourself with knowledge for a healthier you! Use the link to register today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-428df490-000078c6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Intellectual Property &amp; Technology Licensing (IPTL) Seminar | April 1</title><link>https://osat.rpi.edu/announcements/intellectual-property-technology-licensing-iptl-seminar-april-1-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, April 1, 2025 11:00 AM - 1:00 PM. Join us for an exciting campuswide seminar hosted by the Office of Intellectual Property and Technology Licensing (IPTL) at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI). This is your chance to learn how IPTL supports faculty and students in turning research into real-world impact—whether through patents, licensing, or industry partnerships. &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/intellectual-property-technology-licensing-seminar"&gt;Please RSVP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://osat.rpi.edu/announcements/intellectual-property-technology-licensing-iptl-seminar-april-1-2025</guid></item><item><title>MANE Seminar Series with Stylianos Chatzidakis | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-80902b8b-0000795fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, March 26, 2025 10:30 AM - 11:30 AM - “AI-Enabled Autonomous Control for Next-Generation Reactors: Digital Twin Implementation and Experimental Insights from PUR-1”, Stylianos Chatzidakis, Assistant Professor, Associate Reactor Director, Purdue University&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-80902b8b-0000795fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ISATMA 2025 Spring Workshop: Reconnecting with Nature | March 26 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-81384e03-00001639calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 26, 2025 2:00 PM - 5:00 PM in the EMPAC Studio Beta - All are invited! The International Symposium on Assistive Technology for Music and Art started as a forum for researchers and artists dealing with the physical limitations of the human body and with embodiment in general. In spring 2025, the symposium expands its scope to workshop immersive technologies and holistic exercises for reducing stress and improving well-being in learning environments. Join us in March for a panel focused on breathing techniques and a demo of new AI developments.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-81384e03-00001639calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Celebrating the Life of Chuck Boylen | March 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-8c1807a3-000047c5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, March 29, 2025 11:00 AM - 2:30 PM - Dr. Charles “Chuck” Boylen died February 13 after a battle with pancreatic cancer. As Professor of Biology and Associate Director of RPI’s Darrin Fresh Water Institute (DFWI), he worked with all aspects of running the research field station. He was internationally known for his New York State limnology research, and was academic advisor to the Theta Xi fraternity. A celebration of life will be held on what would have been his 83rd birthday. All who knew him are welcome.Where: Chapel+Cultural Center, 2125 Burdett Avenue, Troy, NY 12180 New…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-8c1807a3-000047c5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Allyship in Action: Panel Event | March 26 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/allyship-action-panel-event-open-entire-campus-community</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Allyship in Action: Wed. Mar. 26th from 2:00 – 3:00 pm (via Webex) Join us for a discussion featuring a panel of lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender, and queer (LGBTQ+) individuals from the RPI campus community. We will explore the meaning of allyship, its importance, and how you can take action to help create supportive and safer environments for LGBTQ+ individuals. Registration Required: https://forms.gle/2ooDFZ4vHDRcXc4AA&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/allyship-action-panel-event-open-entire-campus-community</guid></item><item><title>Open Data Hackathon - Build with AI | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-a5c8071c-00003dc7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 26, 2025 10:30 AM - 4:00 PM - Open Data &amp;amp; AI Hackathon is a community-run, one-day in-person Get Together event focused on intensive problem solving in collaborative setting. We aim to bring technologists, developers, students, tech companies, and guest speakers together in one location to learn, and experiment with open source, open data and modern AI technology. This is an event hosted by GDG Hudson Valley, GDG Capital Region and GDG on Campus Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI) and Google Women Techmakers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-a5c8071c-00003dc7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Do you know RPI’s Student Handbook?</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/do-you-know-rpis-student-handbook</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that for RPI students, the Student Handbook and Graduate Student Supplement outline academic and disciplinary policies? For faculty and staff, these are detailed in the Human Resources Policy Guidelines and the Faculty Handbook. For more information, explore Standard 2 of RPI’s Self-Study for Middle States Accreditation: Ethics and Integrity, a team led by Dr. Dorit Nevo.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/do-you-know-rpis-student-handbook</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents! Dr. Theresa Jean Tanenbaum: Transformative Play Lab | March 26 (Virtual Event)</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-dr-theresa-jean-tanenbaum-transformative-play-lab-virtual-event</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this talk, Dr. Theresa Jean Tanenbaum theorizes an emancipatory design practice intended to restore agency and power to those of us who have suffered at the hands of the oppressive normative social order (which is to say, most of us). She illustrates this with a vulnerable autoethnographic discussion of her own experiences of gender transition, and with examples from larp, tabletop roleplaying games, and popular media. Join virtually on 3/26 at 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-dr-theresa-jean-tanenbaum-transformative-play-lab-virtual-event</guid></item><item><title>C&amp;M Colloquium with Kevin Coe to be held on March 26</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cm-colloquium-kevin-coe-media-and-democracy-tumultuous-times</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join the Communication and Media Department on Wednesday, March 26th from 2:30 - 4:30 pm for a seminar titled “Media and Democracy in Tumultuous Times” by Dr. Kevin Coe, Professor in the Department of Communication at the University of Utah.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cm-colloquium-kevin-coe-media-and-democracy-tumultuous-times</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO - Information on Email sending limit exceeded – bulk emailing</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-information-email-sending-limit-exceeded-bulk-emailing</link><description>&lt;p&gt;For security reasons, a limitation of sending no more than 1000 emails/recipients per day and no more than 500 emails/recipients within an hour is in place for all students faculty and staff. This limit exists to stop bulk malicious email from accounts taken over by malware or scammers. Additionally, something to be aware of is that Microsoft has its own sending limit of 30 emails per minute. Please click in for more detail.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-information-email-sending-limit-exceeded-bulk-emailing</guid></item><item><title>Leaders in Action Conversation with Major General Kimberly M. Colloton’92 PMP, Deputy Chief of Engineers &amp; Deputy Commanding General U.S. Army Corps of Engineers scheduled for March 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-1fb1d01f-000037a0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, March 27, 2025 12:00 PM - 2:00 PM at the Heffner Alumni House Great HallDuring this session, host Prof. Azita Hirsa and Major General Kimberly M. Colloton’92 PMP, Deputy Chief of Engineers &amp;amp; Deputy Commanding General U.S. Army Corps of Engineers will discuss Engineering Ethics in the 21st Century. Participants will be able to ask relevant questions; refreshments will be served following the session.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-1fb1d01f-000037a0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Helping Students Learn: Session 2-Making It Stick</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/helping-students-learn-session-2-making-it-stick</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Faculty are invited to participate in the second workshop of the 3-part series, Helping Students Learn. The topic of the second session is Making it Stick: Enhancing Practice and Transfer of New Knowledge and will be led by Eric Burkholder (Auburn University, Engineering Education Researcher). Participants will be able to apply research from cognitive psychology directly to their instructional approach in a way that centers and promotes student learning and success. This series focuses on research-based teaching theories and methods funded by the NSF as part of the MANE RED grant. Session 2:…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:31:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/helping-students-learn-session-2-making-it-stick</guid></item></channel></rss>
