<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>An Evening with President Schmidt: Summer Arch! | June 10</title><link>https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/evening-president-schmidt-arch-summer</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Arch and the CCPD would like to formally invite you to An Evening with President Schmidt: Summer Arch! This event will be held on Tuesday, June 10 from 5:00-7:00 P.M. at President Schmidt’s Residence. Please RSVP on Handshake by May 27th to join us!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/evening-president-schmidt-arch-summer</guid></item><item><title>Summer Parking Permits Now Available for Purchase</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/summer-parking-permits-now-available-purchase</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Students enrolled in summer classes and Arch: Summer parking permits are now on sale! Please be sure to purchased your summer parking permit to avoid any parking violations. Permits are required on all Rensselaer property. To register please visit: https://rpi.aimsparking.com If you have any questions, please contact Parking and Transportation at 518-276-6616 or parking@rpi.edu. Drive safely and have a great summer semester!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/summer-parking-permits-now-available-purchase</guid></item><item><title>Summer Arch Shuttle Service</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/summer-arch-shuttle-announcement</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Parking and Transportation is pleased to announce to the Rensselaer community that the Summer Arch shuttle service will begin on Monday, May 19th. Shuttle operating hours are posted on the Parking and Transportation website. Any questions please call Parking and Transportation at 518-276-6616.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/summer-arch-shuttle-announcement</guid></item><item><title>Coffee &amp; Conversations | May 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0196-ee1aa84b-00003a0ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 22, 2025 11:00 AM - 1:00 PM - Students are invited to stop by for a cup of coffee, a little treat and an opportunity to socially connect with peers!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0196-ee1aa84b-00003a0ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Virtual Summer Series: Consigli Construction | May 27</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-virtual-summer-series-consigli-construction-may-27</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the CCPD’s Virtual Summer Series, join Consigli Construction virtually on Tuesday, May 27th to learn more about their available internship and co-op opportunities and connect with recruiters. Register in Handshake for more info!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-virtual-summer-series-consigli-construction-may-27</guid></item><item><title>Game Development Camp to be Held July 14-18</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/game-development-camp</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Game Development Camp is a summer camp for Middle Schoolers and High Schoolers looking to jump start their game development careers at RPI. This 1 week long camp teaches students the basics of Game Design, Art, Animation, Audio, and Programming while taking a more serious look at video games and how they are made. Registration below. Join us July 14-18 in SAGE 2411. https://hass.rpi.edu/rpi-game-development-camp&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/game-development-camp</guid></item><item><title>Get setup for with passwordless single sign on</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/get-setup-passwordless-single-sign</link><description>&lt;p&gt;You can use your device or laptop biometrics to login to RPI’s single sign on. Our SSO works with TouchID/FaceID, Andriod Biometrics, and Windows Hello.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/get-setup-passwordless-single-sign</guid></item><item><title>Early registration is open for Qiskit Global Summer School 2025</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/early-registration-open-qiskit-global-summer-school-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Early registration is open for Qiskit Global Summer School 2025. Qiskit Global Summer School is an opportunity to learn quantum programming from researchers and programmers at IBM through live lectures, Q&amp;amp;A with experts, and programming challenges. Previous years’ lessons are available on the Qiskit YouTube Channel. This year’s theme is Qiskit Global Summer School 2025: The Past, Present, and Future of Quantum Computing. The class runs remotely July 7-22, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/early-registration-open-qiskit-global-summer-school-2025</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience several “Supervisory Simulations” with colleagues. In addition, the importance of coaching employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team capacity will be explored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-0</guid></item></channel></rss>
