<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CCPD Announces Western Digital HDD Teardown Workshop</title><link>https://app.joinhandshake.com/events/1583247/share_preview</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled from 4:00PM to 5:00PM on September 24 in the Rensselaer Union’s Shelnutt Gallery, this hands-on workshop related to data storage gives students the opportunity to learn about the cloud, including the various types of storage devices and the considerations that are most important for the cloud. Participants will also disassemble an actual hard-drive and discuss the engineering behind it. Space is limited to 25, so &lt;a href="https://app.joinhandshake.com/login"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.joinhandshake.com/events/1583247/share_preview</guid></item><item><title>“Just In Time” Career Fair Prep with Western Digital to be Held September 25</title><link>https://app.joinhandshake.com/events/1567274/share_preview</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s the week of the Career Fair, so if you need some last-minute prep, this is the workshop for you! Just attend this session in the CCPD conference room from 3:00PM to 4:00PM on Wednesday, September 25 to learn how to prepare your resume, deliver an elevator pitch, talk with employers, use the platform, and more!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.joinhandshake.com/events/1567274/share_preview</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of Rensselaer’s Fifth Service Day on October 5!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-bb9cd8de-00007da7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, October 5, 2024 9:00 AM - 2:00 PM - RPI Service Day is an event open to all students to give them a chance to spend a few hours helping the community at various local organizations! Alpha Phi Omega, Rensselaer’s co-ed service fraternity, is working closely with the Bicentennial committee to elevate this event and allow all interested students to learn about and help the local community. Free transportation and lunch will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-bb9cd8de-00007da7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>First Game Jam of the Year Starting September 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/september-game-jam-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Game Dev Club is hosting its first Game Jam of the year starting on Friday, September 20 at 5pm in Sage 2411! Kick off the fall and join us once again (or for the first time!) for a 48-hour jam, with overnight breaks beginning at 10:00 PM both Friday and Saturday nights and doors opening again at 8:00 AM each morning. Teams will be formed to design your own game from scratch. Students of all years, areas of study, and experience levels are welcome to participate!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/september-game-jam-0</guid></item><item><title>Planning to Graduate This December?</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/office-registrar/09/17/2024/planning-graduate-decmber-2024%C2%A0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you plan to graduate in December 2024 and haven’t completed your degree application yet, the &lt;a href="https://sis.rpi.edu/"&gt;Student Information System&lt;/a&gt; (SIS) is now open to apply! The application deadline is Friday, October 11. Please make sure you refer to the &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/registrar/graduation-commencement"&gt;Registrar’s Graduation &amp;amp; Commencement webpage&lt;/a&gt; for complete details!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/office-registrar/09/17/2024/planning-graduate-decmber-2024%C2%A0</guid></item><item><title>OGE to Hold Co-Terminal Program Information Session</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-0ac468ae-000044cacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 23, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - The Office of Graduate Education invites students interested in learning about the application process and the great opportunities the Co-Terminal Program provides to attend this session! Please &lt;a href="mailto:atkins3@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Steven Atkinson&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-0ac468ae-000044cacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC Fall Building Tours to Begin September 28</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/fall-building-tours</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Each of EMPAC’s tours takes visitors behind the scenes to experience the center’s infrastructure as few do, so plan to join Associate Director Jonas Braasch for a free public tour of the building at 1:00PM on Saturday, September 28. Each tour is hosted by an EMPAC staff member with a different area of expertise, so there’s always something new to learn and discover! Tours begin in the main lobby and run approximately 90 minutes; please arrive 15 minutes before tour time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/fall-building-tours</guid></item><item><title>Session to Review Certificates in Analytics, Machine Learning and AI</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8ff160d0-00005c2bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 27, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for a session highlighting Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning and AI. Attendees can expect to learn how data can inform better decisions, and will review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/analytics27"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8ff160d0-00005c2bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of the Annual “Run to Remember” 5K!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-0ea510f6-00004e07calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, September 28, 2024 7:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Brought to the Troy community by RPI AFROTC Detachment 550, this family-friendly, community-wide event is aimed at supporting local veterans as well as current college students. With RPI celebrating its 200th year, we hope the Bicentennial will bring the community together to enjoy this outstanding event. 60% of the event profits made will be donated to the Special Operations Warrior Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-0ea510f6-00004e07calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>LGBTQ+ Task Force Meeting Slated for September 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-ecb57350-00007d28calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 24, 2024 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - The LGBTQ+ Task Force is a group of faculty, staff, and students working to improve the climate for the LGBTQ+ community at RPI. If you’re interested in joining the Task Force, please come to the group’s first meeting of the year! If you can’t attend the meeting but would still like to participate, please &lt;a href="mailto:mailto;lgbtqtaskforce@rpi.edu"&gt;contact the Task Force&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-ecb57350-00007d28calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>NSF Leader Explores RPI Research and Workforce Development Initiatives During Visit</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/09/17/nsf-leader-explores-rpi-research-and-workforce-development-initiatives-during-visit</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer recently welcomed Susan Margulies, Ph.D., leader of the U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) Directorate for Engineering to learn about RPI research and education capabilities, participate in a panel discussion, and give a presentation on NSF programs and opportunities to RPI community members and representatives from the University at Albany, Siena College, and Union College.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/09/17/nsf-leader-explores-rpi-research-and-workforce-development-initiatives-during-visit</guid></item><item><title>Math Colloquium Slated for September 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-069724c7-00001e98calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 25, 2024 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM - This Mathematical Sciences Colloquium will feature a presentation titled “Direct interpolative construction of quantized tensor trains” by speaker Michael Lindsey from UC Berkeley.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-069724c7-00001e98calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Perspectives from Palestine” Event to be Held September 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-0b6ee765-0000005acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 24, 2024 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM - Hosted by Rensselaer Voices for Palestine, this event features Keren Carmeli, an Israeli-American and member of the Albany chapter of Jewish Voices for Peace, and Faris Amer, a Palestinian-American pharmaceutical professional at Regeneron and active member in the Capital Region’s Muslim community. Come for a chance to hear first-person perspectives from individuals who grew up in the region, as well as for a Q&amp;amp;A session.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-0b6ee765-0000005acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity Holding In-Person Confidential Retirement Consultation Sessions October 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f8c5401-00005a34calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 3, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f8c5401-00005a34calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
