<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Administration Division: Roof Replacements Scheduled for Summer Months</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/administration/06/06/2024/roof-replacements-materials-research-center-mrc-empire-state-hall-esh-and</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All members of the campus community should note that roof replacements are scheduled for the Materials Research Center (MRC), Empire State Hall (ESH), and the west wing of the Jonsson Rowland Science Center (JRSC). Construction will begin on Monday, June 17 and be completed by Friday, August 9, with tentative daily work hours set for 6:00AM to 2:30PM, Monday through Friday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/administration/06/06/2024/roof-replacements-materials-research-center-mrc-empire-state-hall-esh-and</guid></item><item><title>Joint ECSE/CBIS Seminar on Life Science Automation Scheduled for July 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0190-e5500128-00001be3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, July 29, 2024 10:30 AM - 11:30 AM - Professors Kerstin Thurow and Heidi Fleischer — from the Center for Life Science Automation (Celisca) at the University of Rostock, Germany — will jointly present a seminar focusing on life science automation research in Celisca.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0190-e5500128-00001be3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Don’t Miss Easton’s 11th Birthday “Pawty”!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-836ecb65-00000cbecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, July 25, 2024 11:30 AM - 1:30 PM - The campus community is invited to help Presidential Pup Eaton Schmidt celebrate his 11th birthday! Just come to the Freshman Quad near Barton Hall, where Easton and his younger sister Jofa will be eagerly waiting to greet everyone. There will also be frozen novelty treats served, so be sure to stop by on your way to or from lunch to enjoy the “pawty”!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-836ecb65-00000cbecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Leading and Managing Graduate Certificates Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4ab6fdca-00005e82calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 31, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/LCCTMTCT31"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., as he highlights Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Leading Change and Innovation, and Managing Technical Organizations. Attendees will learn how individuals can manage and lead effective cross-functional teams, and implement changes designed to optimize the realization of tactics and strategies….&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4ab6fdca-00005e82calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Swimming &amp; Diving Teams Recognized for Academic Excellence</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/7/19/rpi-swimming-recognized-for-academic-excellence-by-cscaa.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer women’s and men’s swimming teams have been selected as College Swimming and Diving Coaches Association of America (CSCAA) Scholar All-America teams for the spring 2024 term; to earn the accolade, teams were required to post a cumulative team GPA of 3.0 or higher for the semester. Additionally, Mike Dowd of the RPI men’s squad was individually named a CSCAA Division III Scholar All-American.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/7/19/rpi-swimming-recognized-for-academic-excellence-by-cscaa.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Update Regarding CCPD MathWorks Info Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2631</link><description>&lt;p&gt;CCPD’s info session with Mathworks, which was originally scheduled for July 18, will now take place from 6:30PM to 7:30PM on Tuesday, July 30. Students are welcome to join the MathWorks team to learn about the company’s career paths and culture, as well as upcoming opportunities for Arch students seeking an Away experience. Also review the &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/edu/jobs/8911739"&gt;Engineering Development Group Spring Co-Op&lt;/a&gt; opportunity posted in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2631</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Virtual Summer Series to Conclude with Velan Studios Info Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2633</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 6:30PM to 7:30PM on Thursday, August 1, the team at Velan Studios will discuss the organization’s career paths and company culture, as well as upcoming opportunities for Arch students seeking an Away experience. Students can also review the &lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/edu/jobs/8888845"&gt;Spring 2025 Programmer Internship opportunity&lt;/a&gt; posted in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2633</guid></item><item><title>Training, Resources to Assist Faculty with Adding Questions to End-of-Term Evaluations</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/07/10/2024/faculty-training-heliocampus-adding-additional-questions-summer-i</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Summer I and III end-of-term course evaluations will be open to students August 1-17, with reports available to instructors on September 13; instructors have until July 31 to add questions to their courses using HelioCampus. The Office of Undergraduate Education will offer training; self-help information is available on the &lt;a href="https://provost.rpi.edu/faculty-resources/heliocampus-formerly-aefis-assessment-tool/heliocampus-formerly-aefis-support"&gt;HelioCampus Resource Site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/07/10/2024/faculty-training-heliocampus-adding-additional-questions-summer-i</guid></item><item><title>Update: Time Changed for CCPD July 29 URP/Handshake Faculty Training Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/urphandshake-faculty-training-session-july-29</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday, July 29 from 2:00PM to 3:30PM in the CCPD conference room, the CCPD will host an interactive opportunity for faculty members to learn how to use Handshake for posting undergraduate research positions. Light snacks will be provided. Space is limited, so interested faculty should &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/form/urp-handshake-training-7-29"&gt;submit a registration webform&lt;/a&gt; to sign up as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/urphandshake-faculty-training-session-july-29</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity to Hold Confidential Retirement Consultation Sessions by Phone, Zoom Video Option</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f940a59-0000605ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, August 6, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f940a59-0000605ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
