<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:31:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Now Accepting Spring Applications for RPI’s Collegiate Science &amp; Technology Entry Program!</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/now-accepting-spring-applications-rpis-collegiate-science-technology-entry-program</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Collegiate Science &amp;amp; Technology Entry Program (CSTEP) is excited to announce that applications for the Spring semester are now open! CSTEP is an academic enrichment program designed to support New York State residents who are economically disadvantaged and pursuing careers in STEM or health-related fields. Apply today by visiting the CSTEP website&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/now-accepting-spring-applications-rpis-collegiate-science-technology-entry-program</guid></item><item><title>The Design Lab Showcase welcomes Justin Weinstein from GlobalFoundries!</title><link>https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-showcase-welcomes-guest-speaker-globalfoundries</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come and hear Justin Weinstein, an alumnus from the Class of 2019, speak about his experiences and the exciting work he is doing at GlobalFoundries. Don’t miss out on this chance to be inspired! We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-showcase-welcomes-guest-speaker-globalfoundries</guid></item><item><title>Design Lab Showcase to be held Wednesday, December 10 from 2:00 - 5:00 P.M.</title><link>https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-will-host-their-design-showcase-wednesday-december-10th-2025-dcc-great</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Design Showcase will be held on Wednesday, December 10th, 2025 from 2:00 to 5:00 p.m. in the DCC Great Hall. Students from multiple engineering disciplines (Computer &amp;amp; Systems, Electrical, Industrial &amp;amp; Management, Materials and Mechanical Engineering) solve real-world design challenges for industry, entrepreneurs and academic/medical partners. Visit the showcase to: Interact with project teams and view their achievements. Learn how students solve complex design challenges. Get inspired by…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-will-host-their-design-showcase-wednesday-december-10th-2025-dcc-great</guid></item><item><title>RPI’s Inaugural Festival of Lessons and Carols on Dec 11</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpis-inaugural-festival-lessons-and-carols</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI Concert Choir, with RPI’s Office of Religious and Spiritual Life, will present its inaugural Festival of Lessons and Carols. Following the format of the University of Cambridge’s famous festival, RPI’s program will interweave readings and music that celebrate charity and benevolence. The program will feature the RPI Concert Choir performing music of Durufle, Chesnokov, Rachmaninoff, Brahms and U2 alongside readings by several distinguished surprise guest readers! Admission is free.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpis-inaugural-festival-lessons-and-carols</guid></item><item><title>RPI at Work Hosts MBA for Professionals Review | Dec. 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-b6c95d9a-000006decalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, December 11, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join RPI Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-b6c95d9a-000006decalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff Appreciation Lunch on December 10th</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-appreciation-lunch-december-10th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us for a special appreciation lunch as we celebrate the hard work, dedication, and contributions of our incredible faculty and staff. Come enjoy a delicious meal, connect with colleagues, and take a well-deserved break! Price: $6 plus tax&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-appreciation-lunch-december-10th</guid></item><item><title>Volunteers Needed: Late Night Breakfast at Commons!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/volunteers-needed-late-night-breakfast-commons</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Help our students get fueled up for finals by helping with Late Night Breakfast on December 11th at Commons Dining Hall. We are looking for enthusiastic faculty and staff volunteers to help make the event a success! If you’re interested in volunteering, please sign up by emailing auxiliaryservices@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/volunteers-needed-late-night-breakfast-commons</guid></item></channel></rss>
