<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>NSF Graduate Research Fellowship Information Session Scheduled</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-56f8bf25-00000368calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 13, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - The National Science Foundation Graduate Research Fellowship provides three years of salary and tuition while students earn a graduate degree. First- and second-year grad students and seniors who are U.S. citizens and permanent residents in 35 STEM fields are encouraged to &lt;a href="https://rpi.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_5q1McRZJMkpb0G2"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; for this session, or to just stop by.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-56f8bf25-00000368calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Location Update for September 4 Study Abroad Info Session</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/08/26/2024/fall-2024-study-abroad-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All undergraduates are welcome to join the Office of International Programs from noon to 1:00PM on Wednesday, September 4 in room 3602 (not 2602, as originally posted) of the Rensselaer Union for a Study Abroad info session and pizza lunch to learn about program opportunities, application procedures, and deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/08/26/2024/fall-2024-study-abroad-info-session</guid></item><item><title>APO Offering Free Public “Bob Ross” Painting Session!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-91cea228-0000446bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 6, 2024 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM - Join APO members in painting happy little trees just like American painter and art instructor Bob Ross used to in his iconic TV series!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-91cea228-0000446bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Library to Hold Open House for New Undergraduate Students</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/librarys-annual-open-house-new-undergraduate-students</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All undergraduate students are welcome to stop by the Folsom Library between 2:00PM and 3:30PM on Wednesday, September 4 to learn about Library services and see demos of available resources, and also meet other new students! Attendees can also enter to win raffle prizes from local businesses, grab a free “library swag” bag, and enjoy some free ice cream, too!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/librarys-annual-open-house-new-undergraduate-students</guid></item><item><title>CCPD, ISSS to Hold “Working in the U.S.: CPT and Internships” Webinar for Undergraduate Students</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-956db078-00002abfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 11, 2024 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Join the Center for Career and Professional Development (CCPD) and International Services for Students and Scholars (ISSS) for a virtual workshop to learn about the internship search and the ways to get Curricular Practical Training (CPT) to work in the U.S. before graduation! This session has information that is specific to undergraduate students.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-956db078-00002abfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Fellowship info Session to Highlight Competitions for Grad School Salary and Tuition</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-57031d17-0000043ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 10, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Competitive fellowships provide salary and tuition for Masters and PhD students. All graduate students, juniors, seniors, and international students are welcome to attend this session to learn how to find and apply to appropriate programs that will fund fall 2025 and beyond. &lt;a href="https://rpi.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_5q1McRZJMkpb0G2"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to attend or just drop in!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-57031d17-0000043ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Posts Security Warning Regarding Duo/MFA Passcodes</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/security-warning-regarding-duomfa-passcodes</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Division of the Chief Information Officer is encouraging everyone to please be aware of sophisticated phishing attempts targeting our community, and to not provide their Duo codes in response to any text messages, phone calls, emails, or other communications they may receive. These requests are fraudulent and designed to steal your information and compromise your RCS account.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/security-warning-regarding-duomfa-passcodes</guid></item><item><title>Webex LTI Legacy Upgraded to Webex LTI 1.3 in Blackboard</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</link><description>&lt;p&gt;MultiMedia Services wishes to inform the campus community that Webex LTI Legacy (formerly Webex Education Connector) has been upgraded in Blackboard to the new Webex LTI 1.3 connector. This is the final upgrade prior to the start of the semester, and brings in increased stability and features for utilizing Webex within a course in Blackboard. Please refer to the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/sections/360008224951"&gt;ITSSC Knowledge Base&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</guid></item><item><title>Mathematical Sciences Colloquium Slated for September 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-9971e599-000059aecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 5, 2024 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - This Mathematical Sciences colloquium will feature a presentation titled “Static currents in type-I superconductors” by speaker Manas Rachh, from Flatiron Institute’s Center for Computational Mathematics.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-9971e599-000059aecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“R as your SuperpoweR!”: RPIrates Monthly Meeting to be Held September 4</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/r-your-superpower-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-4-sep-6p-ae217</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI R users community is invited to AE 217 for the first RPIrates meeting of the Fall 2024 term! The event’s topic will be “R as your SuperpoweR!” and will be led by Dr. John Erickson, Dir. of Research Operations of the Rensselaer FOCI. John has co-taught R-based data analytics courses for nearly a decade, has presented numerous R bootcamps and tutorials, and is the founder of RPIrates, the RPI R Users Group.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/r-your-superpower-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-4-sep-6p-ae217</guid></item><item><title>Gonzalez, Ridenour Win Doubles Title at Mary Haskins Invite</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/1/flora-gonzalez-and-ridenour-win-doubles-title-at-mary-haskins-invite.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Lorna Flores Gonzalez and Nicole Ridenour of the Rensselaer women’s tennis team outlasted the field to earn the double’s victory in this weekend’s Mary Haskins Invite at William Smith College.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/1/flora-gonzalez-and-ridenour-win-doubles-title-at-mary-haskins-invite.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Quantum Computing Users Group Monthly Meeting</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-monthly-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join students and colleagues interested in quantum computing or those currently working on the subject on Wednesday, September 18, at noon in Amos Eaton 217. If you are interested in participating, contact Tom Morgan at morgat5@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-monthly-meeting</guid></item><item><title>“in a plenum space” Film Program to Feature Works by Mazú González, Nguyen-Chi</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-331f73dc-00002ed2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 5, 2024 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM - Join EMPAC curator Katherine C.M. Adams for a program featuring two short works by Thuy-Han Nguyen-Chi and a feature-length experimental documentary by Tatiana Mazú González. Each work reflects off-screen realities and experiments with ways sound can take prominence when film is used to search for something the viewer never sees.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-331f73dc-00002ed2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>OUE Announces Syllabus Guidance for Language with Generative AI Tools</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/21/2024/syllabus-guidance-language-generative-ai-tools</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer instructors are welcome to use the Office of Undergraduate Education’s &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory/#SyllabusGuidanceforLanguagewithGenerativeAITools"&gt;syllabus guidance statements&lt;/a&gt; — which focus on generative AI tools in the classroom and were curated from discussions and openly available Web resources — to decide if AI tools fit within their pedagogical goals.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/21/2024/syllabus-guidance-language-generative-ai-tools</guid></item><item><title>Office of Strategic Alliances and Translation to Hold “Meet, Greet &amp; Eat!”</title><link>https://osat.rpi.edu/announcements/osat-informational-meet-greet-eat</link><description>&lt;p&gt;At 4:00PM on Wednesday, September 4 in the CBIS auditorium, please join the Office of Strategic Alliances and Translation for an OSAT Informational, where they will be unveiling new resources and support for faculty and staff with intellectual property, new ventures, and industry collaborations. President Schmidt will be making opening remarks; a reception will follow the event. Please &lt;a href="mailto:jonesa18@rpi.edu"&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; to Ashley Jones.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://osat.rpi.edu/announcements/osat-informational-meet-greet-eat</guid></item><item><title>Collegiate Store Offering Birthday Specials for Faculty, Staff</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/collegiate-store/03/07/2024/birthday-special-collegiate-store</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Collegiate Store is happy to announce that it will be celebrating RPI faculty and staff birthdays with an invitation to shop for one clothing or gift item at 20% off. Beginning in March 2024, faculty and staff can just come in during their birthday month to get their coupon, which can then be used in-store or online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/collegiate-store/03/07/2024/birthday-special-collegiate-store</guid></item></channel></rss>
