<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:31:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>ValleyCats Baseball Game Trip | July 31 (Sign Up Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-cc849145-00003ebecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, July 31, 2025 6:00 PM - 10:00 PM - On July 31st we will be attending a ValleyCats Baseball Game at the Joseph Bruno Stadium in Troy! The ticket as well as a food voucher will be provided for those who attend. Priority will be given to students on their arch summer semester of classes, but anyone interested should sign up!Sign ups will close on Monday, July 28th. Register to attend using the event URL by 7/28 - all students are welcome!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:31:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-cc849145-00003ebecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Paul Mason Jr. Retiring After 37 Years of Service</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/paul-mason-jr-retiring-after-37-years-service</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us in celebrating the retirement of Paul Mason Jr., who will retire on Thursday, July 31, following an outstanding 37-year tenure at RPI. A proud second-generation RPI team member, his father also served the institute for over a decade. Paul joined us in 1987 and rose to the role of Access Control Technician. Access control systems are a cornerstone of campus safety, managing electronic entry to labs, dorms, offices, and other sensitive areas. Over nearly four decades, Paul contributed not…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:31:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/paul-mason-jr-retiring-after-37-years-service</guid></item><item><title>Cleanout Day for West Hall, July 24th</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/cleanout-day-west-hall-july-24th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please be advised that the Environmental Health &amp;amp; Safety Department (EH&amp;amp;S) is planning a Cleanout Day for West Hall this Thursday, July 24th. During this time, the adjacent parking lot ( small lot near first floor entrance) will be used to stage waste containers and support the event. As a result, there will be no available parking spots in that lot on Thursday. Please note that the fire lane and emergency access will remain clear at all time-only standard parking spaces will be impacted.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:31:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/cleanout-day-west-hall-july-24th</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar- RPI MAX: Setting Goals and Reviewing Results | Aug. 1</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-rpi-max-setting-goals-and-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This seminar will establish the positive effect of transforming the traditional role of planner and evaluator solely from the people-leader to a shared responsibility between leader and direct report. Leaders will experience how to develop and use effective SMART goals to help them, and their employees track progress and accurately evaluate outcomes. In addition, the fundamentals of an impactful performance discussion and the three phased approach of RPI MAX will be explored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:31:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-rpi-max-setting-goals-and-0</guid></item></channel></rss>
