<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:32:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>TOPOS 2025: King Britt presents Liberation Meditations: A Call at EMPAC | Aug. 28</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-7bfaf33f-000061b8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, August 28, 2025 9:00 PM - 39 speakers. 1 immersive ritual. Visionary producer and sonic explorer King Britt returns with a powerful spatial sound experience unfolding within EMPAC’s state-of-the-art Studio 1—Goodman. Featuring collaborators Suzi Analogue and Myles Ortiz-Green, their performances weave turntables, analog synths, and digital textures into a ritual of rhythm and healing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:32:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-7bfaf33f-000061b8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Browser Support Change - Effective July 2025</title><link>https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-browser-support-change-effective-july-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;HelioCampus, our tool for syllabus, assessment and course evaluations is streamlining their browser support to focus on the following most widely used browsers: Google Chrome, Microsoft Edge, and Apple Safari.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:32:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-browser-support-change-effective-july-2025</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources: Getting the Most from Percipio (Getting Started with Percipio: Navigation Q&amp;A)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-42bec315-00007b41calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 5, 2025 9:00 AM - 9:30 AM - This brief course is designed to help you get comfortable using Percipio, RPI’s digital learning platform. You’ll learn how to navigate the main dashboard, search for content, access assigned learning, and track your progress. We’ll also walk through common questions users have and show you where to find help when needed. Whether you’re brand new or just need a refresher, this session will ensure you’re ready to make the most of Percipio.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:32:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-42bec315-00007b41calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Nanomanufacturing Breakthrough Could Revolutionize Night Vision Technology, Other Fields</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2025/08/18/nanomanufacturing-breakthrough-could-revolutionize-night-vision-technology-other-fields</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI scientists played a pivotal role in the development of a new manufacturing technique that could revolutionize infrared detection technology, potentially making thermal imaging devices cheaper, smaller, more accurate and far more affordable.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:32:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2025/08/18/nanomanufacturing-breakthrough-could-revolutionize-night-vision-technology-other-fields</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Fall Syllabus Available - Complete by September 11, 2025</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-fall-syllabus-available-complete-september-11-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The HelioCampus syllabus module is available for faculty to access for the fall beginning on August 7, 2025. Based on the requirements from the Provost’s office, faculty should have their syllabi published in HelioCampus by September 11, 2025. For a Refresher Handout and information on Training please see the expanded announcement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:32:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-fall-syllabus-available-complete-september-11-2025</guid></item></channel></rss>
