<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:31:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Fall 2024 Academic and Refund Policy Changes Announced</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/office-registrar/06/26/2024/policy-changes</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past year, Provost Rebecca Doerge carefully reviewed the Institute’s academic policies and procedures alongside student leaders and academic and administrative groups. Based on their findings, she is excited to announce drop period, refund, and undergraduate course repeat policy changes that will become effective for the Fall 2024 semester.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:31:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/office-registrar/06/26/2024/policy-changes</guid></item><item><title>RAF Announces Mary Ellen Mainello’s Retirement</title><link>https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/mary-ellen-mainello-retirement</link><description>&lt;p&gt;After more than 25 years of service at Rensselaer, Mary Ellen Mainello will be retiring on June 30. On behalf of the Institute, the Division of Research Administration and Finance would like to take this opportunity to thank Mary Ellen for everything that she has done for RPI, and in particular for the Research Finance division. Please join RAF in congratulating Mary Ellen and wishing her well in her future endeavors!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:31:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/mary-ellen-mainello-retirement</guid></item><item><title>Professor Radke Recognized by IEEE for Innovative Pedagogy</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/06/18/rpi-professor-rich-radke-recognized-ieee-innovative-pedagogy</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rich Radke, a professor in Rensselaer’s Department of Electrical, Computer, and Systems Engineering, has won the IEEE Signal Processing Society Regional Distinguished Teacher Award for his career contributions to signal processing education and, most recently, his inventive approach to immersing students in the fast-moving field of generative artificial intelligence (AI).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:31:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/06/18/rpi-professor-rich-radke-recognized-ieee-innovative-pedagogy</guid></item><item><title>With New Grant, RPI Researcher Unravels Causes of ‘Neutron Noise’ in Nuclear Reactors</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/06/21/new-grant-rpi-researcher-unravels-causes-neutron-noise-nuclear-reactors</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Hunter Belanger ’18, ’19G, Ph.D., assistant professor in Rensselaer’s Department of Mechanical, Aerospace, and Nuclear Engineering, is one of four researchers nationwide to receive a Department of Energy Distinguished Early Career Award.T he five-year, $625,000 grant will fund Belanger’s research aimed at making nuclear power safer and more efficient, supporting state and national efforts to transition away from carbon-emitting energy sources.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:31:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/06/21/new-grant-rpi-researcher-unravels-causes-neutron-noise-nuclear-reactors</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Session to Review Supply Chain, Lean Six Sigma, Systems Engineering</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4aa5dc65-00003f8dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, July 2, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/SCCT2"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D. as he highlights Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in areas surrounding Supply Chain and Logistics, Systems Engineering, and Lean Quality. Attendees will also learn how these certificates were created in consultation with enterprises that recognize the opportunity and risks of a global supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:31:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4aa5dc65-00003f8dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Study Abroad Applications Now Being Accepted for Spring 2025</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of International Programs’ &lt;a href="https://rpi-sa.terradotta.com/index.cfm?FuseAction=Abroad.Home"&gt;application portal&lt;/a&gt; is now open to undergraduate students who wish to apply for spring 2025 study abroad. Deadlines, contact info, and application guidelines are available via the &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025"&gt;International Programs website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:31:05 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/06/07/2024/study-abroad-applications-now-being-accepted-spring-2025</guid></item></channel></rss>
