<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:34:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Gateways Shuttle Service to be Available for Holiday/Winter Break</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/12/10/2024/gateways-shuttle-service-be-available-holidaywinter-break</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Department of Parking and Transportation is pleased to announce that it will once again be offering Gateways shuttle transportation to and from regional destination points - including the Amtrak train station, the Albany International Airport, and the Albany bus terminal - for the upcoming holiday/winter break. Be sure to submit your transportation request by Tuesday, December 17!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:34:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/12/10/2024/gateways-shuttle-service-be-available-holidaywinter-break</guid></item><item><title>Applications Now Being Accepted for Arch and Fall 2025 Resident Assistants</title><link>https://sll.rpi.edu/announcements/applications-now-being-accepted-arch-and-fall-2025-resident-assistants</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Student Living and Learning is looking for applicants to join their Arch 2025 and Fall 2025 staff, so apply between now and January 31, 2025 to join their team of leaders on campus and help create a community in your residence hall! Qualified applicants will be required to attend both a group and individual interview in October. To learn more, &lt;a href="https://sll.rpi.edu/RA"&gt;sign up&lt;/a&gt; to attend an information session.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:34:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sll.rpi.edu/announcements/applications-now-being-accepted-arch-and-fall-2025-resident-assistants</guid></item><item><title>Janelle Fayette, M.S., Receives Pillar of Rensselaer Award</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/12/12/janelle-fayette-ms-receives-pillar-rensselaer-award</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI President Marty Schmidt, Ph.D., has announced that Janelle Fayette, M.S., dean of the Office of the First-Year Experience, has been named a Pillar of Rensselaer.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:34:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/12/12/janelle-fayette-ms-receives-pillar-rensselaer-award</guid></item><item><title>Blackboard Maintenance Scheduled for December 26</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/blackboard-maintenance-scheduled-26-december-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Campus community members should note that Blackboard will be performing required maintenance beginning at 1:00am on Thursday, December 26, 2024. The maintenance is scheduled to last approximately six to eight hours, and the LMS will not be available during this time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:34:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/blackboard-maintenance-scheduled-26-december-2024</guid></item><item><title>Libraries Selected as ScienceDirect AI Search Pilot</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/science-direct-ai-search-pilot</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI Libraries have been selected for early access to a feature leveraging Generative AI on ScienceDirect, home of the largest collection of peer-reviewed books and research journal articles. The AI feature searches through the full text of thousands of papers at once, looking for the insights most relevant for your specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:34:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/science-direct-ai-search-pilot</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Spring 2025 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-spring-2025-course-requests-please-read</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Spring 2025 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:34:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-spring-2025-course-requests-please-read</guid></item><item><title>Open House-Farewell to Helen Grzymala, Welcome to Ann Marie Scheidegger to be Held December 16</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0193-88736160-000017aecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, December 16, 2024 1:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Attend this event to help wish Helen Grzymala a “final” farewell on her retirement, and also to welcome Ann Marie Scheidegger as she takes over the reigns from Helen as our new Assistant Vice President for Budget and Resource Planning! Refreshments will be served.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:34:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0193-88736160-000017aecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
