<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Handshake’s Just In Time Engineering Virtual Career Fair | May 9</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/handshakes-just-time-engineering-virtual-career-fair-may-9-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to explore exciting opportunities and connect with industry leaders? This VIRTUAL engineering-focused fair is the perfect opportunity to do so! Join Handshake, the CCPD, and other schools across the country on Friday, May 9, 2025 between 12-3pm to network with employers who are eager to recruit for internships, co-ops, and full-time positions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/handshakes-just-time-engineering-virtual-career-fair-may-9-2025</guid></item><item><title>Lavender Graduation | May 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-211684d5-00004a6fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, May 7, 2025 2:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Celebrating Rensselaer students of the LGBTQ+ community, Lavender Graduation is sure to be an inclusive and celebratory experience! We look forward to acknowledging your accomplishments and evolutions into college graduates of Rensselaer. Business casual recommended, but come as you feel comfortable. Graduating students who wish to be recognized must register at http://bit.ly/4klWQnL by Monday, May 5. There is no charge to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-211684d5-00004a6fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering Commencement Dinner and Celebration | May 9 (RSVP Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-71605693-00003247calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 9, 2025 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM - Join faculty and staff as we honor our graduates and their families at the Hilton Garden Inn in Troy.The sit-down dinner will be followed by the presentation of awards and prizes. A professional photographer will be on hand to take photos of the graduates with their families and friends. Reservations are due May 1, 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-71605693-00003247calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Arch Summer Kick-Off Event | May 19 at 12 PM</title><link>https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/arch-summer-kick-event-may-19-12-2-pm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting at 12PM, you are invited to kick off the Arch Summer featuring a fun BBQ, good company, inflatable obstacle course, and great music by DJ Kev! It’s a perfect opportunity to relax, connect with the community, and celebrate the start of the season together. Be sure to visit the Resource tent, where you can find student support offices and grab some free swag!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/arch-summer-kick-event-may-19-12-2-pm</guid></item><item><title>CASE Spring Open House | May 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-68f1baad-00000373calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 2, 2025 11:00 AM - 6:00 PM - Each year CASE celebrates the work of faculty and students at this daylong event which features presentations and exhibitions by students, startup ventures, and industry partners. The Open House brings together academic, research, industry and community members to discuss the important climate-related challenges facing the built world and advances of the current era. As part of this program CASE hosts a panel discussion with industry, government…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-68f1baad-00000373calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Temporary Closure of Portions of Sage Avenue</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/temporary-closure-portions-sage-avenue</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We would like to inform you that essential repairs to a low-pressure condensate line serving our steam and heating systems will require the temporary closure of portions of Sage Avenue. The affected area is located near the Sage Avenue entrance to the academic campus, between the Ricketts Building and the 87’ Gymnasium. This work is scheduled to occur from approximately mid-July through mid-August, with completion planned before the start of the fall semester.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/temporary-closure-portions-sage-avenue</guid></item><item><title>Removal of Unused Webex Recordings</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/removal-unused-webex-recordings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As the semester ends, Multimedia Services highly recommends deleting any Webex recordings that are no longer required for future viewing or archival. This will ensure that storage space is available for all users for future recordings. For assistance with Webex recording management, please submit a Help Desk request.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/removal-unused-webex-recordings</guid></item><item><title>Does Your Syllabus Need a Tune-Up? HelioCampus Syllabus Assistance Available</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-assistance-available-may-7</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you new to HelioCampus? Would you like to give your syllabus a “tune-up? Come to the Fischbach Room in the library on May 7 at 10:00 for assistance. Amy Svirsky, RPI’s Learning Assessment Specialist, will be there to assist you, answer your questions and show you how to use the tool.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-assistance-available-may-7</guid></item><item><title>Workshop Explores Funding Opportunities with the Simons Foundation | April 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-821580ef-00001d80calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 30, 2025 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - The Office of Foundation Philanthropy invites faculty to a workshop on securing funding from the Simons Foundation, one of RPI’s key philanthropic partners. Attendees will gain insight into the foundation’s priorities, explore available grant opportunities, and hear strategies from a successful RPI grant recipient. Faculty at all stages of the funding process are encouraged to attend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-821580ef-00001d80calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
