<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Engineering Ambassadors Recruitment Open as of October 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-4f3b0ebf-00003defcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, October 7, 2024 12:00 AM - Tue , November 12, 2024 12:00 AM - Attention, all freshmen and sophomores! Applications are now open for the Engineering Ambassadors, a group that works with local schools to promote STEM exploration and make engineering more accessible to a younger audience. A recruitment information session will be held from 6PM to 7PM on November 12 in JEC 3232 to allow interested students to learn more about the organization and meet current Ambassadors.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-4f3b0ebf-00003defcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ASCE Chapter Meeting Slated for October 8</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-53f1c974-00001758calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 8, 2024 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - If you’re curious about career prospects in Civil &amp;amp; Environmental Engineering, or want to learn more about the latest developments in the field, mark your calendars to attend this presentation by CDM Smith, who will provide insights and inspiration as they discuss some of their recent endeavors in the transportation, water, environmental, energy, and construction industry. Come connect with your fellow students and enjoy some pizza!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-53f1c974-00001758calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>GEM Fellowship Seeking Candidates for Fully-Funded Graduate Education, Industry Internships</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-574367db-0000169fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 9, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - GEM brings together top universities, industry, and national lab partners to support Masters and PhD students for up to five years. &lt;a href="https://rpi.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_5q1McRZJMkpb0G2"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to receive the link to attend this info session to learn about the benefits, explore participating partners, and prepare to apply for the November deadline. Please note that candidates must be U.S. citizens or permanent residents.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-574367db-0000169fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>NPZ Law Group to Hold Free Immigration Workshop</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-a4dd2693-00007a49calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 9, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:30 PM - Hosted by ISSS and presented by NPZ Group (Nachman Phulwani Zimovcak (NPZ) Law Group, P.C.), this virtual workshop will feature expert immigration lawyers discussing visa options that are available after graduation, including H-1B, O-1, and much more. Please &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/NPZworkshop-FA24"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-a4dd2693-00007a49calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>OGE Online Workshop to Offer Tips for Dissertation, Thesis Preparation and Submission</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-27f8ae71-00007357calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 9, 2024 6:00 PM - 7:30 PM - This workshop will discuss the basics of correct thesis organization and format, appropriate paper attribution and reference citation styles, and review the most common mistakes and ways to avoid them. All students who will be writing a thesis or dissertation are welcome to &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSer2BNWyOXoNC3ybGu-nRKOLHHH1N2T-sNPqEPEOSCLYFE_iA/viewform?usp=sf_link"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; and get their questions ready!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-27f8ae71-00007357calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Check Out the MSE Undergraduate Research Fair!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-2072adba-00004150calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 9, 2024 4:00 PM - 6:00 PM - Stop by to check out the latest student research at this year’s URP Fair, which is open to all undergraduates and especially those interested in Materials Science &amp;amp; Engineering or Applied Physics. Attendees will also have a chance to meet Material Advantage members and enter a raffle for a basket of RPI swag! Food and beverages will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-2072adba-00004150calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Writing a Literature Review” to be Topic of Graduate Brunch and Learn Session</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-97cee5bb-000019aacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 16, 2024 8:30 AM - 11:00 AM - Literature reviews come in many forms, such as a part of a research paper or one chapter of a doctoral dissertation. During this session, Professor Dorit Nevo shows how a literature review is a document — or section of one — that collects key sources on a topic, and discusses those sources in conversation with each other. Seating for this hybrid event is limited; brunch will be served from 8:30 AM to 9:00 AM.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-97cee5bb-000019aacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>85 New Employees Join RPI in July and August</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/85-new-employees-join-rpi-july-and-august</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Division of Human Resources is thrilled to announce that 85 new employees joined RPI in July and August. Let’s give a warm welcome to these new members of our campus community!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/85-new-employees-join-rpi-july-and-august</guid></item><item><title>RPI Students Take Leadership Role at the Intersection of Finance and Quantum</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-students-take-leadership-role-intersection-finance-and-quantum</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer students developed more than 30% of the available finance coding libraries in Qiskit — the open-source software development environment for working with quantum computers — using RPI’s quantum computer, the only quantum computer in the world available on a university campus.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-students-take-leadership-role-intersection-finance-and-quantum</guid></item><item><title>“Works in Sensing and Feeling” Topic of Talk with Artist Constantina Zavitsanos</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c941a165-00006919calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 8, 2024 6:00 PM - Join EMPAC for a talk from artist Constantina Zavitsanos, whose work ranges from sculpture to performance, and deals with debt and dependency, entropy, thresholds of perception, incapacity, and modes of sensing and feeling. This presentation concludes curator Katherine C.M. Adams’s Decommission series.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c941a165-00006919calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HR Announces Professional Development Book Discussion Series, “Everyday People, Extraordinary Leadership”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-book-discussion-series-everday</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The premise of this book is quite simple: Leadership is a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. This virtual book discussion, which is scheduled to be held from 1:00PM to 2:30PM on Friday, November 22, will explore the five practices of exemplary leadership that are detailed, and participants will share their reactions to the book’s themes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-book-discussion-series-everday</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Training, Resources to Aid Instructors in Adding Questions to SoE Midterm Course Evaluations</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/09/17/2024/soe-faculty-training-heliocampus-adding-additional-questions-soe</link><description>&lt;p&gt;School of Engineering midterm course evaluations will open to the students on October 10 and will close on October 23, with reports available to instructors on October 24. Any instructors who wish to add questions to their courses prior to the course survey opening may do so until October 9; the Office of Undergraduate Education will be offering webinar training sessions on September 25 and October 7 to those who need assistance adding their questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/09/17/2024/soe-faculty-training-heliocampus-adding-additional-questions-soe</guid></item></channel></rss>
