<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Fall 2024 URP Applications Now Being Accepted</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-research-program-urp/08/23/2024/fall-2024-urp-applications-now-being-accepted</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Education is currently accepting Undergraduate Research Program (URP) applications for the Fall 2024 semester! Through the URP, full- and part-time undergraduate students may pursue research for academic credit or as a paid research assistant working in the labs of world-leading Rensselaer faculty researchers during the academic year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-research-program-urp/08/23/2024/fall-2024-urp-applications-now-being-accepted</guid></item><item><title>September 17 Marvell Semiconductor Info Session for RPI Students Only</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2691</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 5:30PM to 6:30PM EDT on Tuesday, September 17 in Low/CII 3112, students are welcome to attend this special session to learn more about Marvell, Inc, a leading semiconductor company at the forefront of data innovation, and the exciting internship opportunities the company has available. If you’re looking for an internship and are passionate about semiconductor design, this is a great chance to discover how you can be a part of Marvell’s journey to shape the future of data technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2691</guid></item><item><title>BD Edge Program - 09/18 - Student Information Sharing Virtual Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/bd-edge-program-0918-student-information-sharing-virtual-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to bring your big ideas and big ambitions to BD, and make your contribution to our next innovation? This virtual session on Wednesday, September 18th, 2024 between 5:30 pm - 7:30 pm will give you insights about working life at BD and our focus on developing new professionals. You’ll hear firsthand how our early career professionals in our Edge Program (Technology &amp;amp; Global Services) are developing their own skills while supporting our mission of, advancing the world of healthTM.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/bd-edge-program-0918-student-information-sharing-virtual-session</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO updated LabView software with new activation serial number</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-updated-labview-software-new-activation-serial-number</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO has updated the LabView activation Serial Number for Students. Please use this new Serial Number when activating LabView products on Single User machines. The ITSSC article providing Installation Instructions for LabView has been updated with this new Serial Number. https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/articles/360014415652-LabVIEW-Installation-Instructions-for-Windows&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-updated-labview-software-new-activation-serial-number</guid></item><item><title>Fellowship Info Session to Highlight Competitions for Grad School Salary and Tuition</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-5705c8e3-0000050acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 20, 2024 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - Competitive fellowships provide salary and tuition for Masters and PhD students. All graduate students, juniors, seniors, and international students are welcome to &lt;a href="https://rpi.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_5q1McRZJMkpb0G2"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; for this session to learn how to find and apply to appropriate programs that will fund fall 2025 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-5705c8e3-0000050acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Don’t Miss the Bicentennial Campus Carnival on September 13!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-5a03a7ae-00004598calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=20240913T150000Z</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In celebration of Rensselaer’s Bicentennial, the campus community is invited to come to Anderson Field from 11:00 AM to 7:00 PM on Friday, September 13 and join the fun at a carnival featuring a Ferris wheel, food trucks, lawn games, and more!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-5a03a7ae-00004598calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=20240913T150000Z</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of the Annual “Run to Remember” 5K!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-0ea510f6-00004e07calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, September 28, 2024 7:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Brought to the Troy community by RPI AFROTC Detachment 550, this family-friendly, community-wide event is aimed at supporting local veterans as well as current college students. With RPI celebrating its 200th year, we hope the Bicentennial will bring the community together to enjoy this outstanding event. 60% of the event profits made will be donated to the Special Operations Warrior Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-0ea510f6-00004e07calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Help Ensure the Upcoming Reunion &amp; Homecoming is a Success!</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23170&amp;ecid=23170&amp;ciid=80446&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Institute Advancement | The Office of Alumni Engagement is looking for assistance/volunteers during Reunion &amp;amp; Homecoming weekend from Friday, September 27 – Sunday, September 29, 2024. Visit the &lt;a href="https://signup.com/go/WuTBGKb"&gt;Reunion &amp;amp; Homecoming SignUp page&lt;/a&gt; to view opportunities and to select the time slots that work for you; training will begin the week of September 16. Your participation will help ensure that our alumni and guests have a great weekend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23170&amp;ecid=23170&amp;ciid=80446&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Harteck Lecture in Physical Chemistry Slated for September 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e1ada44c-0000079fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 17, 2024 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - This event in the Chemistry Department’s Harteck Lecture Series will feature Gabriela Schlau-Cohen, Professor of Chemistry at MIT, who will speak on the topic “Why Don’t Plants Get Sunburn?” All are invited to attend; a reception with food will begin at 3:15 PM.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e1ada44c-0000079fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Congress to Campus” Community Town Hall to be Held September 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e274bf38-00002bf0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 17, 2024 6:30 PM - 8:00 PM - Featuring former members of Congress The Honorable Elizabeth Esty (D-CT) and The Honorable John J. Faso (R-NY), this Town Hall will focus on how technology and social media impact governing and electoral politics, the mechanics of the proposed TikTok ban, and other science and technology policy matters. &lt;a href="https://www.rpi.edu/congress-campus"&gt;Learn more and RSVP&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e274bf38-00002bf0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>American Welding Society, Wire-Arc Additive Manufacturing Event to be Held September 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e6830939-00005cc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 19, 2024 3:00 PM - 7:00 PM - The Manufacturing Innovation Center will host the American Welding Society and SERVO-ROBOT for a conference and demonstration of Wire-Arc Additive Manufacturing, robotic welding and advanced sensors for welding automation. Please &lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/rpi-x-servo-robot-wire-arc-additive-manufacturing-demonstration-tickets-983937281897?aff=oddtdtcreator"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e6830939-00005cc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Webex LTI Legacy Upgraded to Webex LTI 1.3 in Blackboard</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</link><description>&lt;p&gt;MultiMedia Services wishes to inform the campus community that Webex LTI Legacy (formerly Webex Education Connector) has been upgraded in Blackboard to the new Webex LTI 1.3 connector. This is the final upgrade prior to the start of the semester, and brings in increased stability and features for utilizing Webex within a course in Blackboard. Please refer to the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/sections/360008224951"&gt;ITSSC Knowledge Base&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-lti-legacy-upgrades-webex-lti-13-blackboard</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Continue Graduate Certificate Review Sessions September 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8fedc273-00005283calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 19, 2024 3:00 PM - 3:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for this information session highlighting the whole range of Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs. Three courses in length, developing targeted ability groups, and able to be completed in as little as seven months, the certificates can add up to a customized, career-aligned master’s degree. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/certs16"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8fedc273-00005283calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CDPHP Nurse, Member Services Consultations Available to Faculty, Staff September 17</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/cdphp-nurse-and-member-services-consultations</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Because Rensselaer’s Division of Human Resources and our partners at CDPHP, Inc. know how important it is to provide you with opportunities and support in answering questions about your health and medical plan benefits, faculty and staff enrolled in Rensselaer’s medical plans with CDPHP can meet in person with our dedicated nurse and/or a member services representative from noon to 3pm on Tuesday, September 17 at the Heffner Alumni House.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/cdphp-nurse-and-member-services-consultations</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity Schedules Confidential In-Person Retirement Consultation Sessions</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f8b402f-00005970calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 16, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6f8b402f-00005970calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
