<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Welcome Aboard: New Lally Student Cruise</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/welcome-aboard-new-student-cruise</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, August 26, 2025 5:00 p.m. – 8:00 p.m. RPI Lally School of Management welcomes new undergraduate and graduate students for an evening of community building, meeting faculty and staff, and peer networking. Please confirm attendance by Friday, August 22. Space may be limited; early responses are encouraged. RSVP here: https://forms.gle/fZa4U7CbSUnUtfeo7. Location: 177 Front Street, Troy, NY 12180. Dress Code: Business Casual. Contact: mcphij@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/welcome-aboard-new-student-cruise</guid></item><item><title>Dr. Jennifer Pazour Named IISE Fellow in Recognition of Contributions to Industrial and Systems Engineering</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/dr-jennifer-pazour-named-iise-fellow-recognition-contributions-industrial-and-systems</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The ISE Department is proud to announce that Dr. Jennifer Pazour has been named a Fellow of the Institute of Industrial and Systems Engineers (IISE), one of the highest honors awarded by IISE. This prestigious recognition reflects Dr. Pazour’s sustained contributions to research, education, service, and leadership within the field of industrial and systems engineering. Her career centers around solving complex logistics and supply chain challenges through mathematical modeling and optimization.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/dr-jennifer-pazour-named-iise-fellow-recognition-contributions-industrial-and-systems</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Information Session Friday, September 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f73e0b-00003baecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 5, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., will be reviewing the online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates. Expect to hear details about how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment. Please RSVP if you plan to attend and learn more about Rensselaer at Work.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f73e0b-00003baecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Analytics, Machine Learning &amp; AI Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f89066-0000408dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 9, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., on a 30-minute information session highlighting Rensselaer online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning &amp;amp; AI. Expect to learn how data can inform better decisions and review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please RSVP if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f89066-0000408dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI’s Pioneering Information Technology and Web Science (ITWS) Program Joins Lally School of Management</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2025/08/20/rpis-pioneering-information-technology-and-web-science-itws-program-joins-lally-school</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI)’s Information Technology and Web Science (ITWS) program, the first of its kind in the United States, became part of the university’s Lally School of Management on August 16, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2025/08/20/rpis-pioneering-information-technology-and-web-science-itws-program-joins-lally-school</guid></item><item><title>RPI Finance Conference 2025</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10807&amp;cid=24402&amp;ecid=24402&amp;ciid=83498&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to announce the second annual RPI Finance Conference on October 1, 2025. Come explore a curated lineup of interactive sessions designed to advance your professional skills and deepen your understanding of critical topics in higher education. From finance and data to leadership and AI, there’s something for every learner. The registration deadline is September 22, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10807&amp;cid=24402&amp;ecid=24402&amp;ciid=83498&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Fall 2025 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-fall-2025-course-requests</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Fall 2025 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/important-notice-all-instructors-regarding-lms-fall-2025-course-requests</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff Quick Learn Webinar - Ways to Engage Students with Reading Assignments and Micro Video Lectures | Aug. 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-82c690ba-00001ae5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, August 26, 2025 11:00 AM - 11:30 AM - Assigning reading assignments and micro video lectures prior to class is always a great option to allow students to gather initial knowledge. This session will review some tips on how we can engage and motivate the students through these readings or video lectures to guide them in pulling out the important details/understandings. To register for this workshop and see a list of other upcoming workshops, please use the link in the See section.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:42:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-82c690ba-00001ae5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
