<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Lally Co-Terminal Lunch — Open to all students — especially fraternity &amp; sorority members! FREE PIZZA + WINGS | Oct. 29</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/lally-co-terminal-lunch-open-all-students-especially-fraternity-sorority</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Oct. 29 | 11:30 AM – 1:00 PM | Ellsworth Room, Union Level up your leadership and career potential. Learn how to earn your MBA or M.S. at Lally while finishing your undergrad — and stand out in any field with business, strategy, and management skills. Free pizza &amp;amp; wings — bring a friend! Register Here- https://forms.gle/KUNPqVVAZo3VHjht8&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/lally-co-terminal-lunch-open-all-students-especially-fraternity-sorority</guid></item><item><title>Complete the Rensselaer Dining Customer Satisfaction Survey</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/students-complete-rensselaer-dining-customer-satisfaction-survey</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Dining wants to hear from YOU! Share your feedback by completing the Customer Satisfaction Survey by Saturday, November 1st.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/students-complete-rensselaer-dining-customer-satisfaction-survey</guid></item><item><title>Graduate Student Lunch and Learn- Chili Check-In- Registration Required| Nov. 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-a969966b-0000484acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Graduate Student Lunch and Learn- Chili Check-In- Registration RequiredWhen: Wednesday, November 5, 2025, 12:00 PM - 2:30 PMWhere: CBIS Bruggeman RoomDescription: Topic: Chili Check-In (In-Person Event - Registration Required) We want to check in with everyone and see how things are going. Please join us for lunch and small group check-ins-Registration required- email &lt;a href="mailto:sanchn2@rpi.edu"&gt;sanchn2@rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-a969966b-0000484acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Tokyo Electron Site Visit | Nov. 12</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/tokyo-electron-site-visit</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD and Tokyo Electron on Wednesday, November 12th for an on-site info session where you can network with Tokyo Electron (TEL) employees, gain insights into their company culture and cutting-edge technologies, and take a guided tour of their facility. Don’t miss this opportunity to explore career possibilities and ask questions in an informal setting. Lunch and transportation will be provided, but space is limited–register in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/tokyo-electron-site-visit</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; Edgewell Personal Care Info Session | Nov. 4</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-edgewell-personal-care-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD for a virtual info session hosted by 2 RPI alumni now working at Edgewell Personal Care (Schick), on November 4th! They’ll share insights about the company and hybrid co-op opportunities available across several departments. Whether you’re curious about engineering roles, product development, or innovation in personal care, this is a great chance to learn more and connect with fellow Engineers who’ve walked the same campus halls. Register &amp;amp; find the link to join in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-edgewell-personal-care-info-session</guid></item><item><title>ABCD invites all CEE students to Dinner | Nov. 6 (RSVP Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-f779ca58-0000290bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 6, 2025 5:30 PM - 8:00 PM - The Association for Bridge Construction &amp;amp; Design welcomes all Civil &amp;amp; Environmental students to their November dinner meeting. This is a great way to network with local professionals. RSVP is required by 10/30/2025. See attached flyer for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-f779ca58-0000290bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty Spotlight on Research &amp; Impact - Special Edition - Joel Giedt - Decoding the 2025 Nobel Prize in Physics: From Tilted Washboards to Bond Trading | Oct. 31</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-0827c489-000077d5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 31, 2025 2:00 PM - 2:30 PM - Can something you can see with your eyes behave like a quantum particle? The 2025 Nobel Prize in Physics honored John Clarke, Michel Devoret, and John Martinis for proving that even large electrical circuits can follow quantum rules. Their discovery paved the way for today’s quantum computers, including the IBM Quantum System One right here at RPI. Prof. Giedt will help explain how their seminal work transformed physics and opened the door to a…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-0827c489-000077d5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>New Letterhead Available in the RPI Brand Hub</title><link>https://www.rpi.edu/announcements/new-letterhead-available-rpi-brand-hub</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new letterhead template is now available in the &lt;a href="https://brand.rpi.edu"&gt;RPI Brand Hub&lt;/a&gt;. You can also personalize and order the new letterhead directly through the Dupli punchout in the OSCAR Marketplace. For any questions, please contact the Project Management Office at &lt;a href="mailto:brandrefresh@rpi.edu"&gt;brandrefresh@rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.rpi.edu/announcements/new-letterhead-available-rpi-brand-hub</guid></item><item><title>10/29 Cognitive Science Colloquium: “Logic as Applied Mathematics” with Dr. Graham Priest</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/1029-cognitive-science-colloquium-logic-applied-mathematics-dr-graham-priest</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join the Cognitive Science Department on Wednesday, October 29th, at 12pm in Carnegie 113 for a presentation by Dr. Graham Priest titled “Logic as Applied Mathematics”. Dr. Priest is currently Distinguished Professor of Philosophy at the Graduate Center, City University of New York, Boyce Gibson Professor Emeritus at the University of Melbourne, and has visiting positions at the Ruhr University of Bochum (Germany), Tohoku University (Japan), and Shandon University (China).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/1029-cognitive-science-colloquium-logic-applied-mathematics-dr-graham-priest</guid></item><item><title>Halloween Fun with Presidential Pups Easton and Jofa | Oct. 31</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-177b884d-000036c1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 31, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM - Come out to see Presidential Pups Easton and Jofa in their Halloween Costumes. Stop by for visit or just say hello on your way in/out for lunch. They will be on the RSDH Patio/Concourse from 11am-12:30pm.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Free Candy and Treats&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-177b884d-000036c1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Webinar: RPI Digital Asset Management (DAM) System | Oct. 30</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-rpi-digital-asset-management-dam-system</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jim Evans, Director of MultiMedia Services, will present an overview of Rensselaer’s Digital Asset Management (DAM) System on Thursday October 30, from 11am-Noon. This webinar, hosted via webex, will include how to search, download, and manage campus-wide multimedia assets and will include a live demonstration and Q&amp;amp;A. Open to all members of the Rensselaer community. Registration is required: https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/rc9c9293a4dc807a6f342a25031e9dcaf&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-rpi-digital-asset-management-dam-system</guid></item><item><title>RPI now has access to the full IEEE Electronic Library</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-now-has-access-full-ieee-electronic-library</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI Libraries are pleased to announce that the RPI community now has full access to the IEEE Electronic Library (IEL), which provides full-text IEEE content published since 1988, with select content dating back to 1884, from journals, conferences, transactions, magazines, standards, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-now-has-access-full-ieee-electronic-library</guid></item><item><title>Resolved: Cable Television Outage in Specific Campus Buildings</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/resolved-cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the campus that the issue affecting CATV services in several buildings–Sage, Troy, Ricketts, and 87Gym–has been resolved. If any continued issues are observed, please file a support request: https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=12539963570701&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/resolved-cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings</guid></item><item><title>NEW DATE: Information Session: 2026 Project RFP: IBM-RPI Future of Computing Research Collaboration (FCRC) Quantum Computing Track</title><link>https://fcrc.rpi.edu/announcements/new-date-information-session-2026-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us via Microsoft Teams on Tuesday, November 4, 2025, 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM (ET) for an Information Session on the Track-4: Accelerate Quantum Computing Research (2026 Projects) RFP. The Future of Computing Research Center (FCRC)—a partnership between RPI and IBM—advances innovation in AI algorithms, hardware-software co-design, semiconductor technologies, and quantum computing. This session will outline research topics of interest, the proposal template, and submission timelines for Track-4…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://fcrc.rpi.edu/announcements/new-date-information-session-2026-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents: Decolonial Practices in Film Workshop with Suneil Sanzgiri | Oct. 29</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-decolonial-practices-film-workshop-suneil-sanzgiri</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us Oct 29 starting at 4:30pm at the Sanctuary for Independent Media. The program opens with a workshop session on film practice. Sanzgiri and Suchak/ Youth FX reflect on the practical work of filmmaking and consider its impact on the histories and communities it engages. The workshop is followed by a dinner for participants, and a concluding screening of works from Sanzgiri’s series Golden Jubilee.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-decolonial-practices-film-workshop-suneil-sanzgiri</guid></item><item><title>Faculty &amp; Staff Appreciation Day - (10/29/25)</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-day-102925</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer Collegiate Store will have a Faculty &amp;amp; Staff Appreciation Day on Wednesday, October 29, 2025. 25% Off select Drinkware&lt;em&gt;. Free gift with the purchase of $75 or more of clothing / gift (pre tax or any discounts). Available In store only, while supplies last on day of event. RPI employees enjoy a 10% discount on clothing/gift purchases (not including already discounted merchandise) when presenting their RPI ID at time of purchase. &lt;/em&gt;Some exclusions apply. See store for details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-day-102925</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff In Person Workshop - Reviewing Supported Polling Tools On Campus for Courses or Meetings | Nov. 10</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-16995eff-00000f9dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 10, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - In this workshop we will take time to look at a couple polling software tools that are available and supported on campus and discuss the differences. The tools we will be discussing include iClicker and Slido. We will also take a quick look at the free version of Kahoot! (not supported on campus with license but fun!). Please register for this workshop by Nov. 6th as space is limited. Please look in the See section for the registration link…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-16995eff-00000f9dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar – “Certifications &amp; Skill Development in Percipio”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-certifications-skill</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This course introduces the tools available in Percipio to support growth through certifications and skill benchmarks. You’ll learn how to identify relevant certifications and use benchmark assessments to measure current knowledge. Perfect for employees and supervisors alike, this session will help you navigate the platform’s upskilling features and align learning with career development objectives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:34:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-certifications-skill</guid></item></channel></rss>
