<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>McKinney Creative Writing Workshop to be Held 2/21</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-creative-writing-workshop-writing-social-change-d-colin</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Have a story that could inspire others? Ready to raise your voice in solidarity with your community? Want to share your experiences with environmental or social activism? Get help composing or revising an essay, poem, or story for submission to the McKinney Writing for Social Change Contest with author and activist D. Colin on 2/21 at 12pm in the Fischbach Conference Room, on the second floor of the Folsom Library.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-creative-writing-workshop-writing-social-change-d-colin</guid></item><item><title>Don’t Forget Those Therapy Dog Sessions!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-3d022783-00002b95calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, February 6, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:30 PM - Join other students in the Mueller Center classroom to relax, de-stress, and pet some furry friends! If you have any questions or would like more information, please &lt;a href="mailto:atkine2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Emma Atkinson&lt;/a&gt; in the Mueller Center.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-3d022783-00002b95calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>OGE Online Dissertation and Thesis Preparation Workshop to be held February 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-28252791-000011b3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 19, 2025 2:30 PM - 4:00 PM - Learn the basics of correct thesis organization and format, appropriate paper attribution and reference citation styles—plus a review of the most commonly found mistakes and ways to avoid them. This workshop is for any student who will be writing an MS thesis or PhD dissertation. Bring your questions! &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScNtXJPWg-dh0rCgpqjNsUPsCvTo84qzvfDgVDOPzSs1Z0ryg/viewform?usp=header"&gt;Register here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-28252791-000011b3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>STS Guest Speaker Caroline Woolard to give "Design in Society" talk</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-guest-speaker-caroline-woolard-design-society</link><description>&lt;p&gt;What institutions - financial, educational, and cultural - might be required to produce designers who imagine contributions to social justice as obvious to the field of design? This talk presents a design methodology which considers the dynamic relationship between discrete objects (“products”) and long-term collaborative networks (“platforms”). Join us in Sage 5711 from 11:30am-1pm on 2/5.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-guest-speaker-caroline-woolard-design-society</guid></item><item><title>Cognitive Science Colloquium Scheduled for February 5th</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cognitive-science-colloquium-scheduled-february-5th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the Cognitive Science Department in Carnegie 113 for a presentation by Dr. Jerome Busemeyer (Distinguished Professor, Indiana University Bloomington) titled “Using Quantum Probability to Understand Contextual Reasoning”. Event runs 12pm- 1:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cognitive-science-colloquium-scheduled-february-5th</guid></item><item><title>02/13/2025 9am to 11am open on-campus office hours held by IBM quantum support</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/02132025-9am-11am-open-campus-office-hours-held-ibm-quantum-support</link><description>&lt;p&gt;IBM quantum support will be holding open on-campus office hours Thursday, February 13th from 9am to 11am ET in CII 3159. During this time, IBM personnel will be available to answer questions regarding your specific applications about quantum computing, quantum algorithms, and other quantum computer questions you may have. For additional information about RPI Quantum Computing, please visit https://quantum.rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/02132025-9am-11am-open-campus-office-hours-held-ibm-quantum-support</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Schedules February 7 Info Session</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-3c8f9a9b-0000566fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, February 7, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/general7"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates. Attendees will also hear details about how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-3c8f9a9b-0000566fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Annual 2025 McKinney Student Awards Ceremony and Speaker Series to be held April 9</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/annual-2025-mckinney-student-awards-ceremony-and-speaker-series</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 83rd annual McKinney Reading Series and Student Awards Ceremony is Wednesday, April 9th, 7:00-9:00 p.m. featuring Lan Samantha Chang, winner of the Anisfield-Wolf Book Award for Fiction and the PEN Open Book Award. The event will feature the announcement of McKinney Student Writing Contest winners, a fiction reading, and audience Q &amp;amp; A. An opportunity to purchase books and meet the author will follow.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/annual-2025-mckinney-student-awards-ceremony-and-speaker-series</guid></item><item><title>ECSE Seminar: “BAWFET: A Compact Monolithic Integration Combining BAWs and FETs for Active Filtering”</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-b33d56ea-00007244calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, February 12, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join us for an ECSE Seminar: “BAWFET: A Compact Monolithic Integration Combining BAWs and FETs for Active Filtering” with Wenwen Zhao, PhD Candidate at Cornell University. Abstract and speaker bio can be found at the event URL.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-b33d56ea-00007244calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Analytics, Machine Learning and AI Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-989a6e48-00001c3bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 19, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., on a 30-minute information session highlighting Rensselaer online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning &amp;amp; AI. Expect to learn how data can inform better decisions and review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please register if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-989a6e48-00001c3bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HR to Hold Professional Development Workshop, “Leading from Anywhere”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: At Rensselaer, we maintain that “leadership” involves a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. In this workshop, scheduled to be held from 9am to 11am on February 20, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership not as positional or based on title, but rather on values and actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:31:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere</guid></item></channel></rss>
