<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Haleon Site Visit | Oct. 29 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/haleon-site-visit</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD for a visit to Haleon’s Oak Hill manufacturing site in East Durham, NY on Wednesday, October 29th from 10am-1pm! You’ll be able to tour the facilities, learn about Haleon’s mission and values, and network with Haleon team members over a pizza lunch. Register in Handshake–transportation is provided but space is limited!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/haleon-site-visit</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 School of Engineering Midterm Student Course Evaluations Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-9b46c654-00003336calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 10, 2025 (all day) - Fall 2025 School of Engineering (SoE) Midterm course evaluations are now open. Your feedback is very important to the Institute and the school, so please complete the SoE midterm evaluation surveys for all your courses! Evaluations will be available through Thursday, October 23, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-9b46c654-00003336calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Lally Co-Terminal Info Session for Computer Science Majors — FREE PIZZA + WINGS | Oct. 23</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/lally-co-terminal-info-session-computer-science-majors-free-pizza-wings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Oct. 23 | 6:00 PM | Lally 102 Stand out in a tough tech job market. Learn how to earn your MBA or M.S. at Lally while finishing your CS degree. Boost your résumé with business, leadership, and innovation skills that set you apart in AI, data, and software careers. We’ll cover program options, admissions steps, and how to make it work for you. Pizza + wings provided! Register Here- https://forms.gle/KUNPqVVAZo3VHjht8&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/lally-co-terminal-info-session-computer-science-majors-free-pizza-wings</guid></item><item><title>New Minor in Quantum Computing Now Available</title><link>https://compsci.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-quantum-computing-now-available</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new interdisciplinary minor is available for any student who wants to explore quantum computing. Students will gain both theoretical insight and practical exposure to quantum algorithms, hardware platforms, and the concept of quantum advantage, the point at which quantum systems outperform classical approaches on meaningful tasks. Minor requirements can be found in the RPI catalog. To discuss declaring this minor, please contact the School of Science Hub at ScienceHub@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://compsci.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-quantum-computing-now-available</guid></item><item><title>Register for the Investiture of Shekhar Garde by Oct. 29</title><link>https://www.rpi.edu/announcements/register-investiture-shekhar-garde</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us November 5 as Dean Shekhar Garde formally assumes the first endowed deanship in RPI’s history, made possible through the generosity of Thomas R. Farino, Jr. ’67 and Patricia E. Farino. Please &lt;a href="https://www.alumni.rpi.edu/s/1225/alumni/index.aspx?sid=1225&amp;amp;gid=1&amp;amp;pgid=10869&amp;amp;cid=24521&amp;amp;ecid=24521"&gt;register online&lt;/a&gt; by Wednesday, October 29.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.rpi.edu/announcements/register-investiture-shekhar-garde</guid></item><item><title>Webex vs Teams: Choosing the Right Tool for Your Campus Workflows | Oct. 24</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-vs-teams-choosing-right-tool-your-campus-workflows</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The campus community has access to both Cisco Webex and Microsoft Teams, but which is best for your needs? Join us on Friday, October 24, 2025, 10-11:30am for a practical, fast-paced session comparing the strengths of each platform. Whether you’re teaching, hosting a symposium, collaborating on a grant proposal, or streamlining your team’s communication, we’ll help you match the right tool to the task. Register at https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/r4235dc39258dd1620e7365907d91af2d&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-vs-teams-choosing-right-tool-your-campus-workflows</guid></item><item><title>HASS Family Weekend Music Showcase on Saturday October 25</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/hass-family-weekend-music-showcase</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This program features the RPI Orchestra, Concert Choir, and Wind Symphony in a musical preview of works that will be included on the Dec. 6th RPI Holiday Concert, including Mark Camphouse’s “A Movement for Rosa”, Christopher Tin’s “Baba Yetu”, and Bedrich Smetana’s “Die Moldau”. Admission is free. Showcase starts at 2:30pm in DCC 308.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/hass-family-weekend-music-showcase</guid></item><item><title>NSF GRFP Letters of Recommendation Due November 7th</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-06d9ac83-00001c8ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 23, 2025 (all day) - Letters of Recommendation for the NSF GRFP are due November 7th, BEFORE student application deadlines. All student applications should be reviewed by Betty Madigan to check for compliance with the NEW formatting requirements. Send statements at least a week before the deadline. Additionally, a faculty guide for writing letters of recommendation is available upon request. Requests for information and reviews should be sent to madige@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-06d9ac83-00001c8ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty &amp; Staff Appreciation Day - (10/29/25)</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-day-102925</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer Collegiate Store will have a Faculty &amp;amp; Staff Appreciation Day on Wednesday, October 29, 2025. 25% Off select Drinkware&lt;em&gt;. Free gift with the purchase of $75 or more of clothing / gift (pre tax or any discounts). Available In store only, while supplies last on day of event. RPI employees enjoy a 10% discount on clothing/gift purchases (not including already discounted merchandise) when presenting their RPI ID at time of purchase. &lt;/em&gt;Some exclusions apply. See store for details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-day-102925</guid></item></channel></rss>
