<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>2026 McKinney Writing Contest is open!</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-mckinney-writing-contest</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2026 McKinney Writing Contest is open from November 1, 2025 through March 9, 2026. Submit in any or all of the following categories: Fiction, Creative Nonfiction, or Drama; Poetry; Academic Essay; Language &amp;amp; Image; or our NEW category: Writing for Games. Undergraduate and graduate divisions. First prize $300; 2nd prize $175; and 3rd prize $75. Submit: https://hass.rpi.edu/mckinney. Submit in fall for December graduates. Questions? McKinney@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-mckinney-writing-contest</guid></item><item><title>Schmidt Science Fellowship Seeking Applicants for Prestigious Post-doctoral Fellowship</title><link>https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/schmidt-science-fellowship-seeking-candidates-2-year-post-doctoral-opportunity</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fellows receive $110K per year for two years, are placed at an internationally prestigious lab, and are mentored by world leaders in science and industry. PhD students graduating between May 2026 and June 2027 who are interested in developing skills in a discipline different than their own should contact Betty Madigan, madige@rpi.edu, by April 10th for information on the internal selection process. A committee will select 2 nominees to be submitted in May. Questions? madige@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/schmidt-science-fellowship-seeking-candidates-2-year-post-doctoral-opportunity</guid></item><item><title>Financial Research Resources Available to All RPI Students</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/financial-research-resources-available-all-rpi-students</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All RPI students have access to financial research tools through the Lally School of Management, including Bloomberg, FactSet, S&amp;amp;P Capital IQ, Wharton Research Data Services (WRDS), and more. Visit the Lally website to learn more about available resources and how to access them.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/financial-research-resources-available-all-rpi-students</guid></item><item><title>City Station West Housing Update</title><link>https://studentexperience.rpi.edu/announcements/city-station-west-housing-update</link><description>&lt;p&gt;City Station West will continue to operate independently from RPI and lease primarily to RPI students. Juniors, seniors, and graduate students who have fulfilled their on-campus housing requirement may lease directly with City Station West as an off-campus option. However, City Station West will no longer be included in Student Living and Learning’s housing inventory or appear on RPI housing applications beginning with Summer and Fall 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studentexperience.rpi.edu/announcements/city-station-west-housing-update</guid></item><item><title>Prepare for the Career Fair with PCA’s (and pizza!)</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/prepare-career-fair-pcas-and-pizza</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for an informative and interactive session hosted by your peers working in the Career Center! Our team of experienced student advisors will share valuable tips and strategies on how to prepare effectively for a career fair. Whether you’re fine-tuning your resume, crafting an elevator pitch, or deciding what to wear, this event will help you feel confident and prepared. Bring your questions and get ready to walk into the career fair with confidence! Free pizza provided!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/prepare-career-fair-pcas-and-pizza</guid></item><item><title>Welcome Back to Campus and the Spring Semester</title><link>https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/welcome-back-campus-and-spring-semester</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s time for your semesterly reminder to review the RPI Handbook of Student Rights &amp;amp; Responsibilities. We’ve updated the Student Handbook to clarify expectations, streamline processes, and strengthen support resources for this academic year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/welcome-back-campus-and-spring-semester</guid></item><item><title>ASCE Student Chapter Meeting</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c1acef6-019c-1f5de8af-00003542calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, February 5, 2026 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - Join fellow students for a presentation by RPI adjunct professor Marc Tartarsky. Prof Tartarsky will highlight Arup’s structural engineering program and discuss some of their current projects. Arup is an international design, engineering, architecture, and planning firm. Pizza will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c1acef6-019c-1f5de8af-00003542calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Big Game and Valentines Day Packages from 1824 Catering!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/big-game-and-valentines-day-packages-1824-catering</link><description>&lt;p&gt;There’s still time to treat your sweetheart or your game day crew to some seriously awesome eats from 1824 Catering! Click the link to find out more information on these packages. Orders for the Big Game are due Friday, February 6th and Valentines Day are due Monday, February 9th. Don’t wait—good food + good company = a win every time!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/big-game-and-valentines-day-packages-1824-catering</guid></item><item><title>Regeneron seeking nominees for Annual Prize for Creative Innovation</title><link>https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/regeneron-seeking-nominees-annual-prize-creative-innovation</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Regeneron seeks to award creativity and innovation in the biomedical sciences with an unrestricted check for $50,000 and an invitation to present a project at Regeneron’s headquarters. Up to 10 finalists will receive a $5,000 award. Rensselaer will select 2 PhD students and 2 post-docs from any discipline for nomination. Contact this office (madige@rpi.edu) for full details and instructions to submit for the internal selection process. Applications will be due to OGE by February 15th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/regeneron-seeking-nominees-annual-prize-creative-innovation</guid></item><item><title>Florian Idenburg</title><link>https://www.arch.rpi.edu/2026/02/florian-idenburg/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;“Once Again, but This Time with More Feeling” Mike Wacholder Memorial Lecture Wednesday, February 04, 5:00p.m. est EMPAC Theater Rensselaer Architecture continues its spring 2026 lecture series this Wednesday, February 4th at 5p.m. est with the lecture “Once Again, but This Time with More Feeling” by Florian Idenburg of Solid Objectives (SO-IL). Florian Idenburg is an internationally renowned Dutch architect with over two decades of professional experience. After…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.arch.rpi.edu/2026/02/florian-idenburg/</guid></item><item><title>Study Abroad Application Portal Open!</title><link>https://isss.rpi.edu/announcements/study-abroad-application-portal-now-open-summer-fall-2026-and-academic-year-2026-2027</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you an undergraduate student who is ready to study abroad? The application portal for summer/fall ’26 &amp;amp; AY ’26-’27 is open! Application deadlines are March 1 for affiliated exchanges and April 1 for non-affiliated study abroad. Visit the Education Abroad website for more information and application instructions: https://isss.rpi.edu/education-abroad/program-information/application-process-and-deadlines. Have questions? Contact Karen Dvorak, Education Abroad Program Manager, dvorak2@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://isss.rpi.edu/announcements/study-abroad-application-portal-now-open-summer-fall-2026-and-academic-year-2026-2027</guid></item></channel></rss>
