<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Student Food Pantry Summer Hours starting next week</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-912fbb99-0000497ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, May 6, 2025 1:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Starting week of May 13th The Student Food pantry will be open Tuesday 1-4 and Wednesday 9am -noon. Any student is welcome to use the resource. Fall hours will begin September 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-912fbb99-0000497ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Hudson Mohawk: Lectures on Tap at The Ruck | May 8</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10575&amp;cid=23885&amp;ecid=23885&amp;ciid=82203&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: 5/8/2025 6:00 PM to 8:00 PM Please join the Hudson Mohawk Chapter of the Rensselaer Alumni Association for the inaugural Technical Lecture Series in a fun, relaxed setting! Aptly named “Lectures on Tap,” we have lined up speaker Dr. Brian Callahan, ’15G, ’18 Ph.D., Director of the Rensselaer Cybersecurity Collaborative. He will be discussing his successes and research at the collaborative regarding cyber security and will convey his knowledge and actionable advice…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10575&amp;cid=23885&amp;ecid=23885&amp;ciid=82203&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>2025 Annual Utility Shutdown</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/administration/04/10/2025/2025-annual-utility-shutdown</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All members of the campus community should note the dates for the 2025 Annual Utility Shutdown for Assessment and Repair. Steam outages are scheduled to take place from May 10th -17th. Electrical outages, which are necessary to exercise distribution feeders and test the campus’ automatic power transfer switches, is scheduled for May 12th-15th. Please check the spreadsheet links on the Administration Division’s website for specific outage dates and times for each building.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/administration/04/10/2025/2025-annual-utility-shutdown</guid></item><item><title>The Last Lecture | May 8</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-35069825-00002756calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 8, 2025 2:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Patterned off the Last Lecture Series made famous by Dr. Randy Pausch, Rensselaer’s graduating class celebrates their last lecture at Rensselaer with lectures by faculty on diverse topics. Graduating students helped to choose who they would like to hear from one last time. Books will be provided to the first 20 students. Reception to follow.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-35069825-00002756calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Removal of Unused Webex Recordings</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/removal-unused-webex-recordings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As the semester ends, Multimedia Services highly recommends deleting any Webex recordings that are no longer required for future viewing or archival. This will ensure that storage space is available for all users for future recordings. For assistance with Webex recording management, please submit a Help Desk request.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/removal-unused-webex-recordings</guid></item><item><title>Does Your Syllabus Need a Tune-Up? HelioCampus Syllabus Assistance Available</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-assistance-available-may-7</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you new to HelioCampus? Would you like to give your syllabus a “tune-up? Come to the Fischbach Room in the library on May 7 at 10:00 for assistance. Amy Svirsky, RPI’s Learning Assessment Specialist, will be there to assist you, answer your questions and show you how to use the tool.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-assistance-available-may-7</guid></item><item><title>Capital Region Basketball Camp at RPI!</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/capital-region-basketball-camp-rpi</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Capital Region Basketball Camp for kids age 8-15, is a unique summer camp in which RPI Head Men’s Basketball Coach Mark Gilbride, and his staff have designed programs to develop all facets of each camper’s game, as well as help increase their individual and team skills in an atmosphere that is challenging, competitive, and fun. Enjoy the convenience of dropping your child off at a sports camp right where you work!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/capital-region-basketball-camp-rpi</guid></item></channel></rss>
