<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:31:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Graduate certificate Review with Rensselaer at Work | May 14</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5f076851-00004993calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, May 14, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., in a 30-minute information session highlighting the whole range of Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs. These certificates are three courses in length, developing targeted ability groups, and can be completed in as little as seven months. Please complete the form below if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5f076851-00004993calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Removal of Unused Webex Recordings</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/removal-unused-webex-recordings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As the semester ends, Multimedia Services highly recommends deleting any Webex recordings that are no longer required for future viewing or archival. This will ensure that storage space is available for all users for future recordings. For assistance with Webex recording management, please submit a Help Desk request.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/removal-unused-webex-recordings</guid></item><item><title>Pittsburgh Building Closed for Renovations This Summer</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/pittsburgh-building-closed-renovations-summer</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Pittsburgh Building will be fully closed for renovations beginning Monday, May 12, and will remain inaccessible through Wednesday, August 21. During this period, no access will be permitted for any faculty, staff, students, or visitors. Please plan accordingly. Thank you for your cooperation as we work to improve our facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/pittsburgh-building-closed-renovations-summer</guid></item><item><title>TIAA Confidential Counseling (In-Person) | May 13</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-753282ad-00004900calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, May 13, 2025 8:00 AM - 4:30 PM - A TIAA Financial Consultant will be available for one-on-one consultations on a broad range of retirement topics. Attend this upcoming event to help you become better informed and more confident about Rensselaer’s retirement plan benefits. Consultations will be conducted in 60 minute increments. To schedule your individual retirement counseling, please call TIAA at 1-800-732-8353 or &lt;a href="https://shared.tiaa.org/public/publictools/events…"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-753282ad-00004900calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HR CONNECT - Your Wellbeing Matters</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/hr-connect-your-wellbeing-matters</link><description>&lt;p&gt;May is Mental Health Awareness Month—a meaningful time to recognize the importance of work-life balance. At RPI, we are committed to supporting the mental health of our faculty and staff through services that help ease everyday responsibilities and stress so you can focus on the things that really matter to you. Join the Division of Human Resources on Wednesday, May 14 at 1:00 PM as we learn about the services A New England Nanny (ANEN) offers and how they can help you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:31:48 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/hr-connect-your-wellbeing-matters</guid></item></channel></rss>
