<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Ph.D. Hooding Ceremony 2025 | May 9</title><link>https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/phd-hooding-ceremony-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When: Friday, May 9, 2025 Where: EMPAC - Concert Hall Check-in starts- at 7:45 AM ( coffee will be served) Ceremony- at 8:30 AM Refreshments- after the ceremony concludes. The hooding ceremony is a unique recognition of the achievement of each student who has earned a doctorate. Each doctoral candidate is introduced individually during the ceremony. They will have their hood placed on them while standing on the stage in the concert hall.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/phd-hooding-ceremony-2025</guid></item><item><title>James Fund Applications Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-40243de0-0000139bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 16, 2025 12:00 AM - Mon , April 28, 2025 12:00 AM - What: Join RPI’s student-managed investment fund to gain hands-on experience managing a six-figure portfolio, conducting investment research, and learning key finance concepts. Members benefit from a collaborative team environment and exclusive networking opportunities. Apply now! Who Should Apply: Students of any background interested in markets, finance, economics, or quantitative risk. Deadline: April 28th&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-40243de0-0000139bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Nominate a student for a 2025 Lavender Graduation Award by May 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-58c087a3-00002668calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, April 21, 2025 11:00 AM - Mon , May 5, 2025 5:00 PM - The Rensselaer LGBTQ+ Task Force is seeking nominations for students, faculty, and staff to be honored at the 8th Annual Lavender Graduation, to be held on Wednesday, May 7th at 2PM in the CBIS Auditorium. These awards celebrate some of our most deserving students for the contributions they have made to the Rensselaer LGBTQ+ community. Our community is better as a result of their time at Rensselaer and these awards are a way of…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-58c087a3-00002668calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI Libraries is here to support you during study days and finals</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-here-support-you-during-study-days-and-finals</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Study late at the Folsom Library on reading and study days. We’re open during finals week until 1 am most days. Argo Tea will also have extended hours. Schedule your study breaks! Folsom Library will have crafts, activities, games, and plushie study buddies available. Show off your RPI knowledge in our staff-created Jeopardy game and exchange your answer card for some study candy at the Service Desk. Bring your family in after commencement! We are open on Saturday, 5/10, from 2 pm to 6 pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-here-support-you-during-study-days-and-finals</guid></item><item><title>Taste of African Grace - “Uso Amara Africa” | April 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-62c8ee46-0000684dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, April 26, 2025 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - “Uso Amara Africa” This Saturday join us for 5PM Catholic Mass with the Otuto Choir and African cookout following!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-62c8ee46-0000684dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Expanded ISSS Advising, Weekdays from April 15-25, 2025</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-services-students-and-scholars/04/14/2025/expanded-isss-advising-april-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;ISSS is offering expanded advising hours for students and alumni to ask questions and get guidance as we approach the end of the semester. The expanded hours will be held on weekdays from April 15 through April 25. Walk-In Advising will be available weekdays from 10:00 a.m. - 11:00 a.m. (new!) and from 2:00 p.m. - 3:00 p.m. Virtual Advising will have expanded hours both weeks. To see the new availability, click &lt;a href="https://outlook.office365.com/book/ISSSOffice1@rpi.edu/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-services-students-and-scholars/04/14/2025/expanded-isss-advising-april-2025</guid></item><item><title>Celebrate the Future Generations of Game Designers at GameFest 2025</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/gamefest-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;GameFest returns to the Tech Valley Center of Gravity in Downtown Troy on Saturday, April 26 from 1pm-7pm. GameFest is an annual showcase of student talent in game development, bringing together students from around New York State and the Northeast to exhibit their games. The GameFest awards recognize excellence in game design, technical innovation, artistic quality, and narrative design, and are awarded by a panel of expert judges from game studios in the Capital Region.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/gamefest-2025</guid></item><item><title>19 New Employees Join RPI in March!</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/19-new-employees-join-rpi-march</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to introduce 19 new employees who joined RPI in March! Let’s give them a warm welcome as they begin their journey at RPI!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:36:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/19-new-employees-join-rpi-march</guid></item></channel></rss>
