<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:31:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Session to Review Supply Chain, Lean Six Sigma, Systems Engineering</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4aa5dc65-00003f8dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, July 2, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/SCCT2"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D. as he highlights Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in areas surrounding Supply Chain and Logistics, Systems Engineering, and Lean Quality. Attendees will also learn how these certificates were created in consultation with enterprises that recognize the opportunity and risks of a global supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-4aa5dc65-00003f8dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Nominations Being Sought for RAA Teaching Award</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22919&amp;ecid=22919&amp;ciid=79492&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Nominations are now being accepted for the 2024 Rensselaer Alumni Association (RAA) Teaching Award, which recognizes current members of the faculty for their outstanding teaching techniques, contributions to the campus experience, and commitment to students. Nominations are due by Wednesday, July 31.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22919&amp;ecid=22919&amp;ciid=79492&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Campus Summer Shuttle Service to Continue for City Station Residents</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/06/13/2024/campus-summer-shuttle-service</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Parking and Transportation will be continuing shuttle service to Rensselaer students living at the City Station residences for the summer, with shuttle service to run from 10AM to 10PM Monday through Saturday, and from noon to 8PM on Sunday. The City Station shuttle bus stop is located in front of City Station East.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/06/13/2024/campus-summer-shuttle-service</guid></item></channel></rss>
