<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>DOSO Day 9/25</title><link>https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/doso-day-925</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come meet the Dean of Students Office Staff while enjoying some activities, snack foods, and ice cream for the first 100 guests! This event is open to the RPI student body on Thursday, 9/25 from 2-4pm located at Off-Campus Commons (1525 15th street). We look forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/doso-day-925</guid></item><item><title>Alumni Fraternity &amp; Sorority Council Student Mental Health Workshop | Sept. 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-37b8eef8-0000518ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, September 20, 2025 10:00 AM - 3:00 PM - Join the Alumni Fraternity &amp;amp; Sorority Council for a FREE full breakfast buffet and the Student Mental Health Workshop! You will hear best practices, learn about available campus resources, and hear how campus involvement can boost mental well-being and enhance your RPI experience. This is an event for ALL students, not just fraternity and sorority members. Join us for connection, conversation, and growth and leave feeling good!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0198-37b8eef8-0000518ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>John Storyk to Speak at DCC September 19</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/john-storyk-lessons-electric-lady</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On September 19 at 2pm in DCC174, John will talk about how the recording studio has changed dramatically in the past 10 years in ways that were at one time almost unpredictable. Both the business models and studio designs, as well as equipment configurations are markedly different, with changes continuing. The shift from large ‘all at once’ sessions to a file-based – shared mixing process has ushered in a new era of small, yet powerful and highly flexible audio content creation environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/john-storyk-lessons-electric-lady</guid></item><item><title>2025-26 Student Advisory Council (SAC) - Application deadline September 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d825c46-00002640calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, September 24, 2025 8:00 AM - 7:00 PM - Applications are now open for the 2025–26 Student Advisory Council (SAC)! Hosted by Vice Provosts Dr. Rob Hradsky and Dr. Matt Oehlschlaeger, the SAC connects students with campus leadership to shape academics, student life, and RPI culture. Meetings are biweekly on Fridays, 12–1:30 PM. Apply by Sept. 24 to make your voice heard and create positive change. Questions? Contact Quadir “Q” Webster at webstq@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d825c46-00002640calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Join RPI Judicial Board! Apply by Sept. 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-4e419755-00007611calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 22, 2025 12:00 AM - RPI Judicial Board, part of student government, is the primary court of judgement in student disciplinary, conduct and union based cases. Be a part of making important campus decision and help shape RPI and our student body. All with a low time commitment! To join apply with the link below! Applications are due Monday Sept 22nd. https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfyosmnRmkl9MVrz4WbF0lyNJHpXpoFE38i7HQQxJPD-mt-1Q/viewform?usp=header&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-4e419755-00007611calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents! Le Ratoire Plant Processing Workshop | Sept. 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-le-ratoire-plant-processing-workshop</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, Le Ratoire artist collective will work with participants to learn how to make black &amp;amp; white film/photo developer using just local plants, ashes, and water. No industrial products, nothing from the store! We will go over the techniques of photograms (also known as rayograms) and phytography, two ways of exposing and making images on photo paper without needing to use a camera. Join us September 20 at 2pm at the NATURE Lab at the Sanctuary for Independent Media.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-le-ratoire-plant-processing-workshop</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents! “Turn the Light Around”: 16mm Plant Processed Performance and Films by Le Ratoire | Sept. 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-turn-light-around-16mm-plant-processed-performance-and-films-le-ratoire</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us September 20 at 7pm at The Sanctuary for Independent Media for screenings of 16mm plant-processed performance films, presented by Katherine Bauer and Joyce Lainé, members of the film collective Le Ratoire and Atelier MTK. The image sin each film emerge before our eyes through the process of a developer composed of plants, ashes, and water. The screening will be followed by Q&amp;amp;A. This event is co-sponsored by iEAR Presents and The Sanctuary for Independent Media.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-turn-light-around-16mm-plant-processed-performance-and-films-le-ratoire</guid></item><item><title>SEPTEMBER Mercer X Workshops and Seminars</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/september-mercer-x-clubhouse-workshops-and-seminars</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The SEPTEMBER Mercer X Clubhouse Workshops and Seminars are available! Please use the contact information on the flyer to register or inquire about the events listed. Navigate to the Calendar view or the Workshop Gallery and Flyers View for more information about how you can join the opportunities to learn in the Mercer X Community! Deep Learning with MATLAB, an IC Design Series, RPAi Brainstorming with Brain Freeze (Ice Cream), and IEEE EPS Seminars are in the September lineup!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/september-mercer-x-clubhouse-workshops-and-seminars</guid></item><item><title>Webex: Recording to the Cloud and Storage Quota</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-recording-cloud-and-storage-quota</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As the semester begins, Multimedia Services recommends that all community members review any Webex recordings stored in the cloud. Each user has an allotted quota of storage space, and exceeding that quota will disallow recording to the cloud. Any recordings which are no longer required for future viewing or archival purposes should be removed. For assistance with Webex recording management, please submit a Help Desk request.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-recording-cloud-and-storage-quota</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff In Person Workshop - Beta Classroom - Teaching with Technology Preview | Sept. 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-0fafb137-00001377calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 22, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Come see the Collaboratory space in the main library, and the exciting technologies available to you in the Beta Classroom. The beta classroom is a high technology testing space for interactive learning. The goal of the beta classroom is for faculty to pilot new or interactive technologies and pedagogical approaches that can be recommended for other classrooms on campus. This is also the educational space of the Teaching and Learning…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-0fafb137-00001377calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Please join us for the next talk in the Quantum Vision Lecture Series Sept. 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-1b3556ad-00006478calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 22, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - This session will feature James A. Misewich, Ph.D., Associate Laboratory Director for Energy and Photon Science, Brookhaven National Laboratory. The talk will explore innovative strategies for advancing quantum research and discuss opportunities to leverage RPI’s intellectual and infrastructure strengths to enhance our position at the forefront of this rapidly evolving domain. The presentation will last approximately 30 minutes, followed by…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-1b3556ad-00006478calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Did you know that a quarter of staff vacancies are filled by current employees?</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/did-you-know-quarter-staff-vacancies-are-filled-current-employees</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that nearly 1 in 4 of the posted staff vacancies at RPI are filled by current RPI employees? Ever wonder if you could be next? Competing for a vacancy is an effective way to learn more about other jobs on campus and has the added benefit of giving hiring managers the chance to learn more about your career aspirations, your talents, and your contributions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:32:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/did-you-know-quarter-staff-vacancies-are-filled-current-employees</guid></item></channel></rss>
