<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Civic Engagement Opportunity: CCPD and Sidewalk Warriors, Troy, NY | April 3</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/civic-engagement-opportunity-ccpd-and-sidewalk-warriors-troy-ny-april-3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Center for Career and Professional Development (CCPD) is excited to extend an invitation to all students who are passionate about making a positive impact in our community. On Thursday, April 3, 2025, beginning at 4:30 PM, the CCPD and participating students will be volunteering with Sidewalk Warriors in Troy, New York. See Handshake for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/civic-engagement-opportunity-ccpd-and-sidewalk-warriors-troy-ny-april-3</guid></item><item><title>Demystifying the Civil Service Merit System: Careers in Public Service | April 8</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/demystifying-civil-service-merit-system-careers-public-service-april-8</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on Tuesday, April 8th, 2025 at 5:30 pm - 6:30 pm in Low 3112 as the CCPD hosts Adam Rossi, Capital Region CCG Specialist from the New York State Department of Civil Service who will present a workshop on career and internship opportunities in New York State and how to apply.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/demystifying-civil-service-merit-system-careers-public-service-april-8</guid></item><item><title>What’s Next After Graduation?</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/whats-next-after-graduation</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI students consistently excel, with placement rates ranging from 91–95% in recent years. In 2023, among those placed, 56% secured employment, 33% enrolled in graduate school, and 11% pursued other opportunities, including military service, travel abroad, the Peace Corps, non-traditional employment, and entrepreneurship. Curious to learn more? Dive into Standard 5 of RPI’s Self-Study for Middle States Accreditation, a team led by Dr. Brett Fajen and Dr. Matt Oehlschlaeger.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/whats-next-after-graduation</guid></item><item><title>Curious About the Middle States Accreditation Findings? | April 9</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-afb9eda7-000022d5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;At the end of the Middle States Accreditation on-campus visit, the visiting team will host a Community Meeting to present their final report. After reviewing our Self-Study, analyzing hundreds of supporting documents, and engaging with many members of the RPI community during their 2.5-day visit, what will they conclude about RPI? Join us for the Final Readout on Wednesday, April 9, at 11:00 AM. Fun fact: the visiting team will present their report but won’t take questions!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-afb9eda7-000022d5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ECSE Mercer Lecture: “Surprises in Information Theory” | April 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-b8f9f98b-00005847calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 2, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join us for an ECSE Mercer Distinguished Lecture: “Surprises in Information Theory” with Prof. Wei Yu of University of Toronto. Abstract and speaker bio can be found at the event URL.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-b8f9f98b-00005847calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Marx, Mars, and Hyrule: Imagining Planetary Futures: Christian P. Haines to Speak on March 28</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/marx-mars-and-hyrule-imagining-planetary-futures-christian-p-haines</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, March 28, 4:30 - 6:00 PM, SAGE 3303: What do Marxism, science fiction, and video games have in common? They are all efforts to imagine what it’s like to live in complex planetary ecosystems. In this lecture, Christian P. Haines (Assoc. Prof. of English, Penn State) critically examines fantasies of terraforming as alibis for socioeconomic inequality and political injustice.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/marx-mars-and-hyrule-imagining-planetary-futures-christian-p-haines</guid></item><item><title>STEAMM Inventor’s Studio offered in Summer 2025</title><link>https://summer.rpi.edu/announcements/steamm-inventors-studio-offered-summer-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Calling all community rising 10th to 12th graders, don’t miss the STEAMM Inventor’s Studio at RPI — a hands-on summer program exploring cutting-edge fields like semiconductors, advanced manufacturing, robotics, AI, quantum computing, and more. This two-week program runs from July 28 to August 8, 2025. Find more details on summer.rpi.edu and apply today.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://summer.rpi.edu/announcements/steamm-inventors-studio-offered-summer-2025</guid></item><item><title>Thank you from the Office of Admissions!</title><link>https://undergrad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/thank-you</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Admissions would like to thank all students, faculty, and staff who volunteered at the Accepted Student Celebration on March 22. Seeing everyone come together to support our yield efforts was very appreciated by all, especially accepted students and their families. We look forward to doing it again on April 12! If you have any questions or want to learn more about helping out, please email Arianna Livshits at paluma3@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/thank-you</guid></item><item><title>Future of Computing Institute (FOCI) Sneak Preview: Project Chapel film by Chris Groban</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-d8d04edf-00000a5ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, April 2, 2025 6:30 PM - FOCI invites the campus community to an exclusive sneak preview of Project Chapel, the new film by acclaimed director Chris Groban. Project Chapel follows the historic, world-first installation of a quantum computer inside RPI’s very own VCC chapel. &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/rsvp-project-chapel-film-chris-groban-sneak-preview"&gt;Please RSVP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-d8d04edf-00000a5ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Celebrating the Life of Chuck Boylen | March 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-8c1807a3-000047c5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, March 29, 2025 11:00 AM - 2:30 PM - Dr. Charles “Chuck” Boylen died February 13 after a battle with pancreatic cancer. As Professor of Biology and Associate Director of RPI’s Darrin Fresh Water Institute (DFWI), he worked with all aspects of running the research field station. He was internationally known for his New York State limnology research, and was academic advisor to the Theta Xi fraternity. A celebration of life will be held on what would have been his 83rd birthday. All who knew him are welcome.Where: Chapel+Cultural Center, 2125 Burdett Avenue, Troy, NY 12180 New…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-8c1807a3-000047c5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty/Staff Memorial Service to be Held April 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-755ae711-00001724calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, April 02, 2025 11:00 AM - 1:00 PM. In remembrance of the individuals we lost this past year, the Pillars of Rensselaer invite all members of the Rensselaer community, including alumni and friends, to attend this year’s Faculty and Staff Memorial Service, which will be held at the Chapel + Cultural Center, located at 2125 Burdett Avenue, Troy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0194-755ae711-00001724calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Math Colloquium: Yunan Yang presents “Transport- and Measure-Theoretic Approaches for Dynamical System Modeling” | April 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-4306678a-000024a8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 2, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM Green Building Rm. 10- This Mathematical Sciences Colloquium will feature a presentation titled “Transport- and Measure-Theoretic Approaches for Dynamical System Modeling” by Dr. Yunan Yang, Assistant Professor in the Department of Mathematics at Cornell University.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-4306678a-000024a8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Sharing Success: Faculty Share Their Experience as Innovative Pedagogy Fellows | April 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-a9910b7f-00007d78calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 2, 2025 11:45 AM - 1:45 PM - Come learn how your colleagues successfully used new teaching approaches to engage students and increase their learning. Nine faculty who were selected as Innovative Pedagogy Fellows in 2024 have been invited to share what they did and how they did it in a special 2-part Lunch and Learn series in April. This series is generously sponsored by the Lally School of Management and Technology. Session 1, April 2, will feature Fellows who use the flipped classroom approach.Where:Sage 4101Sage 4203&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:32:16 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-a9910b7f-00007d78calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
