<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>2025-26 Student Advisory Council (SAC) - Application deadline September 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d825c46-00002640calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, September 24, 2025 8:00 AM - 7:00 PM - Applications are now open for the 2025–26 Student Advisory Council (SAC)! Hosted by Vice Provosts Dr. Rob Hradsky and Dr. Matt Oehlschlaeger, the SAC connects students with campus leadership to shape academics, student life, and RPI culture. Meetings are biweekly on Fridays, 12–1:30 PM. Apply by Sept. 24 to make your voice heard and create positive change. Questions? Contact Quadir “Q” Webster at webstq@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-4d825c46-00002640calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>DOSO Day 9/25</title><link>https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/doso-day-925</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come meet the Dean of Students Office Staff while enjoying some activities, snack foods, and ice cream for the first 100 guests! This event is open to the RPI student body on Thursday, 9/25 from 2-4pm located at Off-Campus Commons (1525 15th street). We look forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/doso-day-925</guid></item><item><title>NEW: Burgers by the Bridge – Thursday Nights Just Got Better!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/new-burgers-bridge-thursday-nights-just-got-better</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Craving something grill-worthy? Swing by Burgers by the Bridge at Russell Sage Dining Hall every Thursday night at Dinner for a stacked burger special that’ll hit the spot.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/new-burgers-bridge-thursday-nights-just-got-better</guid></item><item><title>Order of the Engineer Registration | Sept. 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-76cfe084-00002722calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 24, 2025 9:00 AM - 4:00 PM - The Order of the Engineer is open to all senior and graduate engineering students. The Order is a national organization that fosters a spirit of pride and responsibility in the engineering profession. The ceremony will be held October 15th at 6:00 PM. You must attend to be inducted and receive your ring. Registration and sizing ends Friday, September 26th. To register: https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSey…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-76cfe084-00002722calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Closure of Sage Avenue Roadway and Sidewalk Beginning September 22</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/closure-sage-avenue-roadway-and-sidewalk-beginning-september-22</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Beginning Monday, September 22, 2025, RPI Facilities Management will begin a project to replace leaking steam pipes along the north sidewalk in front of E Dorm and across the roadway at the Sage Avenue campus entrance. As a result, the north sidewalk and entrance to the academic campus off Sage Avenue will be closed and will remain closed for approximately five to six weeks. Additionally, Sage Avenue will be closed between the crosswalk at Troy Building and the crosswalk on the east side of E…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/closure-sage-avenue-roadway-and-sidewalk-beginning-september-22</guid></item><item><title>These Hands Don’t Haze! | Sept. 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-4f12577a-0000276ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 26, 2025 10:00 AM - 6:00 PM - For National Hazing Prevention Week, join various student leaders from across campus to take the anti-hazing pledge! When you sign the pledge, you’ll have the opportunity to add to our “These Hands Don’t Haze” mural. We’ll also have trivia, giveaways, and more! Stop by anytime between 10 a.m. - 6 p.m. outside of the Russell Sage Dining Hall to participate.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-4f12577a-0000276ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Cable Television Outage in Specific Campus Buildings</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the campus about an issue affecting CATV services in several buildings: Sage, Troy, Ricketts, and 87Gym. Our service provider has identify the issue–an underground cable–and will implement repairs as soon as possible. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause and appreciate patience as we work toward a resolution. New information will be provided as soon as it becomes available. Thank you for your understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar – “Assigning Learning in Percipio: A Guide for Supervisors”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-assigning-learning-percipio</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This course provides supervisors with a step-by-step overview of how to assign learning content to employees using Percipio. You’ll learn how to search for relevant courses, create and manage assignments, track completion, and support your team’s development goals. Designed to be quick and practical, this session equips you with the tools needed to guide your team’s learning journey effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-assigning-learning-percipio</guid></item><item><title>Faculty &amp; Staff Appreciation Lunch on September 24th</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-september-24th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We’re celebrating you! As a token of our appreciation, all faculty and staff are invited to enjoy lunch at Commons or Russell Sage Dining Halls for just $6 on September 24th!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-september-24th</guid></item></channel></rss>
