<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Apartment Hunting Workshop | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-b90c7a22-00005a5bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 26, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:00 PM - Red &amp;amp; White invites Juniors, Seniors, and Graduate Students to come learn about apartment hunting in a new city from local realtor Kareem Jandall! The event will be held on Wednesday, March 26th from 2-3pm in the Heffner Alumni House Great Hall Kareem is the President for the Women’s Council of Realtors, owns her own real estate business, and is a Senior Real Estate Specialist.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-b90c7a22-00005a5bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Lift &amp; Learn | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-3d1757a2-00001198calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, March 26, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:30 PM at the Mueller Center. One hour of lift coaching from the Assistant Strength &amp;amp; Conditioning Coach, followed by 30 minutes of nutrition information on proper fueling for workouts. No experience necessary! Free and open to everyone with all equipment provided. Use the link to register today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-3d1757a2-00001198calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Review the Master of Engineering in Mechanical Engineering with Rensselaer at Work | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-67049e72-00004fe9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, March 26, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work faculty on a 30-minute information session covering Rensselaer’s online, project-based Master of Engineering program in Mechanical Engineering. Experienced engineers are asked to take on larger and more complex tasks as they progress in their careers, and this program provides the necessary breadth and depth, no matter where one’s career takes them. &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MECLMARCH26"&gt;Please register&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-67049e72-00004fe9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Lally Undergraduate Open Forum | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-428d5859-000032edcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 26, 2025 1:00 PM - 3:00 PM in the CBIS Auditorium - Join Dean Liad Wagman, Lally faculty, and Lally leadership at the Lally Undergraduate Open Forum! Learn about their vision for Lally’s future, and submit your questions for the Live Q&amp;amp;A at the link below. Refreshments and reception to follow.Submit questions here: &lt;a class="uri" href="https://forms.gle/i2A1kzP8msVMw4X77"&gt;https://forms.gle/i2A1kzP8msVMw4X77&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-428d5859-000032edcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Civic Engagement Opportunity: CCPD and Sidewalk Warriors, Troy, NY | April 3</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/civic-engagement-opportunity-ccpd-and-sidewalk-warriors-troy-ny-april-3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Center for Career and Professional Development (CCPD) is excited to extend an invitation to all students who are passionate about making a positive impact in our community. On Thursday, April 3, 2025, beginning at 4:30 PM, the CCPD and participating students will be volunteering with Sidewalk Warriors in Troy, New York. See Handshake for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/civic-engagement-opportunity-ccpd-and-sidewalk-warriors-troy-ny-april-3</guid></item><item><title>Collegiate Store Offering 20% - 50% Off During Spring Art Sale</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rensselaer-collegiate-store/01/08/2025/spring-art-sale-20-50</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer Collegiate Store is currently hosting its Spring 2025 Art Sale from now through Saturday, June 28, 2025, with sale items available both in-store and online. While supplies last, customers can save 20% off select art supplies, 40% off select brushes, and 50% off paper and canvas! Note that this sale excludes clearance items, art kits, metals, and jewelry, and cannot be combined with other coupons or discounts.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rensselaer-collegiate-store/01/08/2025/spring-art-sale-20-50</guid></item><item><title>2025 ECAC Esports Spring Showdown | April 4–6</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2025/2025-ecac-spring-showdown</link><description>&lt;p&gt;April 4–6, 2025 | The ECAC Esports Spring Showdown will bring collegiate gaming teams from around the country to the university’s Curtis R. Priem Experimental and Performing Arts Center. The teams will compete in several esports titles, including Rocket League and Overwatch. Bringing in over 125 schools and 800 student teams, the event is reportedly expected to draw in thousands of participants and spectators to Troy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2025/2025-ecac-spring-showdown</guid></item><item><title>Marx, Mars, and Hyrule: Imagining Planetary Futures: Christian P. Haines to Speak on March 28</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/marx-mars-and-hyrule-imagining-planetary-futures-christian-p-haines</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, March 28, 4:30 - 6:00 PM, SAGE 3303: What do Marxism, science fiction, and video games have in common? They are all efforts to imagine what it’s like to live in complex planetary ecosystems. In this lecture, Christian P. Haines (Assoc. Prof. of English, Penn State) critically examines fantasies of terraforming as alibis for socioeconomic inequality and political injustice.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/marx-mars-and-hyrule-imagining-planetary-futures-christian-p-haines</guid></item><item><title>Joint ECSE-Phyics Seminar: 100 years of Field Effect Transistor: Industrial Face of Nanotechnology | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-5c600e68-00007d5ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 26, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Joint ECSE-Physics Seminar: Professor Michael S. Shur, Patricia W. and C. Sheldon Roberts Professor of Solid State Electronics, Electrical, Computer, and Systems Engineering. Title: “100 years of Field Effect Transistor: Industrial Face of Nanotechnology”&lt;a href="https://ecse.rpi.edu/lectures/2025/joint-ecse-phyics-seminar-100-years-field-effect-transistor-industrial-face"&gt;More information&lt;/a&gt;Darrin Communications Center (DCC) 324&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-5c600e68-00007d5ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>19 New Employees Join RPI in February!</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/19-new-employees-join-rpi-february</link><description>&lt;p&gt;19 new employees joined RPI in February! Let’s give them a warm welcome as they begin their journey at RPI!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/19-new-employees-join-rpi-february</guid></item><item><title>03/27/2025 - 7am to 8am ET- DotCIO to perform maintenance on VPN (vpn.net.rpi.edu)</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/03272025-7am-8am-et-dotcio-perform-maintenance-vpn-vpnnetrpiedu</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All members of the campus community should note that VPN connections to vpn.net.rpi.edu will experience a brief outage between 7:00 a.m. and 8:00 a.m. ET on Thursday, March 27, due to required network maintenance. All VPN connections to vpn.net.rpi.edu will be interrupted during this outage. All other VPN server addresses and on-campus connectivity will not be impacted. If you have any questions about this maintenance, please submit a Support Request via https://itssc.rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/03272025-7am-8am-et-dotcio-perform-maintenance-vpn-vpnnetrpiedu</guid></item><item><title>Fire Evacuation Drills to be Conducted during March and April</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/fire-evacuation-drills-be-conducted-during-march-and-april-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fire evacuation drills will be conducted in all campus buildings during March and April. These unannounced drills are required by New York State Fire Code and provide an opportunity for building occupants to practice evacuation procedures.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/fire-evacuation-drills-be-conducted-during-march-and-april-0</guid></item><item><title>Transcending Gender exhibit at Folsom Library | Through April 1</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-86bac793-00003fe6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, March 12, 2025 - Tue , April 1, 2025 (all day) - This exhibit examines ways that gender identity, gender expression, and sexual orientation intersect. Materials provided by the Stonewall National Museum, Archives, and Library with the generous support of Jason Hagopian ’91, ’92, the RAA, and Folsom Library staff. Sponsored by the LGBTQ+ Task Force.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-86bac793-00003fe6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MSE Seminar: Dr. Kenneth Burch | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-8662e683-00002436calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 26, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM Where: Low 4050 - Quantum Materials: a new paradigm for sensing Kenneth Burch Chair and Professor of Physics Boston College&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-8662e683-00002436calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Webex Maintenance Planned for Wednesday March 26th</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-maintenance-planned-wednesday-march-26th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Webex platform will undergo planned maintenance between 10pm March 26th and 3am March 27th. During this time, there may be intermittent issues requiring users to rejoin or restart meetings. It is highly recommended to reschedule any meetings planned during this time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-maintenance-planned-wednesday-march-26th</guid></item><item><title>RAF Guide to Sponsored Programs Update</title><link>https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/raf-guide-sponsored-programs-update</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RAF has updated the RPI Guide to Sponsored Programs to reflect recommendations resulting from an recent internal audit. Updates were made to Part II, Section 2.2 Research Involving Human Subjects, Animals, and Recombinant DNA and Part IV Proposal Approval Process, to clarify that awards will not be set up until all required campus approvals are received. While this Guide contains helpful guidance, nothing within the Guide to Sponsored Programs should be interpreted as formal institute policy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/raf-guide-sponsored-programs-update</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Colloquia: Clayton Thomas - Explaining Matching Mechanisms to Participants | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-aa5c0ab8-00001a1bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, March 26, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Clayton Thomas is a postdoctoral researcher in the Economics and Computation group at Microsoft Research, New England. His work focuses on theoretical computer science and economic design: striving to build systems that perform well under strategic incentives. He completed his PhD in the computer science theory group at Princeton University, where he was awarded the Wallace Memorial Fellowship in Engineering and a Siebel Scholar award.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-aa5c0ab8-00001a1bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>How Many Student Support Resources Are You Using?</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/how-many-student-support-resources-are-you-using</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you explored our comprehensive advising model? Have you taken full advantage of the Center for Career and Professional Development and the Center for Global Communication + Design? What about I-PERSIST and the Student Success Labs? Did you know our median course evaluation for overall instructor rating is above 4/5? There’s so much more to discover! Dive into Standard 3 of RPI’s Self-Study for Middle States Accreditation, a team led by Dr. Sibel Adali and Dr. Tracy Sullivan.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/how-many-student-support-resources-are-you-using</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents! Dr. Theresa Jean Tanenbaum: Transformative Play Lab | March 26 (Virtual Event)</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-dr-theresa-jean-tanenbaum-transformative-play-lab-virtual-event</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this talk, Dr. Theresa Jean Tanenbaum theorizes an emancipatory design practice intended to restore agency and power to those of us who have suffered at the hands of the oppressive normative social order (which is to say, most of us). She illustrates this with a vulnerable autoethnographic discussion of her own experiences of gender transition, and with examples from larp, tabletop roleplaying games, and popular media. Join virtually on 3/26 at 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-dr-theresa-jean-tanenbaum-transformative-play-lab-virtual-event</guid></item><item><title>Information Session for 2025 Project RFP: IBM-RPI Future of Computing Research Collaboration (FCRC) Quantum Computing Track | March 28</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/information-session-2025-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research-collaboration-fcrc</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on March 28th, 2-3pm for the Info Session concerning the Request for Joint RPI/IBM Research Proposals in the Quantum Computing Track, a collaborative research initiative between RPI and IBM (FCRC) to drive world class innovation and fundamental advances in artificial intelligence algorithm, AI hardware software co-design, Semiconductor Technology and Quantum Computing for the benefit of society. The full RFP is available via the IDEA Intranet. REGISTER to participate at idea.rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/information-session-2025-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research-collaboration-fcrc</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff In Person Workshop - Reviewing Supported Polling Tools On Campus for Courses or Meetings</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-c8f3f556-00002a88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, April 7, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - In this workshop we will take time to look at a couple polling software tools that are available and supported on campus and discuss the differences. The tools we will be discussing include iClicker and Slido. We will also take a quick look at the free version of Kahoot! (not supported on campus with license but fun!). Please register for this workshop by April 4th as space is limited. Please look in the See section for the registration link and more details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-c8f3f556-00002a88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Call for Faculty Reflective Pedagogy Fellows – Applications due April 11th</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/call-faculty-reflective-pedagogy-fellows-applications-due-april-11th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Inquiry-based learning and creativity are key elements toward creating engaged learning. The Gameful and Immersive Learning Teams invite interested faculty to apply to redesign one of their courses (or a course element). Following the successful spring 2024 Innovative Pedagogy Fellows initiative, the Office of Undergraduate Education is capitalizing on this momentum by funding a professional development opportunity for a new cohort of fellows in 2025, the Reflective Pedagogy Fellows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/call-faculty-reflective-pedagogy-fellows-applications-due-april-11th</guid></item></channel></rss>
