<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:31:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Gateway Shuttle for Winter Break Sign Ups</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/gateway-shuttle-winter-break-sign-ups</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Department of Parking and Transportation will again offer Gateway shuttle service to the Albany International Airport, Albany Bus Terminal, and Amtrak Train Station for Winter Break. Shuttles depart from the RPI Student Union horseshoe via CDTA bus and RPI Transportation. Deadline to sign up is December 17th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:31:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/gateway-shuttle-winter-break-sign-ups</guid></item><item><title>Join us: Step inside a world of detritus with work-in-progress RAFT by Yanira Castro</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2025/work-progress-raft</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Thursday / December 18, 2025 at 2:00 pm How do we build a world from the detritus of a faltering society? How are we responsive to the environment, people, and objects around us? This in-progress installation from artist Yanira Castro and her team—including RPI arts alum Stephan Moore—invites you to enter and effect a rumbling, buoyant, weather-like microcosm constructed of shipping pallets, clothing bundles, tarps, and emergency paraphernalia.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:31:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2025/work-progress-raft</guid></item><item><title>JEC Walkway</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/jec-walkway</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The JEC Walkway will be entering a construction slowdown during the winter months and will resume as more temperate seasonal conditions return. In the interim, a temporary walkway providing access to the Greene Building, 2nd Floor ADA side entrance has been installed and will open to foot traffic on December 17, 2025. Please note that this temporary walkway only provides access to the Greene Building. The ramp section on the west side remains closed and under construction. Additionally, in…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:31:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/jec-walkway</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Spring 2026 Syllabus Available - Complete by January 26, 2026</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-spring-2026-syllabus-available-complete-january-26-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The HelioCampus syllabus module is now available for faculty to access for the spring. Based on the requirements from the Provost’s office, faculty should have their syllabi published in HelioCampus by January 26, 2026. HelioCampus will publish all syllabi automatically on February 2, 2026. Please review post to register for one of the two training sessions that will be offered in January 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:31:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-spring-2026-syllabus-available-complete-january-26-2026</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Getting the Most Out of AI with Percipio”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-getting-most-out-ai-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;“Getting the Most Out of AI with Percipio” This workshop introduces you to Percipio’s AI Chat, AI Skill Benchmarks, and interactive AI scenarios. You’ll learn how to navigate AI Chat to explore ideas, ask questions, and get quick support. You’ll also be shown how to access and complete AI Skill Benchmarks and use guided scenarios to practice applying Percipio’s AI features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:31:19 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-getting-most-out-ai-0</guid></item></channel></rss>
