<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Fall 2024 SoE Midterm Student Course Evaluations Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-4400b0b6-00003999calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 10, 2024 (all day) - School of Engineering (SoE) midterm course evaluations are now open for the Fall 2024 semester. Your feedback is very important to the Institute and the school, so please complete the SoE midterm evaluation surveys for all your courses! Evaluations will be available through Wednesday, October 23, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-4400b0b6-00003999calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ITWS Co-Terminal Program Info Sessions Continue October 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-24574619-00007f98calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 22, 2024 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Attend this session to learn about the Information Technology &amp;amp; Web Science co-terminal program as Dr. Brian Callahan discusses program requirements, the application process, and upcoming deadlines, and also answers questions. This info session is geared toward first- and second-semester seniors, but all students are welcome to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-24574619-00007f98calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>The McKinney Student Writing Contest Is Now Open!</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-mckinney-writing-contest-open</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2025 McKinney Writing Contest is open, and both undergraduate and graduate students are invited to &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/mckinney-writing-contest/submission"&gt;submit&lt;/a&gt; entries in a wide range of categories to win cash prizes! Entries are due by midnight on March 11, 2025. Please see the &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/mckinney"&gt;McKinney Writing Contest page&lt;/a&gt; for more information, or &lt;a href="mailto:McKinney@rpi.edu"&gt;email the contest committee&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-mckinney-writing-contest-open</guid></item><item><title>Check Out the Nature Scavenger Hunt!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9154daf9-000039e9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 18, 2024 12:00 AM - Celebrate the last day of Outdoor Week by joining Outdoor Programming in a campus-wide nature scavenger hunt! Please &lt;a href="mailto:weinew2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Will Weinert&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9154daf9-000039e9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Free Seasonal Flu Shot Clinic Being Held for Students October 17</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/free-seasonal-flu-shot-clinic-students-oct-17</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting at 10:00 a.m. on Thursday, October 17, the Student Health Center will be in the Rensselaer Union giving free flu shots to students with their Rensselaer student ID. No appointment is necessary, but shots will only be available while supplies last, so be sure to get your shot…don’t let the flu get you!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/free-seasonal-flu-shot-clinic-students-oct-17</guid></item><item><title>Blood Drive Being Held Today, October 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-91d3c157-00002197calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 17, 2024 10:00 AM - 5:00 PM - Stop by Mother’s, located on the first floor of the Rensselaer Union, to donate blood and help give the gift of life!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-91d3c157-00002197calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>October is Cybersecurity Awareness Month!</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/october-cybersecurity-awareness-month</link><description>&lt;p&gt;To help all members of the campus community enhance their cybersecurity knowledge, brush up on best practices and stay informed about the latest campus cybersecurity threats, DotCIO has worked with Rensselaer’s Division of Human Resources to curate a number of training resources in Percipio.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/october-cybersecurity-awareness-month</guid></item><item><title>Capital Region AI Plus Symposium Scheduled for October 22</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/capital-region-ai-plus-symposium</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/capital-region-ai-plus-symposium-tickets-920877237607?aff=odcleoeventsincollection"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to join the Future of Computing Institute at Rensselaer on October 22 for the Capital Region AI Plus Symposium, a joint effort by RPI and UAlbany that will bring together thought leaders, innovators, and professionals from across the Capital Region and New York State to discuss the impact and future of AI.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/capital-region-ai-plus-symposium</guid></item><item><title>Family Weekend Concert Slated for October 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-6d61737b-00000cf4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, October 19, 2024 7:00 PM - 8:30 PM - The program for this year’s Family Weekend Concert includes festive performances by Rensselaer’s Orchestra, Concert Choir, and Wind Symphony, and features works by Berlioz, Brahms, Copland, Respighi, and Verdi. In addition, Rensselaer Student Concerto Competition-winner Rachael Marseglia will perform the third movement from Mozart’s Flute Concerto No. 1 in G Major.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-6d61737b-00000cf4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC Premieres Two Commissions for Fall 2024</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/news/2024/empac-premieres-two-commissions-fall-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;EMPAC and its curatorial program will celebrate the American premiere of two commissions during the Center’s 16th fall season. On October 25, filmmaker Bassem Saad and writer Sanja Grozdanić will present their jointly-authored performance for stage Permanent Trespass (Beirut of the Balkans &amp;amp; the American Century). On November 8, in a new performance and video installation, Marina Rosenfeld will premiere μ (mu), following its first presentation in the 15th Gwangju Biennale.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/news/2024/empac-premieres-two-commissions-fall-2024</guid></item><item><title>RPI Economics Professor Participates in Big Tech-AI Symposium</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/10/10/rpi-economics-professor-participates-big-tech-ai-symposium</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Vivek Ghosal, Ph.D., Virginia and Lloyd W. Rittenhouse Professor and Head of Rensselaer’s Economics department, was an invited participant in ProMarket’s Big Tech-AI Investment Symposium. The event brought together prominent scholars and researchers from the fields of economics, law, and information science to discuss whether government intervention into investment by various technology giants would be likely to hamper competition and development among artificial intelligence startups.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/10/10/rpi-economics-professor-participates-big-tech-ai-symposium</guid></item><item><title>Harnessing Vibrations: RPI-Engineered Material Generates Electricity from Unexpected Source</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/10/15/harnessing-vibrations-rpi-engineered-material-generates-electricity-unexpected-source</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine tires that charge a vehicle as it drives, streetlights powered by the rumble of traffic, or skyscrapers that generate electricity as the buildings naturally sway and shudder. Thanks to Rensselaer researchers who are developing environmentally friendly materials that produce electricity when compressed or exposed to vibrations, these energy innovations could be possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/10/15/harnessing-vibrations-rpi-engineered-material-generates-electricity-unexpected-source</guid></item><item><title>“Responsible AI: Moving Principles to Practice” Topid of October 18 Discussion</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-914da4b7-00006adfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 18, 2024 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - One of the first movers in Responsible AI and an expert in AI Ethics and production innovation, Olivia Gambelin will break down what it means to use ethics and values as a modern-day decision-making tool in the design and development of AI. She will also discuss how ethics can be used to identify risks and establish safeguards in the development of AI, and discover how to use ethics-by-design methods to stimulate AI innovation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-914da4b7-00006adfcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
