<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer Dining Student Culinary Council Meeting</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-dining-student-culinary-council-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on Wednesday, February 25th at 3:30 PM in Union Room 3418 for the upcoming Rensselaer Dining Student Culinary Council meeting!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-dining-student-culinary-council-meeting</guid></item><item><title>Spring 2026 School of Engineering Midterm Student Course Evaluations Now Open</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-718fde35-00001bb8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 25, 2026 (all day) - Spring 2026 School of Engineering (SoE) Midterm course evaluations are now open. Your feedback is very important to the Institute and the school, so please complete the SoE midterm evaluation surveys for all your courses! Evaluations will be available through Friday, March 13, 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-718fde35-00001bb8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>2026 Spring Interfaith Lecture</title><link>https://studentexperience.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-spring-interfaith-lecture</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for a meaningful evening of insight and conversation as Rabbi Reena Judd shares reflections on love, family, and belonging. Rabbi Judd will read selections from her book of contemporary midrashim, offering thoughtful perspectives rooted in tradition and resonant with modern life.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studentexperience.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-spring-interfaith-lecture</guid></item><item><title>Webinar Friday February 27: RPI Digital Asset Management (DAM) System</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-february-27-rpi-digital-asset-management-dam-system</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Jim Evans, Director of MultiMedia Services, on Friday February 27 from 11am to 12pm, for a live webinar introducing Rensselaer’s Digital Asset Management System. Discover how to access campus‑wide photography, multimedia files, and institutional assets—all in one place. Register now: https://rensselaer.webex.com/webappng/sites/rensselaer/webinar/webinarSeries/register/783d951c6ab8482e9198a7bd6075a700&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-february-27-rpi-digital-asset-management-dam-system</guid></item><item><title>Accepted Student Celebrations – Undergraduate Admissions</title><link>https://undergrad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/accepted-student-celebrations-undergraduate-admissions</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Admissions will host two Accepted Student Celebrations this spring - Saturday, March 21 and Saturday, April 11. We look forward to celebrating with admitted students and their families and highlighting how an RPI education will prepare them to change the world. If you or a campus organization you are part of would like to volunteer during the event, please contact Arianna Livshits, Senior Event Planner, at paluma3@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/accepted-student-celebrations-undergraduate-admissions</guid></item><item><title>RPI at Work Information Session on February 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-c277ee9c-000036edcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, February 27, 2026 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - RPI at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., will be reviewing the online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates. Expect to hear details about how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment. Please RSVP if you plan to attend and learn more about RPI at Work.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-c277ee9c-000036edcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Spring Break 2026 Hours – Residential and Retail Dining</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-break-2026-hours-residential-and-retail-dining</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Spring Break is almost here! Residential Dining Halls (BARH, Blitman, Commons, and Russell Sage) will be closed February 28th, 2026 - March 7th, 2026. Retail Hours can be found in the link above. Normal residential and retail dining hours of operations will resume on March 9th, 2026. Have a safe and relaxing Spring Break!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-break-2026-hours-residential-and-retail-dining</guid></item><item><title>Systems Engineering &amp; Technology Management Review with RPI at Work</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-76b335c7-00006303calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, March 5, 2026 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - This 30-minute information session is hosted by Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., and will focus on RPI’s Systems Engineering &amp;amp; Technology Management graduate degree. The degree is digitally delivered, flexible, and project-based to prepare decision-makers with broader and deeper capabilities in leading dynamic organizations. The session will highlight program details and how you can select graduate certificates relevant to your work to complete…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9c22e398-019c-76b335c7-00006303calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Upcoming closures in Shuttle services</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/upcoming-shuttle-closure-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friendly reminder that shuttles do not operate on holidays or during University closures. In observance of Spring Break (February 28–March 7), shuttles will not be running. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/upcoming-shuttle-closure-0</guid></item><item><title>McKinney Contest Award Ceremony to be held April 9</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-contest-award-ceremony</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2026 Annual McKinney Reading Series and Student Awards Ceremony will take place on Thursday, April 9, 2026, from 7:00–9:00 p.m. at the Heffner Alumni House. The event will feature Hisham Matar, the Pulitzer Prize–winning author of three novels and two memoirs. The evening will include the announcement of the McKinney Student Writing Contest winners, a literary reading, and an audience Q&amp;amp;A, followed by a book signing. Books will be available for purchase at the event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-contest-award-ceremony</guid></item><item><title>Small Group Tutoring Options at the Success Center</title><link>https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/tutoring-appointment-options</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that you can easily book online a small group tutoring session in many of RPI’s upper-level courses? Check out the fantastic small group tutoring sessions being offered at the Success Center!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/tutoring-appointment-options</guid></item><item><title>Information Security - Vote on Top 3 AI Phish Coach Names:</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/information-security-vote-top-3-ai-phish-coach-names</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you everyone for sending proposed names for our new AI Phishing Coach! After team vote, we have narrowed our selection down to the top three choices: bAIt and tackle, Phishing Net, and PhishStick. Please click above link to vote for your favorite name! Voting will close on Monday, March 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/information-security-vote-top-3-ai-phish-coach-names</guid></item></channel></rss>
