<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Gateway Shuttle for Thanksgiving Break</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/updated-gateway-shuttle-thanksgiving-break</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Department of Parking and Transportation will again offer Gateway shuttle service to the Albany International Airport, Albany Bus Terminal, and Amtrak Train Station for Thanksgiving break. Shuttles depart from the RPI Student Union horseshoe via CDTA bus. To reserve a seat, email hosgob@rpi.edu or call 518-276-6616 by Wednesday, November 19. Please be sure to include your full name, RIN and which departure date and time you would like to sign up for.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/updated-gateway-shuttle-thanksgiving-break</guid></item><item><title>Econ Club Discussion: Affordable Health Coverage at a Crossroads? | Nov. 19</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/affordable-health-coverage-crossroads</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the Econ Club to learn about and discuss how health care subsidies caused a record-breaking US government shutdown in Sage 3205 at 5pm on 11/19.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/affordable-health-coverage-crossroads</guid></item><item><title>ASCE Chapter meeting | Nov. 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-f7b12254-00006133calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 20, 2025 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - Join fellow students and Don Adams from Creighton Manning before heading home for the holiday. Mr. Adams will discuss his company’s Adirondack Rail Project. This project transformed a 34-mile railroad corridor into a multi-use trail designed for pedestrians, bicyclists, snowmobilers, and cross-country skiers. Refreshments will be served.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-f7b12254-00006133calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>NYS Taxation &amp; Finance Tabling | Nov. 18</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/nys-taxation-and-finance-tabling</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The New York State Department of Taxation and Finance will be in the RPI Student Union on Tuesday, November 18th from 11:00am – 2:00pm. Stop by to learn more about the career opportunities available, including the Data Analyst position and other potential openings across the department. This is a great opportunity to meet with a representative, ask questions, and gain insight into the department’s career paths, organizational culture, and the important work they do serving New York State.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/nys-taxation-and-finance-tabling</guid></item><item><title>Title IX and Beyond: Understand Your Rights</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/title-ix-and-beyond-understand-your-rights</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for Title IX and Beyond, an informational session focused on understanding your rights, navigating personal and professional boundaries, and learning about reporting pathways at RPI and in the workplace. The event will be held on Tuesday, November 18, at 4 p.m. in the Bruggeman Room, CBIS, with Jackie McPhillips Balcerak and Elizabeth Brown-Goyette. All students, faculty, and staff are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/title-ix-and-beyond-understand-your-rights</guid></item><item><title>Tech The Halls (11/17-11/22) at Collegiate Store</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/tech-halls-1117-1122-collegiate-store</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s time to Tech The Halls! Select technology items are on sale in-store and online from Monday, Nov 17 until Saturday, Nov 22. Customers will get: 5% off Apple M5 MacBook Pro 14-inch and M5 iPad Pro models, 10% off Apple M3 and M4 models - MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, iMac, iPad Pro and iPad Air, and 25% off select OnHand and Belkin accessories. There will also be two Accessory One-Day Flash Sales on 11/18 and 11/20. Some exclusions may apply. See store for details. Shop at rensselaerstore.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/tech-halls-1117-1122-collegiate-store</guid></item><item><title>Early Black Friday Sale (11/17-11/21) at Collegiate Store</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/early-black-friday-sale-1117-1121-collegiate-store</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Early Black Friday Sale runs from Monday, Nov 17 until Friday, Nov 21 at the Rensselaer Collegiate Store. Available both In-store and Online (rensselaerstore.com), enjoy up to 25% Off select apparel brands including Campus United, Colosseum, Concept Sports, Nike, Zephyr and ZooZatz. Online orders $75+ get free shipping. Some restrictions may apply. See store for details. We are located on the Lower Level of the Rensselaer Student Union. Open from 10am-6pm, Mon - Fri and 11am-3pm on Sat.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/early-black-friday-sale-1117-1121-collegiate-store</guid></item><item><title>Waive The Fee on Select Visa and Mastercard $50 &amp; $100 Gift Cards</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/waive-fee-select-visa-mastercard-50-100-gift-cards</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Customers can purchase $50 and $100 Visa or Mastercard Blackhawk gift cards with no activation fee! Running from Monday, November 15th until Monday, December 1st. This deal is exclusive to in-store shoppers only. See store for additional details. &lt;a href="https://rensselaerstore.com/"&gt;rensselaerstore.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/waive-fee-select-visa-mastercard-50-100-gift-cards</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Colloquia -: James Riley Inventor of VibroGuide a tactical guidance for blind athletes | Nov. 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-9364df55-0000482acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 20, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:00 PM - James Riley is the inventor of VibroGuide, a tactical guidance for blind athletes. VibroGuide seeks to enhance guide/blind athlete navigation by mixing Bluetooth Direction Finding and tactile technologies. We would like to demonstrate how it provides a wireless and near-silent connection between guide and blind athlete with a tactile interface to the torso. We would invite sharing of ideas on mixing Soundscape navigation with a similar…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-9364df55-0000482acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Tech The Halls Flash Sale - AirPods 4 with ANC $30 Off</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/tech-halls-flash-sale-airpods-4-anc-30</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, November 18th, 2025 - enjoy $30 off Apple AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation. This one day flash sale is while supplies last In Store. The Rensselaer Collegiate Store is located on the Lower Level of the Rensselaer Student Union and we are open from 10am-6pm, Monday - Friday. Call 518-276-6555 for more details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/tech-halls-flash-sale-airpods-4-anc-30</guid></item><item><title>Annual RPI United Way Thanksgiving Feast | Nov. 20 (Reservations Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-c47d5b63-000039b3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 20, 2025 11:30 AM - 2:00 PM - Members of the campus community are welcome to come to the RSDH to enjoy a Thanksgiving feast featuring roast turkey, ham, and all the traditional holiday trimmings for still $15! Vegan and gluten-free options will also be available. Reservations are required; take-out meals will also be available upon request. No walk-ins will be accepted. Cash, check, or departmental charge must be received by Wednesday, November 12. We will have raffle…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-c47d5b63-000039b3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO - reminder Microsoft has ended support for Windows 10</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-reminder-microsoft-has-ended-support-windows-10</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Windows 10 support ended on October 14th, 2025. At this time Windows 10 systems are no longer eligible for support including important security patches. Without appropriate mitigation, Windows 10 systems are non-compliant with multiple RPI security policies. Please click in for additional information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-reminder-microsoft-has-ended-support-windows-10</guid></item><item><title>Presence, Play, and Collective Dreaming: Embodied Social Practice as Research with Jane Rigler</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/presence-play-and-collective-dreaming-embodied-social-practice-research-jane-rigler</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This interactive experience explores how engaged social practice can serve as a methodology for collective research and restorative community building. Through facilitated invitation, inspired by the work of Pauline Oliveros (musician, humanitarian, and founder of Deep Listening), participants explore presence and play, cultivating capacity for orientation to what is emerging in this moment. Join at EMPAC Studio Beta from 5-7pm on 11/19.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/presence-play-and-collective-dreaming-embodied-social-practice-research-jane-rigler</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity Confidential Consultation (In Person) | Nov. 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-76c898c7-00002373calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 20, 2025 8:00 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits. To schedule an appointment, call 1-800-642-7131, Monday through Friday, 8:00 am to midnight, or online at https://nb.fidelity.com/public/nbpreloginnav/rpi/microsite/#/tem/meet-with-us&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-76c898c7-00002373calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop- Book Discussion-“Powered by Me: From Burned Out to Fully Charged at Work and in Life” – Virtual Class | Nov. 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-bfbe840a-000058cecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 20, 2025 9:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Join an instructor-led discussion of Powered by Me: From Burned Out to Fully Charged at Work and in Life by Neha Sangwan (Available in Percipio). Burnout is an energy crisis across five key dimensions—physical, mental, emotional, social, and spiritual. Together, we’ll explore how chronic stress depletes our energy, erodes our relationships, and diminishes our sense of purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-bfbe840a-000058cecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
