<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>2026 Silicon Valley Career Immersion Trip- Applications Open Now!</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-silicon-valley-career-immersion-trip-applications-open-now</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Ready to see where engineering and innovation meet? RPI’s School of Engineering and Center for Career &amp;amp; Professional Development invite applications for the 2026 Silicon Valley Career Immersion Trip, a five-day experience exploring the tech capital of the world. Join a select group of students to: · Explore world-class innovators like Apple, Google, Microsoft, and PayPal (among others) through site visits and alumni events. · Connect with RPI alumni shaping the future of technology. · Gain…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-silicon-valley-career-immersion-trip-applications-open-now</guid></item><item><title>Want to change the world? Study the Earth! | Nov. 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-4ba3aa28-0000758ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 5, 2025 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - On Wed, Nov 5, at 6 pm in JRSC 3W13, come learn about majors &amp;amp; minors in Environmental Science and Geology (field trips! hands-on research! diverse career paths!) and enjoy a slice of pizza! Meet faculty and students, ask questions, and find out how Earth and Environmental Sciences can complement your academic path.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-4ba3aa28-0000758ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; NYS Department of Design &amp; Construction Info Session | Nov. 6</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-nys-department-design-construction-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The New York State Department of Design &amp;amp; Construction will be hosting an info session with the CCPD on Thursday, November 6th from 5-6:30pm. Come learn about their entry-level opportunities, paid internship program, and the Civil Service Exam process. Learn more and register in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-nys-department-design-construction-info-session</guid></item><item><title>New Minor in Behavioral Data Science</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-behavioral-data-science</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new interdisciplinary minor is now available for students interested in the intersection between data science and human behavior. The Behavioral Data Science minor combines psychological science, statistics, and computational methods to analyze, predict, and influence human behavior across a wide range of real-world contexts. Minor requirements can be found in the RPI catalog. For questions, please contact the School of HASS advising hub at HASSinfo@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-behavioral-data-science</guid></item><item><title>Women’s Mentoring Program Thanksgiving Dinner | Nov. 13 (Register by Nov. 5)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-36af4747-000020dccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 13, 2025 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM - Join the Women’s Mentoring Program for our annual Thanksgiving Dinner on November 13, from 6pm to 8pm in the Sage Banquet Hall. Play games, meet fellow students, learn from our keynote speaker Dr. Azita Hirsa, and enjoy a delicious Thanksgiving meal! Undergraduate students, Graduate students, and faculty are all welcome to attend. Registration required. If you would like to attend, please fill out this form by November 5, 11:59 pm: https:/…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-36af4747-000020dccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Annual RPI United Way Thanksgiving Feast | Nov. 20 (Reservations Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-c47d5b63-000039b3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 20, 2025 11:30 AM - 2:00 PM - Members of the campus community are welcome to come to the RSDH to enjoy a Thanksgiving feast featuring roast turkey, ham, and all the traditional holiday trimmings for still $15! Vegan and gluten-free options will also be available. Reservations are required; take-out meals will also be available upon request. No walk-ins will be accepted. Cash, check, or departmental charge must be received by Wednesday, November 12. We will have raffle…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-c47d5b63-000039b3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Analytics, Machine Learning &amp; AI Review | Nov. 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-4a1c3e8b-000003cdcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 5, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join RPI at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., on a 30-minute information session highlighting the online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning &amp;amp; AI. Expect to learn how data can inform better decisions and review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please register if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-4a1c3e8b-000003cdcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Colloquia - Alexei Bulazel: Reflection on Hacking | Nov. 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-113e9b33-00000b7ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, November 7, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:00 PM - Alexei Bulazel currently serves as Special Assistant to the President &amp;amp; Senior Director for Cyber at the White House National Security Council (NSC), where he leads US government coordination of national security policy on cyber issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-113e9b33-00000b7ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Reflections on Waterways Symposium | Nov. 14</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-symposium-explores-art-environment-and-legacy-erie-canal</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The School of Humanities, Arts, and Social Sciences at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI), in collaboration with the Albany Symphony, the New York State Canal Corporation, and the New York Power Authority, will host a symposium titled Reflections on Waterways: Intersections of Arts, Culture, and the Environment in New York on Friday, November 14, 2025, from 9:30 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. in the Center For Biotechnology and Interdisciplinary Studies (CBIS) Auditorium at RPI. The symposium revisits…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-symposium-explores-art-environment-and-legacy-erie-canal</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar - “Shaping a Motivational Workplace”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-shaping-motivational</link><description>&lt;p&gt;People want to use their abilities, connect with others and guide their own efforts. Research has shown that people share these three psychological needs: Competence, Relatedness and Autonomy. In this seminar leaders learn to create an environment that inspires superior performance by helping employees satisfy these basic needs. Contact: Will Fahey 518-276-2318&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-shaping-motivational</guid></item><item><title>NSF GRFP Letters of Recommendation Due November 7th</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-06d9ac83-00001c8ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 23, 2025 (all day) - Letters of Recommendation for the NSF GRFP are due November 7th, BEFORE student application deadlines. All student applications should be reviewed by Betty Madigan to check for compliance with the NEW formatting requirements. Send statements at least a week before the deadline. Additionally, a faculty guide for writing letters of recommendation is available upon request. Requests for information and reviews should be sent to madige@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-06d9ac83-00001c8ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff In Person Workshop - Reviewing Supported Polling Tools On Campus for Courses or Meetings | Nov. 10</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-16995eff-00000f9dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 10, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - In this workshop we will take time to look at a couple polling software tools that are available and supported on campus and discuss the differences. The tools we will be discussing include iClicker and Slido. We will also take a quick look at the free version of Kahoot! (not supported on campus with license but fun!). Please register for this workshop by Nov. 6th as space is limited. Please look in the See section for the registration link…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-16995eff-00000f9dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Call for Survey Participants - First Generation Faculty &amp; Staff</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/call-survey-participants-first-generation-faculty-staff</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As we prepare for our National First-Generation Student week November 3-7, the Office of Inclusive Excellence invites you to complete this short survey if you are a faculty or staff member who identifies—or has identified—as a first-generation college graduate- (defined as someone whose parent(s)/guardian(s) did not complete a four-year college degree).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:34:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/call-survey-participants-first-generation-faculty-staff</guid></item></channel></rss>
