<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Welcome Back to Campus and the Spring Semester</title><link>https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/welcome-back-campus-and-spring-semester</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s time for your semesterly reminder to review the RPI Handbook of Student Rights &amp;amp; Responsibilities. We’ve updated the Student Handbook to clarify expectations, streamline processes, and strengthen support resources for this academic year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/welcome-back-campus-and-spring-semester</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Dining Survey Time</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-dining-survey-time</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Help shape the future of Rensselaer Dining by taking our annual survey and win a private chef experience for you and 5 friends! All students that take the survey are eligible for this giveaway. Last day to take the survey is Friday, February 13th 2026. For more information and how to take the survey click the link above.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-dining-survey-time</guid></item><item><title>NSF 3 Year Graduate Fellowship Information Session to be held Feb. 18th</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019c-1eff0a7e-000063bbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 18, 2026 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - The NSF GRFP provides 3 years of salary and tuition for Masters and PhD students in 30+ STEM fields. Rensselaer students earn this prestigious award every year. Seniors, 1st year grad students (fall 2026) who are U.S. citizens and permanent residents are eligible. Email madige@rpi.edu for information or Register for the virtual session: https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV_6L3FFwv0qCROrvE&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019c-1eff0a7e-000063bbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Webinar Friday February 6: Carousel Digital Signage</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-february-6-carousel-digital-signage</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Jim Evans, Director of MultiMedia Services, on Friday February 6 from 11am-12pm, for a hands-on training session and learn how to create and publish slides on RPI’s digital signage system, Carousel Digital Signage. Whether you’re promoting a lecture, club event, or campus initiative—this session will help you get your message on screens across RPI. Register now: https://rensselaer.webex.com/webappng/sites/rensselaer/webinar/webinarSeries/register/783d951c6ab8482e9198a7bd6075a700&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-february-6-carousel-digital-signage</guid></item><item><title>McKinney Writing Contest Open Through March 9</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-writing-contest-open-through-march-9</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2026 McKinney Writing Contest is open from November 1, 2025 through March 9, 2026. Submit in any or all of the following categories: Fiction, Creative Nonfiction, or Drama; Poetry; Academic Essay; Language &amp;amp; Image; or our NEW category: Writing for Games. Undergraduate and graduate divisions. First prize $300; 2nd prize $175; and 3rd prize $75. Submit: https://hass.rpi.edu/mckinney. Current students only. Questions? McKinney@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/mckinney-writing-contest-open-through-march-9</guid></item><item><title>Division of Finance - The Controller’s Office is Moving!</title><link>https://finance.rpi.edu/announcements/division-finance-controllers-office-moving</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Finance teams that were located downtown in the Proctor’s Building will be moving! Effective February 17, 2026, the Accounting, Accounts Payable, FAST, Payroll, RAF, and Tax teams, will be located in the Troy Building, 5th Floor. Effective on or about March 2, 2026, the Procurement Office will be located at 185 Jordan Rd, Rensselaer Technology Park. Contact information for the teams remains the same. Please contact Debbie Maloney (malond6@rpi.edu, x6426) if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.rpi.edu/announcements/division-finance-controllers-office-moving</guid></item><item><title>The 2026 Annual Conflict of Interest Survey Has Opened</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-annual-conflict-interest-survey-has-opened</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2026 Annual Conflict of Interest and Commitment survey has opened. This year, RPI has moved the survey to a new platform, Huron Research Suite. Also, responsibility for administering the survey has moved to the Institute Compliance Office. More information, including instructions for using the new platform, can be found at Compliance Office.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-annual-conflict-interest-survey-has-opened</guid></item><item><title>Teaching and Learning Collaboratory Faculty Call for Proposals: Submissions due March 9, 2026</title><link>https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory-faculty-call-proposals-submissions-due-march-9</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The OUE and the TLC invites proposals from full time tenure track faculty members or lecturers/Professors of Practice for piloting and assessing pedagogical innovations, especially those integrating interactive technologies into the classroom. We wish to fund seed projects that will serve as the foundation for external grant applications. Project proposals should entail the implementation of new interactive approaches, gaming, remote laboratories, or other innovative methods.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory-faculty-call-proposals-submissions-due-march-9</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Leading from Anywhere” February 20, 2026 9:00 am - 11:00 am</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere-february</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: In this workshop, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership not as positional or based on title, but rather on values and actions. Contact: Melissa Duquette - 518.276.3931&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere-february</guid></item><item><title>RPI Faculty and Staff In-Person Workshop: Talk Smart, Teach Strong: Sharpening Your Academic Presentation Skills</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-e1638373-00007c1acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, February 10, 2026 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - This session aims to strengthen academic presentation and facilitation skills, combining elements of presentation best practices with effective teaching strategies. You will explore techniques to enhance voice, presence, and impact in the classroom, while also engaging in train-the-trainer methods to foster active student participation. Please register by 2/6 using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-e1638373-00007c1acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>2025 Form W-2 Now Available on Employee Self-Service System</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-form-w-2-now-available-employee-self-service-system</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Payroll Office is pleased to announce to all members of the campus community that the 2025 W-2 information is now available via the Rensselaer Self-Service Information System.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-form-w-2-now-available-employee-self-service-system</guid></item><item><title>Coming Soon – Blackboard Learn Ultra Course View</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/coming-soon-blackboard-learn-ultra-course-view</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Blackboard has announced an end-of-life for Original course view, the course view we currently use. Therefore, RPI will be moving to Blackboard Learn Ultra Course View beginning with the summer 2026 semester. Details on the training and support available to help you get the most out of Blackboard Learn Ultra’s tools and features are coming soon. Please watch MorningMail over the next few months for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:31:46 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/coming-soon-blackboard-learn-ultra-course-view</guid></item></channel></rss>
