<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:31:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Graduate Certificate Review on June 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-3497f6b4-00002083calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 12, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for this information session highlighting the whole range of Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs. Three courses in length and able to be completed in a year or less, the certificates can add up to a customized, career-aligned master’s degree. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/certs12"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-3497f6b4-00002083calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>New Summer Arch Dining Options Announced</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/administration/06/07/2024/dining-options-summer-arch</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Dining is pleased to announce two new exciting Arch summer pop-up dining options that will be available during the week: “Summer Sizzle &amp;amp; Smoke” outside on the Student Union concourse, and “Patio Grill,” which will be located on the Union’s second-floor patio. The upcoming summer months will be a great time to stop by and check out what’s cooking at both locations!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/administration/06/07/2024/dining-options-summer-arch</guid></item><item><title>Deep-Dive Presentation of Recent Advances in HPC-Quantum Integration to be Held June 14</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/collaborative-effort-ibm-quantum-hpc-quantum-integration</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 10AM to 11m on Friday, June 14, the Future of Computing Institute at Rensselaer is pleased to announce a collaborative effort with IBM Quantum for HPC-Quantum integration, and invites you to join this deep-dive presentation of recent advances in HPC-Quantum integration. The goal is to identify subject-matter experts at RPI in HPC and Quantum Computing and their applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/collaborative-effort-ibm-quantum-hpc-quantum-integration</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Tech Tip Tuesday: Transcribe an Audio File as Text in Word</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/tech-tip-tuesday-transcribe-audio-file-text-word</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Can audio files be transcribed as text in Word? They sure can! The transcribe service can be used for many different types of audio files as well as recording audio, so if you have your voicemail setup to email you, the VoiceMessage.wav file in Outlook can be transcribed as text in Word.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/tech-tip-tuesday-transcribe-audio-file-text-word</guid></item><item><title>Summer Outdoor Program Series Continues with Overnight Backpacking Weekend</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-aab34b15-00002130calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, June 21, 2024 5:00 PM - Sun , June 23, 2024 2:00 PM - All students are invited to join the Outdoor Program’s trip to Pharaoh Lake Wilderness for a weekend of overnight backpacking! Registration is required, and each session has a maximum of eight participants; please &lt;a href="mailto:weinew2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Will Weinert&lt;/a&gt; in the Mueller Center to sign up or if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-aab34b15-00002130calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>LGBTQ+ Trivia Night Slated for June 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-f80896f7-00000113calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 12, 2024 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM - Stop by the Mueller Center lobby for some LGBTQ+ Trivia, run by the Rensselaer Pride Alliance!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-f80896f7-00000113calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty Training, “Using Handshake for Undergraduate Research Postings,” to be Held June 25</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-training-using-handshake-undergraduate-research-postings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, June 25 from noon to 1:30pm, the CCPD will host an interactive opportunity for faculty members to learn how to use Handshake for posting undergraduate research positions. At the end of the training, attendees will know more about Handshake, have an employer profile set up, and be prepared to post their first job. Space is limited to 15 participants; interested faculty should &lt;a href="mailto:stongn@rpi.edu"&gt;email Nicole Doran&lt;/a&gt; to sign up. Lunch will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-training-using-handshake-undergraduate-research-postings</guid></item></channel></rss>
