<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>OIP to Hold Study Abroad Info Session November 11</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/11/06/2024/november-study-abroad-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Interested in study abroad? All undergraduate students are welcome to join Office of International Programs staff at 4:00PM on Monday, November 11 in the CBIS Bruggeman Conference Room to learn about education abroad program options, study abroad and the ARCH, application procedures and deadlines, and how to get started. Please &lt;a href="mailto:dvorak2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Karen Dvorak&lt;/a&gt; if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/international-programs/11/06/2024/november-study-abroad-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Looking to Move into an Apartment?</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-9fdecf66-00000107calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 12, 2024 4:30 PM - 5:30 PM - All students are welcome to attend this session to learn about how to search for — and explore the considerations for selecting — an apartment, as well as get information on the resources that the Off-Campus Commons has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-9fdecf66-00000107calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>APO to Hold Thrift Sale November 13</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-c4012ba6-00000201calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 13, 2024 10:00 AM - 5:00 PM - This thrift sale in the Union will feature chargers, calculators, electronics, umbrellas, jackets, and various other things for very cheap. It’s a great way to buy small things you may have forgotten, or get great deals on a variety of items!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-c4012ba6-00000201calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Constellation Energy Virtual Info Session to be Held November 12</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/constellation-energy-virtual-info-session-be-held-november-12</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 5:30PM to 6:30PM EST on Tuesday, November 12, Constellation will host an information session for Rensselaer undergraduate students to discuss their initiatives and commitment to sustainability, the evolving energy industry, and what a career path at Constellation would look like! There will also be time for Q&amp;amp;A, networking, and one-on-one chats to answer your questions and get to know you better.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/constellation-energy-virtual-info-session-be-held-november-12</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Peer Career Advisors to Host “Major Mixer” November 14</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/major-mixer-hosted-ccpd-peer-career-advisors-be-held-november-14</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD’s Peer Career Advisors from 6pm to 8pm on Thursday, November 14 in the second-floor banquet hall in Russell Sage Dining Hall for a night of mingling and mixing with students across majors at RPI! Students will discuss their majors, experiences at RPI, and careers while enjoying a casual night with free food.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/major-mixer-hosted-ccpd-peer-career-advisors-be-held-november-14</guid></item><item><title>Gateway Shuttles to be Available for Thanksgiving Holiday</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/11/06/2024/gateway-shuttles-thanksgiving-holiday-break</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Department of Parking and Transportation is pleased to announce that it will once again be offering Gateway shuttle transportation to and from regional destination points — including the Albany International Airport, Albany bus terminal, and the Amtrak train station — for the upcoming Thanksgiving holiday. All reservations must be received by Wednesday, November 20, so be sure to sign up ASAP!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/11/06/2024/gateway-shuttles-thanksgiving-holiday-break</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Physicist Recognized by American Physical Society</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/11/01/rensselaer-physicist-recognized-american-physical-society</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Gwo-Ching Wang, Ph.D., Travelstead Institute Chair, is the 2025 recipient of the Davisson-Germer Prize in Atomic or Surface Physics from the American Physical Society (APS). Wang is being honored for “pioneering contributions to the development and use of electron diffraction techniques to study surfaces, growth-front ordering, and two-dimensional materials.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/11/01/rensselaer-physicist-recognized-american-physical-society</guid></item><item><title>Cognitive Science Seminar Scheduled for November 13th</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/charting-middle-path-beyond-dialogue-systems-dichotomies-dr-david-traum</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join the Cognitive Science Department at noon on Wednesday, November 13th in Carnegie 113, for a seminar titled “Charting a Middle Path: Beyond Dialogue Systems Dichotomies” by Dr. David Traum, Director for Natural Language Research at the Institute for Creative Technologies (ICT) and Research Professor in the Department of Computer Science at the University of Southern California (USC).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/charting-middle-path-beyond-dialogue-systems-dichotomies-dr-david-traum</guid></item><item><title>Veterans Day Memorial Ceremony to be Held November 11</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/11/07/veterans-day-memorial</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Air Force Reserve Officers Training Corps (AFROTC) Detachment 550 will honor and celebrate all veterans—past and present—this Veterans Day on November 11 at the Approach; all are welcome to join the cadets at 10:45 a.m. as they lay a wreath near the WWI and WWII memorials and highlight the stories of a few RPI veterans. Thanks to the Registrar’s Office, a small gathering will follow the ceremony to honor veterans and their families at Evelyn’s Café in EMPAC.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/11/07/veterans-day-memorial</guid></item><item><title>HackRPI to Draw Hundreds This Weekend</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/11/07/hackrpi-draw-hundreds-weekend</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, November 9, hundreds will gather at Rensselaer for HackRPI 2024, the 24-hour coding marathon in which participants will team up to address the competition’s Urban Upgrades theme, and will then be asked to enhance the infrastructure, services, and quality of life in cities by developing new ideas and technologies. Prizes will be awarded during the closing ceremony around 2 p.m. on Sunday, November 10.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/11/07/hackrpi-draw-hundreds-weekend</guid></item><item><title>ECSE Mercer Lecture Scheduled for November 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-72d5ba98-00003ec4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 13, 2024 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join ECSE for this Mercer Lecture titled “Understanding Actors, Actions and Scenes from Unconstrained Images and Videos Collected at Varying Altitudes and Ranges” with Prof. Rama Chellappa of Johns Hopkins University.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-72d5ba98-00003ec4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of the Veterans Day Remembrance Event!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-dd48cbd5-00000954calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 11, 2024 10:45 AM - 1:00 PM - All are welcome to join event host Air Force ROTC, Detachment 550, for a Veterans Day remembrance event at the Louis Rubin Memorial Approach to celebrate RPI veterans past and present. A reception, hosted by the Office of the Registrar, will follow at EMPAC’s Evelyn’s Cafe.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-dd48cbd5-00000954calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Mark Your Calendars for 24 for 1824 Giving Day on November 12!</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23279&amp;ecid=23279&amp;ciid=80762&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer recognizes its Founders Day each year on November 5, the date Stephen Van Rensselaer wrote a letter announcing the formation of the Rensselaer School, where he declared his intent to educate students “in the application of science to the common purposes of life.” In honor of Founders Day and the Institute’s Bicentennial, RPI will host this year’s Giving Day, 24 for 1824, on Tuesday, November 12 to provide a 24-hour opportunity to support our students, the next generation of RPI alumni.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23279&amp;ecid=23279&amp;ciid=80762&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>AI Assistant to Guide Researchers in Labyrinthine World of Computational Modeling and Discovery</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/10/31/ai-assistant-guide-researchers-labyrinthine-world-computational-modeling-and-discovery</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In ancient Greek mythology, the hero Theseus is famous for cleverly solving a labyrinth and defeating the Minotaur at its center. That story, as well as a famous maze experiment from the history of machine learning, is the inspiration for a new generative AI tool that helps researchers navigate the domain of computer modeling.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/10/31/ai-assistant-guide-researchers-labyrinthine-world-computational-modeling-and-discovery</guid></item><item><title>CMDIS Annual Research Symposium Scheduled for November 22</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-fd72cae8-00006657calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, November 22, 2024 8:30 AM - 6:00 PM - The Center for Materials, Devices and Integrated Systems is pleased to host its annual Research Symposium, and invites all faculty, visiting scholars, researchers, graduate students, facility users and undergraduate researchers to &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/form/cmdis-annual-research-symposium"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to participate! Breakfast and lunch will be provided, and an award ceremony and reception will follow the event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-fd72cae8-00006657calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI Lecturer Participates in Virtual NASA Training</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/11/04/rpi-lecturer-participates-virtual-nasa-training</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Richard Bonocora, Ph.D., a senior lecturer in biological sciences, recently joined 29 other international participants for the Spaceflight Technology, Applications and Research (STAR) program, which is “a virtual NASA training for space biosciences.” The program, which runs until February, will give Bonocora an overview of the current topics in space biology, discuss how to conduct an experiment in space and all of the unique considerations, and provide unique collaborative opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/11/04/rpi-lecturer-participates-virtual-nasa-training</guid></item><item><title>Nominations Now Open for Phalanx Honor Society</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9b0fbf83-00003ac7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 25, 2024 12:00 AM - Nominations are now open for the Phalanx Honor Society, which has been active for over 100 years with the purpose of recognizing students, faculty, and staff who exemplify the three pillars of Leadership, Service, and Devotion to the Alma Mater. From now through November 25, please consider taking a moment to &lt;a href="https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV_a3K4bOfZkZf07em"&gt;nominate&lt;/a&gt; a peer, colleague or friend for this special honor!…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9b0fbf83-00003ac7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HR Announces Professional Development Book Discussion Series, “Everyday People, Extraordinary Leadership”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-book-discussion-series-everday</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The premise of this book is quite simple: Leadership is a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. This virtual book discussion, which is scheduled to be held from 1:00PM to 2:30PM on Friday, November 22, will explore the five practices of exemplary leadership that are detailed, and participants will share their reactions to the book’s themes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-book-discussion-series-everday</guid></item><item><title>Virtual URP Handshake Faculty Training to be Held November 21</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/virtual-urp-handshake-training-be-held-november-21</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 2:00PM to 3:00PM on Thursday, November 21, the CCPD will host an opportunity for faculty members to learn how to use Handshake for posting undergraduate research positions. If you can’t make it to this session but would like to be notified of future trainings, please &lt;a href="mailto:stongn@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Nicole Doran&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:10 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/virtual-urp-handshake-training-be-held-november-21</guid></item></channel></rss>
