<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:31:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Fellowship info Session to Highlight Competitions for Grad School Salary and Tuition</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-56fd2090-0000036fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 4, 2024 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Competitive fellowships provide salary and tuition for Masters and PhD students. All graduate students, juniors, seniors, and international students are welcome to attend this session to learn how to find and apply to appropriate programs that will fund fall 2025 and beyond. &lt;a href="https://rpi.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_5q1McRZJMkpb0G2"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; to attend or just drop in!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:31:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-56fd2090-0000036fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Help Give the Gift of Life!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-98818506-00004c10calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, August 29, 2024 11:30 AM - 5:30 PM - Please take a minute to &lt;a href="https://tinyurl.com/7htbykph"&gt;sign up&lt;/a&gt; for this blood drive, to be held in the Rensselaer Union’s Shelnutt Gallery and Ellsworth Room, located in rooms 3602 and 3606, respectively. For more info, follow &lt;span class="citation" data-cites="RPIUnion"&gt;@RPIUnion&lt;/span&gt;, stop by the Mueller Center, or &lt;a href="mailto:rastos4@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Saurabh Rastogi&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:31:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-98818506-00004c10calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>From Multimedia Services: New MyMediasite Video Editor Now Available</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-new-mymediasite-video-editor-now-available</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the Rensselaer community that the MyMediasite multimedia video system now has a new video editor with increased functionality that is immediately available to everyone with access to MyMediaite for recorded and uploaded videos. Please see the &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/articles/26717262422157"&gt;ITSSC article&lt;/a&gt;, “Editing Video in MyMediasite,” for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:31:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-new-mymediasite-video-editor-now-available</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC Artist-in-Residence Laurie Anderson to Speak on “ARK”</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-32ef9ceb-00002759calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, August 29, 2024 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - Renowned artist and musician Laurie Anderson opens the fall season at EMPAC with the free artist talk, “Building an ARK,” in which she reveals the process behind her newest major stage work, described as “a hallucinatory incantation on history and time, a dark comedy for the end of the world.” Anderson is at EMPAC for a final production residency in preparation for ARK’s November 2024 world premiere in Manchester, United Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:31:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-32ef9ceb-00002759calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Doctoral Student Envisions Solar Power for All</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/08/19/solar-power-all</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Ozioma Ozioko, a doctoral student at Rensselaer, is on a mission to give her home country of Nigeria — and the rest of the world — ready access to solar energy. Ozioko, who first became interested in solar power when she received a scholarship to attend a local high school that had more consistent power than her home, is collaborating with SolaBlock, a Massachusetts and New York company that integrates solar technology into masonry, as part of her doctoral work.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:31:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/08/19/solar-power-all</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Fall 2024 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-fall-2024-course-requests-please-read</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Fall 2024 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:31:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-fall-2024-course-requests-please-read</guid></item><item><title>OUE Announces Syllabus Guidance for Language with Generative AI Tools</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/21/2024/syllabus-guidance-language-generative-ai-tools</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer instructors are welcome to use the Office of Undergraduate Education’s &lt;a href="https://info.rpi.edu/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory/#SyllabusGuidanceforLanguagewithGenerativeAITools"&gt;syllabus guidance statements&lt;/a&gt; — which focus on generative AI tools in the classroom and were curated from discussions and openly available Web resources — to decide if AI tools fit within their pedagogical goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:31:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/21/2024/syllabus-guidance-language-generative-ai-tools</guid></item></channel></rss>
