<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:35:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Will Tech Valley become an artificial intelligence hub?</title><link>https://www.timesunion.com/business/article/tech-valley-artificial-intelligence-hub-19437052.php</link><description>&lt;p&gt;With the GlobalFoundries microchip plant in Malta and SUNY Polytechnic’s nanotechnology lab in Albany, the Capital Region has in the last decade earned the moniker “Tech Valley,” shorthand for a region where cutting-edge computer chips are developed and manufactured. Now, leaders of two area colleges would like to build on that and create a hub for work in the artificial intelligence field, in which super computers can learn, think and possibly, someday, reason for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.timesunion.com/business/article/tech-valley-artificial-intelligence-hub-19437052.php</guid></item><item><title>Football Announces Three Additions to Coaching Staff</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/5/6/rpi-football-announces-three-additions-to-coaching-staff.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer football team and Head Coach Ralph Isernia have announced three additions to the coaching staff ahead of the 2024 season, with Kevin Billington, Sean Moore, and Pete Palczewski all set to join the Engineer’s sideline. Billington and Moore will work on the defensive side of the ball as the respective Safeties and Defensive Line Coach, while Palczewski will instruct the Wide Receivers unit.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/5/6/rpi-football-announces-three-additions-to-coaching-staff.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Music Curator to Lead EMPAC Tour</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8c5f627b-018d-7f7e632a-000069bbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, May 11, 2024 11:00 AM - Each of EMPAC’s performance spaces was designed as a blank canvas, endlessly customizable according to the needs of its diverse productions. Join Music Curator Amadeus Julian Regucera for a free public tour of EMPAC as he discusses the acoustic and visual potential of each venue for the making of complex artworks, with stories from recent productions. Tours begin in the main lobby; please arrive 15 minutes before tour time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8c5f627b-018d-7f7e632a-000069bbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Don’t Miss the 26th Annual RPI Football Golf Tournament!</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=9806&amp;cid=22506&amp;ecid=22506&amp;ciid=78792&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mark your calendar for this year’s RPI Football Golf Outing, which is scheduled to be held on May 17 at Western Turnpike Golf Course in Guilderland, New York; check-in is at 8AM, with a shotgun start at 9AM. The outing provides a great opportunity for our current and former players to celebrate the past, enjoy the present, and look ahead to the future, and this is your chance to help both the golf outing and Rensselaer’s football program reach new heights!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=9806&amp;cid=22506&amp;ecid=22506&amp;ciid=78792&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Seniors Encouraged to Complete Senior Survey</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/seniorsurvey24</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As the academic year at RPI draws to a close, graduating seniors are asked to remember that their voice matters, and are invited to please complete the senior survey! A unique link was sent to graduating students’ email, and the survey results will be used to improve the student experience at Rensselaer. For more information or assistance, please &lt;a href="mailto:svirsa2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Amy Svirsky&lt;/a&gt; in Institutional Research.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/seniorsurvey24</guid></item><item><title>Ph.D. Hooding Ceremony to be Held May 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8bd409ab-018c-3b2135cd-00002b17calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 17, 2024 8:30 AM - 10:30 AM - The hooding ceremony is a unique recognition of the achievement of each student who has earned a doctorate! During the ceremoney, each candidate is introduced individually and will have their hood placed on them while standing on the stage. Check-in starts at 7:45AM and the ceremony begins at 8:30AM; refreshments will be available after the ceremony concludes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:35:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8bd409ab-018c-3b2135cd-00002b17calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
