<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Spring 2026 Mercer XLab: Join Our Team!</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-2026-mercer-xlab-join-our-team</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mercer XLab is looking for curious individuals passionate about learning, helping others, and making the TECH in PolyTECHnic visible all over campus! Please fill out the Join Our Team Form to be considered for Spring 2026. We offer a collaborative work environment, opportunities to lead, and continuous professional development. Paid positions are available. Curiosity, creativity, and communication are the only requirements for the For-Credit option. All majors are welcome to apply!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-2026-mercer-xlab-join-our-team</guid></item><item><title>Finals Week Dining Halls Updated Hours</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/finals-week-dining-halls-updated-hours</link><description>&lt;p&gt;To better support students during finals, Commons and Russell Sage Dining Halls will open for breakfast 30 minutes earlier during finals. Please click the link to see the announcement and to find out hours of operations for these dining halls. Good luck on your exams!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/finals-week-dining-halls-updated-hours</guid></item><item><title>Fuel Up for Finals with Brain Food Week!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fuel-finals-brain-food-week</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Get ready to power through finals—Brain Food Week is coming December 15–19! Stop by Commons’ Bliss station and locations throughout Father’s to find Mindful, brain-boosting snacks designed to help you stay sharp, energized, and focused.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fuel-finals-brain-food-week</guid></item><item><title>Extended hours and study spaces for Reading Days</title><link>https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/reading-day-events</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Don’t study in you room! Extended hours and Drop-in tutoring for Reading Days Dec 13-15 at three locations: EMPAC (Sat 10am-8pm, Sun 2pm-10pm, Mon 9am-10pm), Heffner Alumni House (Sun-Mon 9am-10pm), and Success Center (Mon 11am-5pm). Subjects include Calculus, Physics, CS, Data Structures, Differential Equations, and engineering courses. Free snacks! Full schedule: successcenter.rpi.edu/tutoring&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/reading-day-events</guid></item><item><title>Claim your Bloomberg.com account courtesy of RPI Libraries</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/claim-your-bloombergcom-account-courtesy-rpi-libraries</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI Libraries are pleased to announce campus access to Bloomberg.com, a premier resource for business and financial information and global insights. Sign in using your RPI credentials for unlimited access to Bloomberg.com, including live radio, podcasts, narrated articles, and live streaming of Bloomberg TV. Also available on the Bloomberg app!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/claim-your-bloombergcom-account-courtesy-rpi-libraries</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents: Guest Speaker Michelle Grabner</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-guest-speaker-michelle-grabner</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us in West Hall 113 or virtually on December 15 from 5pm-7pm for an iEAR Presents event. Guest Speaker Michelle Grabner is a Wisconsin-based artist, writer, and curator. She co-curated the 2014 Whitney Biennial and was the Artistic Director for the inaugural 2018 FRONT International: Cleveland Triennial for Contemporary Art. Her practice spans a variety of media including drawing, painting, and sculpture, and finds a creative center in operating across platforms and towards community.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-guest-speaker-michelle-grabner</guid></item><item><title>Math Colloquium: Jacob Beckey (University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign) | Dec. 15</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019b-0ef32190-00000bfccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, December 15, 2025 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM - This Mathematical Sciences Colloquium will feature a presentation titled “Characterizing Non-local Quantum Properties with Local Measurements” by Dr. Jacob Beckey. He is a National Science Foundation Mathematical Sciences and Illinois Quantum Information Science and Technology Center Postdoctoral Fellow at the University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019b-0ef32190-00000bfccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI at Work Single Course Enrollment Options | Dec. 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-b6cb154c-00000bc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, December 17, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., will host this RPI at Work information session reviewing the online graduate programs for working professionals and provide course enrollment options to make an immediate impact on one’s work. Participants can also explore courses for developing valuable skills that benefit employee and employer alike. Please register to attend&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-b6cb154c-00000bc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Getting the Most Out of AI with Percipio”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-getting-most-out-ai-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;“Getting the Most Out of AI with Percipio” This workshop introduces you to Percipio’s AI Chat, AI Skill Benchmarks, and interactive AI scenarios. You’ll learn how to navigate AI Chat to explore ideas, ask questions, and get quick support. You’ll also be shown how to access and complete AI Skill Benchmarks and use guided scenarios to practice applying Percipio’s AI features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-getting-most-out-ai-0</guid></item></channel></rss>
