<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Introducing the Library’s New Virtual Service Desk!</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/introducing-librarys-new-virtual-service-desk</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Need help but can’t make it to the library? Our Access Services team is now available online through the Virtual Service Desk seven days a week. Whether you’re looking for help searching for an item, accessing your library account to renew books, or reserving group study rooms, you can now chat directly with our staff in real time—no matter where you are. Get the same support you’d receive at the service desk, right from your laptop or phone.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/introducing-librarys-new-virtual-service-desk</guid></item><item><title>Introduction to Nationally Competitive Fellowships: Funding Your Graduate Education | Dec. 3 (Registration Required by Dec. 2)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-83d73ea7-000069b4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, December 3, 2025 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Competitive programs provide salary and tuition for graduate students, allowing you to focus on your research, network within and beyond your field, and travel for research and conferences. Learn how to find and apply to programs. Graduate students, juniors and seniors are invited to this virtual information session highlighting major programs Rensselaer students are eligible for. Register at https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-83d73ea7-000069b4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; GE Vernova Info Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-ge-vernova-info-session-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Calling all Electrical Engineering students! GE Vernova will be on campus for an info session on Tuesday, December 2nd from 5:30-7:30pm. Come meet with Khine Win (Sr Engineering Manager - Electrical Component) and Zeeky Bukhala (Consulting Engineer - Electrical Accessories) to discuss full time and intern opportunities at GE Vernova within the Gas Power Electrical Engineering team. Register and learn more in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-ge-vernova-info-session-0</guid></item><item><title>Russell Sage Dining Hall to Relocate Cashier Station</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/russell-sage-dining-hall-relocate-cashier-station</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon! The cashier station for Russell Sage Dining Hall will be relocated to the East entrance of the building. This entrance will also be the designated exit point for leaving Russell Sage Dining Hall. Please note that Simply To Go will continue to be accessed through the West entrance.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/russell-sage-dining-hall-relocate-cashier-station</guid></item><item><title>DoD S.M.A.R.T. application reviews now available!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-6e94f0eb-00004ffbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, November 10, 2025 12:00 AM - Mon , December 1, 2025 12:00 PM - Students applying to the DoD S.M.A.R.T. Scholars program are encouraged to seek application assistance and review from the DoD on-campus support advisor. The program provides one-five years of salary and full tuition for undergraduate and graduate students with guaranteed work post-graduation. Send application drafts and/or questions to Betty Madigan madige@rpi.edu before the December 5th deadline.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-6e94f0eb-00004ffbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Mercer XLab 2025 Take It, Break It, Make It Contest</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-2025-take-it-break-it-make-it-contest</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mercer X Take It, Break It, Make It 2025 edition is here! You (and your collaborators) can take apart and reconstruct, in your own innovative way, anything that helps you learn: electronic hardware, software, theoretical models. Show your creativity and depth of knowledge by reverse-engineering and then making something new! Fill out the 2025 Take It, Break It, Make It participation form by December 20th. Your video submission is due January 12th. Email sawyes@rpi.edu for more details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-2025-take-it-break-it-make-it-contest</guid></item><item><title>ECSE Seminar: “Equation-Oriented Languages in Industry: From Model-Based Design to Digital Twins” | Dec. 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-7e374b76-000077eccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, December 2, 2025 3:30 PM - 5:00 PM - ECSE seminar by Dr. Christopher Laughman on applying methods to building systems, which are increasingly emphasizing system integration in order to coordinate the dynamic behavior of the electrical grid, distributed energy resources, and energy consumers (e.g., HVAC systems).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-7e374b76-000077eccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI Holiday Concert and Victorian Stroll Kickoff | Dec. 6 (Registration Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-023482d1-0000232fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, December 6, 2025 7:00 PM - 8:30 PM - Presented in partnership with the Rensselaer County Regional Chamber of Commerce, this free, family-friendly event invites you to celebrate the season with music, community, and festive refreshments. The concert will feature performances by the RPI Orchestra, Concert Choir, and Wind Symphony, with works by Smetana, Tchaikovsky, Gershwin, Lauridsen, and Saint-Saëns. &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/holiday-concert"&gt;Registration is required&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-023482d1-0000232fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Shut the Sash: Fume Hood Energy Conservation</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/shut-sash-fume-hood-energy-conservation</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Attention lab users! Minimize chemical exposure and reduce campus energy use by closing the fume hood sash when not in use. To support this practice, Environmental Health &amp;amp; Safety (EHS) has placed Shut the Sash stickers on chemical fume hoods, which can help reduce energy consumption by up to 40%.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/shut-sash-fume-hood-energy-conservation</guid></item><item><title>Single Course Enrollment Options with RPI at Work | Dec. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-b6c66dc5-00007d17calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, December 3, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., will host this RPI at Work information session reviewing the online graduate programs for working professionals and provide course enrollment options to make an immediate impact on one’s work. Participants can also explore courses for developing valuable skills that benefit employee and employer alike. Please register to attend&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-b6c66dc5-00007d17calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents Guest Speaker: Pieter Schoolwerth</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-guest-speaker-pieter-schoolwerth</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us in West Hall 113 on December 3 at 5pm to listen to a talk by Pieter Schoolwerth. After graduating from the California Institute of the Arts in 1994, he moved to New York. From 2003 to 2013, Schoolwerth founded and ran Wierd Records, a now legendary institution based out of New York’s Lower East Side that released music by 46 bands and produced over 500 live shows and performance events.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-guest-speaker-pieter-schoolwerth</guid></item><item><title>Winter Sounds Performances on December 7</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/winter-sounds-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;End of the semester musical performance by student members of the RPI Chamber Ensembles in the DCC Media Studio. As well as performances by faculty music fellows performing Composition Seminar students final compositions. 3:30pm-4:30pm Chamber part 1 4pm-6pm Chamber part 2 7pm-8:30pm Composition Seminar&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/winter-sounds-2025</guid></item><item><title>ECSE Mercer Lecture: “Heterogeneous Integrated Sub-THz Transceiver Front End” | Dec. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-2a73fdde-00006c7bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, December 3, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join us for an ECSE Mercer Lecture: “Heterogeneous Integrated Sub-THz Transceiver Front End” with Prof. James Hwang of Cornell University. Abstract and speaker bio can be found at the event URL.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0199-2a73fdde-00006c7bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Physics, Applied Physics and Astronomy Colloquium: Professor Philip Kurian, Howard University | Dec. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-7d90233e-00007f61calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, December 3, 2025 12:00 AM - 1:00 AM - Title: From slime molds to the stars: Morphological computational capacity of Physarum polycephalum&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-7d90233e-00007f61calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Volunteers Needed: Late Night Breakfast at Commons!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/volunteers-needed-late-night-breakfast-commons</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Help our students get fueled up for finals by helping with Late Night Breakfast on December 11th at Commons Dining Hall. We are looking for enthusiastic faculty and staff volunteers to help make the event a success! If you’re interested in volunteering, please sign up by emailing auxiliaryservices@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/volunteers-needed-late-night-breakfast-commons</guid></item><item><title>Drug Free Schools and Campuses Act Notification</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/drug-free-schools-and-campuses-act-notification</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The health and safety of our RPI community is of utmost importance. In furtherance of our efforts to enhance the wellbeing of our students, staff, and faculty, and in compliance with the Drug-Free Schools and Communities Act (DFSCA), we have reviewed and updated Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute’s Drug-Free Schools and Campus Regulations Annual Notification.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/drug-free-schools-and-campuses-act-notification</guid></item><item><title>What’s New in Employee Benefits for 2026</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/whats-new-employee-benefits-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Division of Human Resources invites all faculty and staff to learn about the updates to employee benefits for 2026 and explore ways to maximize your coverage. Each virtual session will include a brief overview followed by time for questions and open dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/whats-new-employee-benefits-2026</guid></item><item><title>TIAA Confidential Counseling (In-Person) | Dec. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0196-b5bac1f0-00003062calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, December 3, 2025 8:00 AM - 4:30 PM - A TIAA Financial Consultant will be available for one-on-one consultations on a broad range of retirement topics. Attend this upcoming event to help you become better informed and more confident about Rensselaer’s retirement plan benefits. Consultations will be conducted in 60 minute increments. To schedule your individual retirement counseling, please call TIAA at 1-800-732-8353 or online at https://www.tiaa.org/public/login/schedule-meeting&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0196-b5bac1f0-00003062calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar - “Shaping a Motivational Workplace” | Dec. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-3b3eb39d-00006872calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, December 3, 2025 8:00 AM - 12:00 PM - People want to use their abilities, connect with others and guide their own efforts. Research has shown that people share these three psychological needs: Competence, Relatedness and Autonomy. In this seminar leaders learn to create an environment that inspires superior performance by helping employees satisfy these basic needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-3b3eb39d-00006872calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
