<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Handshake’s Just In Time Engineering Virtual Career Fair | May 9</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/handshakes-just-time-engineering-virtual-career-fair-may-9-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to explore exciting opportunities and connect with industry leaders? This VIRTUAL engineering-focused fair is the perfect opportunity to do so! Join Handshake, the CCPD, and other schools across the country on Friday, May 9, 2025 between 12-3pm to network with employers who are eager to recruit for internships, co-ops, and full-time positions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/handshakes-just-time-engineering-virtual-career-fair-may-9-2025</guid></item><item><title>Ph.D. Hooding Ceremony | May 9</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-1a98bc9c-00003d3dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 9, 2025 8:30 AM - 10:30 AM - The hooding ceremony is a unique recognition of the achievement of each student who has earned a doctorate. Each doctoral candidate is introduced individually during the ceremony. They will have their hood placed on them while standing on the stage in the concert hall. Check-in starts- at 7:45 AM Ceremony- at 8:30 AM Refreshments- after the ceremony concludes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-1a98bc9c-00003d3dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering Commencement Dinner and Celebration | May 9 (RSVP Required)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-71605693-00003247calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 9, 2025 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM - Join faculty and staff as we honor our graduates and their families at the Hilton Garden Inn in Troy.The sit-down dinner will be followed by the presentation of awards and prizes. A professional photographer will be on hand to take photos of the graduates with their families and friends. Reservations are due May 1, 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-71605693-00003247calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>You’re Invited to a Special Fireside Chat: May 9</title><link>https://commencement.rpi.edu/announcements/youre-invited-special-fireside-chat-presidents-commencement-colloquy-driving</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Martin A. Schmidt ’81, Ph.D., and his wife, Lyn, invite you to the President’s Commencement Colloquy, a special Fireside Chat featuring Lisa Su, Ph.D., chair and CEO of AMD, TIME’s CEO of the Year, and one of TIME’s 100 Most Influential People in AI. Don’t miss this opportunity to hear firsthand from two visionary leaders about driving technology innovation in industry. This free event is open to the public and will be followed by a reception with refreshments in Evelyn’s Café.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://commencement.rpi.edu/announcements/youre-invited-special-fireside-chat-presidents-commencement-colloquy-driving</guid></item><item><title>Pittsburgh Building Closed for Renovations This Summer</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/pittsburgh-building-closed-renovations-summer</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Pittsburgh Building will be fully closed for renovations beginning Monday, May 12, and will remain inaccessible through Wednesday, August 21. During this period, no access will be permitted for any faculty, staff, students, or visitors. Please plan accordingly. Thank you for your cooperation as we work to improve our facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/pittsburgh-building-closed-renovations-summer</guid></item><item><title>Physics, Applied Physics and Astronomy Colloquium: Professor Shengbai Zhang, Physics, RPI | April 9</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-d29f92cd-000076e0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 9, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Title and abstract to be announced.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-d29f92cd-000076e0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>2025 Annual Steam &amp; Electrical Shutdowns | May 10-May 17</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/facilities-management/03/26/2025/2025-annual-steam-electrical-shutdowns</link><description>&lt;p&gt;2025 Annual Shutdowns • Campus wide steam and electrical distribution systems outages will take place beginning Saturday May, 10th and ending on Sunday May 17th. This work is done on the main Rensselaer campus annually in order to perform critical infrastructure preventative maintenance. The Physical Plant works closely with the Registrar’s Office, Summer Arch, Summer at Rensselaer and Rensselaer’s Conference Services to minimize the impact to our students.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/facilities-management/03/26/2025/2025-annual-steam-electrical-shutdowns</guid></item><item><title>Informational Webinar for Rensselaer at Work | May 9</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5ef58f3b-000040e0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 9, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., will be reviewing the online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates. Expect to hear details about how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment. Please RSVP if you plan to attend and learn more about Rensselaer at Work.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5ef58f3b-000040e0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Temporary Closure of Portions of Sage Avenue</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/temporary-closure-portions-sage-avenue</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We would like to inform you that essential repairs to a low-pressure condensate line serving our steam and heating systems will require the temporary closure of portions of Sage Avenue. The affected area is located near the Sage Avenue entrance to the academic campus, between the Ricketts Building and the 87’ Gymnasium. This work is scheduled to occur from approximately mid-July through mid-August, with completion planned before the start of the fall semester.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/temporary-closure-portions-sage-avenue</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience several “Supervisory Simulations” with colleagues. In addition, the importance of coaching employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team capacity will be explored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:38:40 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-0</guid></item></channel></rss>
