<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:31:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Multimedia Services Announces Upcoming Outage for Blackboard LMS, Mediasite</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-announces-upcoming-outage-blackboard-lms-mediasite</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the Rensselaer community that the integration between the Blackboard LMS and the Mediasite streaming platform will be upgraded between 10:00AM and 3:00PM on Thursday, May 9. Because this work may impact links to Mediasite videos within Blackboard and the ability to embed new links, DotCIO highly recommends avoiding adding or testing Mediasite course content during this time period.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:31:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-announces-upcoming-outage-blackboard-lms-mediasite</guid></item><item><title>An Important Update and Reminder Regarding Rensselaer’s Export Control Program</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/export-controls/05/06/2024/important-update-and-reminder-regarding-rensselaers-export-control</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Export Control Office recently announced that, in proactive response to updated federal requirements and guidance, Rensselaer is updating its relevant export control processes and expanding them to include a global research security program responsive to pending federal requirements.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:31:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/export-controls/05/06/2024/important-update-and-reminder-regarding-rensselaers-export-control</guid></item><item><title>Music Curator to Lead EMPAC Tour</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8c5f627b-018d-7f7e632a-000069bbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, May 11, 2024 11:00 AM - Each of EMPAC’s performance spaces was designed as a blank canvas, endlessly customizable according to the needs of its diverse productions. Join Music Curator Amadeus Julian Regucera for a free public tour of EMPAC as he discusses the acoustic and visual potential of each venue for the making of complex artworks, with stories from recent productions. Tours begin in the main lobby; please arrive 15 minutes before tour time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:31:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8c5f627b-018d-7f7e632a-000069bbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CBE 2024 Abbott Lecture to be Held May 8</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-4f53312c-000059cecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, May 8, 2024 9:15 AM - 10:15 AM - This event will feature a presentation titled “A Hitchhiker’s and Backpacker’s Guide to Drug Delivery,” by Samir Mitragotri of Harvard University.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:31:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-4f53312c-000059cecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Collegiate Store Offering Birthday Specials for Faculty, Staff</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/collegiate-store/03/07/2024/birthday-special-collegiate-store</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Collegiate Store is happy to announce that it will be celebrating RPI faculty and staff birthdays with an invitation to shop for one clothing or gift item at 20% off. Beginning in March 2024, faculty and staff can just come in during their birthday month to get their coupon, which can then be used in-store or online.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:31:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/collegiate-store/03/07/2024/birthday-special-collegiate-store</guid></item><item><title>Multimedia Services Announces Mediasite Capture Now Available to Faculty, Staff</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-announces-mediasite-capture-now-available-faculty-staff</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services is pleased to announce that Mediasite Capture is now available to staff and faculty through MyMediasite. Capture allows recording of video through a browser without installing any additional software. Please refer to &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/articles/24815238635277-Creating-Content-Recording-Video-Using-Mediasite-Capture"&gt;ITSSC&lt;/a&gt; for more information on Mediasite Capture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:31:47 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/multimedia-services-announces-mediasite-capture-now-available-faculty-staff</guid></item></channel></rss>
