<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Student Insurance Plan Change for 2025 - 2026</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/student-insurance-plan-change-2025-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI student health insurance plan has renewed for the 2025-2026 year. There are no changes to the insurance benefits and there is no increase in the health insurance fee. However, there has been a change in the insurance carrier. The new carrier is Aetna. Students are encouraged to complete enrollment on the insurance portal to activate their health insurance benefits. The deadline to waive out of the plan is September 1st.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/student-insurance-plan-change-2025-2026</guid></item><item><title>Fellowship info Session to Highlight Competitions for Grad School Salary and Tuition | Sept. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-aeefb2db-000063d1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 3, 2025 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Competitive fellowships provide salary and tuition for masters and PhD students. Seniors and graduate students will learn how to find and apply to appropriate programs that will fund fall 2026 and beyond. Programs are available for all stages of your academic career. International students are welcome! Register for the virtual session. Email madige@rpi.edu for information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-aeefb2db-000063d1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; Western Digital HDD Teardown Workshop | Sept. 10</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-western-digital-hdd-teardown-workshop</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD and Western Digital for the popular HDD Teardown Workshop on Wednesday, September 10th from 5-6pm! Learn from Western Digital team members as they discuss types of cloud storage and lead you through a hands-on opportunity to disassemble a hard drive. Space is limited–register and learn more in Handshake! More information &amp;amp; Registration: https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/events/1789804/share_preview&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-western-digital-hdd-teardown-workshop</guid></item><item><title>Counseling Center New Location</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/counseling-center-new-location</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Counseling Center has moved to a new location within Academy Hall. You can now find us in Suite 4200 (next door) the space formerly occupied by ALAC.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/counseling-center-new-location</guid></item><item><title>TOPOS 2025: Sarah Davachi premieres The Rose Dialogues with pre-concert talk | Aug. 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-7be7a188-000059a4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, August 29, 2025 6:00 PM - 8:30 PM - TOPOS is proud to present the world premiere of a newly commissioned work by Sarah Davachi, a leading voice in contemporary experimental music. The Rose Dialogues, scored for two violas, cello, organ, and electronics, begins with the canon form and unfolds into an expansive exploration of harmony, resonance, and temporal suspension. Davachi’s music doesn’t declare itself; it reveals itself. If you follow her work, you already know: these moments…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-7be7a188-000059a4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources: Getting the Most from Percipio (Getting Started with Percipio: Navigation Q&amp;A) | Sept. 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-42bec315-00007b41calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 5, 2025 9:00 AM - 9:30 AM - This brief course is designed to help you get comfortable using Percipio, RPI’s digital learning platform. You’ll learn how to navigate the main dashboard, search for content, access assigned learning, and track your progress. We’ll also walk through common questions users have and show you where to find help when needed. Whether you’re brand new or just need a refresher, this session will ensure you’re ready to make the most of Percipio.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-42bec315-00007b41calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CBE’s 2025 Birnboim Lecture Series features Dr. Nitash Balsara | Sept. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-d20cb83e-00006f04calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 3, 2025 9:15 AM - 10:15 AM - The Professor Meyer H. Birnboim Endowed Lecture Series, a joint lecture series between Chemical and Biological Engineering and Physics, features Dr. Nitash Balsara, a Professor from U.C. Berkeley. Dr. Balsara’s lecture, “Movement of Polymer Molecules under Electric Fields and Relevance to Rechargeable Batteries” is open to all. Refreshments will be available in the CBIS Auditorium Gallery at 8:45 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-d20cb83e-00006f04calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Todd Przybycien Named Head of RPI’s Howard P. Isermann Department of Chemical and Biological Engineering</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2025/08/25/todd-przybycien-named-head-rpis-howard-p-isermann-department-chemical-and-biological</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Todd Przybycien, Ph.D., professor of chemical and biological engineering at RPI, has been named head of RPI’s Howard P. Isermann Department of Chemical and Biological Engineering (CBE). Under Przybycien’s leadership, the department will continue to drive innovation in sustainable biopharmaceutical manufacturing, metabolic and enzyme engineering, advanced materials development, transport processes, and process systems engineering.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2025/08/25/todd-przybycien-named-head-rpis-howard-p-isermann-department-chemical-and-biological</guid></item><item><title>Pingkun Yan Named Head of RPI’s Department of Biomedical Engineering</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2025/08/25/pingkun-yan-named-head-rpis-department-biomedical-engineering</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI) has appointed Pingkun Yan, Ph.D., the P.K. Lashmet Career Development Chair Associate Professor at the Department of Biomedical Engineering at RPI, as head of the Department of Biomedical Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2025/08/25/pingkun-yan-named-head-rpis-department-biomedical-engineering</guid></item><item><title>Arts Sr. Lecturer Ken Ragsdale’s new exhibition “Symphony” at Hudson’s Front Room Gallery is earning critical acclaim</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/arts-sr-lecturer-ken-ragsdales-new-exhibition-symphony-hudsons-front-room-gallery</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Arts Sr. Lecturer Ken Ragsdale’s new exhibition “Symphony” at Hudson’s Front Room Gallery is earning critical acclaim! Hyperallergic’s Taliesin Thomas calls it “impressive” and “elegant,” while Musée Magazine’s Yu Lam Yau praises its “remarkably singular vision that immediately compels and intrigues.” Visit the Front Room Gallery this week to experience Ragsdale’s work in person. The show ends August 31.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/arts-sr-lecturer-ken-ragsdales-new-exhibition-symphony-hudsons-front-room-gallery</guid></item><item><title>Apple Back-to-School Promotion (6/25-9/30)</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/apple-back-school-promotion</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Apple Back-to-School Promotion is back! Running from June 25 until September 30, 2025, the Rensselaer community can enjoy FREE Apple AirPods 4 Active Noise Cancelling (ANC) with the purchase of an eligible iMac or MacBook -or- FREE Apple Pencil Pro with the purchase of an eligible iPad Air or iPad Pro. Check out rensselaerstore.com to see what eligible devices are available. When you add an eligible device to your cart, you must also add the FREE item to your cart for the promotion to be…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/apple-back-school-promotion</guid></item><item><title>Founders Award Nomintations Due</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-52bb2328-00003e04calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, August 4, 2025 - Fri , August 29, 2025 (all day) - The Founders Award of Excellence was established in 1994 to honor students who embody the qualities of creativity, discovery, and leadership, and the values of pride and responsibility at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute. Eligible nominees must be enrolled as a sophomore, junior, senior, fifth-year architecture student, or graduate student in the fall semester of 2025. Nominations should be submitted via emailed Qualtrics Form no…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-52bb2328-00003e04calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 RPI Faculty and Staff Teaching and Learning Workshops/Webinars Schedule Available</title><link>https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-2025-rpi-faculty-and-staff-teaching-and-learning-workshopswebinars-schedule</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Teaching and Learning Collaboratory has just announced the upcoming trainings for RPI faculty and staff for the Fall 2025 term. Please be sure to visit the training page link for a listing of sessions, dates, times, and links to register!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-2025-rpi-faculty-and-staff-teaching-and-learning-workshopswebinars-schedule</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff In-Person Workshop: Get Wise with the Owl | Sept. 15</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-be9f4a82-00007d88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 15, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Discover how to make the most of your Meeting Owl! Whether your department already has an Owl or you’re considering one, this hands-on workshop will walk you through everything you need to know — from setup and placement to an overview of benefits and key features like 360° video, automatic speaker tracking, and pairing devices. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:24 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-be9f4a82-00007d88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
