<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Counseling Center Announces Walk-in Counseling Hours for Fall 2024</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/walk-counseling-hours-fall-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer’s Counseling Center invites students to meet with a counselor without a formal appointment, during the two designated walk-in hours that are available each day: Mondays, Wednesdays and Fridays from 10AM to noon, and Tuesdays and Thursdays from 2PM to 4PM. Walk-in counseling is available on a first-come, first-served basis on days when classes are in session. Students who cannot attend walk-in times can call (518) 276-6479 to schedule an appointment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/walk-counseling-hours-fall-2024</guid></item><item><title>“Learn How a Nuclear Submarine Works” Seminar Scheduled for September 18</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-b96f1a2e-00007ee8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM - If you’ve ever wanted to know how a nuclear-powered submarine works, attend this session in the CBIS Isermann Auditorium for a discussion and Q&amp;amp;A opportunity! Like spacecrafts here on Earth, these amazing ships operate submerged and independent for months at a time; this session will focus on the submarines’ nuclear reactor, key engineering systems, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-b96f1a2e-00007ee8calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Announces Western Digital HDD Teardown Workshop</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2686</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled from 4:00PM to 5:00PM on September 24 in the Rensselaer Union’s Shelnutt Gallery, this hands-on workshop related to data storage gives students the opportunity to learn about the cloud, including the various types of storage devices and the considerations that are most important for the cloud. Participants will also disassemble an actual hard-drive and discuss the engineering behind it. Space is limited to 25, so &lt;a href="https://app.joinhandshake.com/login"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2686</guid></item><item><title>SWE to Host “Evening with Industry”</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-2335f4fe-00003dc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 25, 2024 7:30 PM - 9:30 PM - If you’re an RPI student looking for an internship or job, join the Society of Women Engineers for this free “Evening with Industry” event to meet recruiters from companies who are looking to hire. Please note that the event will be capped at about 60 students.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-2335f4fe-00003dc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Thinking about Off-Campus Housing?</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-dc3c09a1-00005896calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 19, 2024 11:00 AM - 1:00 PM - Staff from the Off-Campus Commons will be available to answer juniors’, seniors’, and graduate students’ questions and offer information about the resources that are available in the Housing Search. Stop by to ask questions, and enter the raffle while you’re there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-dc3c09a1-00005896calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>First Game Jam of the Year Starting September 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/september-game-jam-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Game Dev Club is hosting its first Game Jam of the year starting on Friday, September 20 at 5pm in Sage 2411! Kick off the fall and join us once again (or for the first time!) for a 48-hour jam, with overnight breaks beginning at 10:00 PM both Friday and Saturday nights and doors opening again at 8:00 AM each morning. Teams will be formed to design your own game from scratch. Students of all years, areas of study, and experience levels are welcome to participate!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/september-game-jam-0</guid></item><item><title>Fellowship Info Session to Highlight Competitions for Grad School Salary and Tuition</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-5705c8e3-0000050acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 20, 2024 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - Competitive fellowships provide salary and tuition for Masters and PhD students. All graduate students, juniors, seniors, and international students are welcome to &lt;a href="https://rpi.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_5q1McRZJMkpb0G2"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; for this session to learn how to find and apply to appropriate programs that will fund fall 2025 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-5705c8e3-0000050acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Memorial Service Scheduled for Trustee Emeritus Neal Barton ’58, ’63G, ’66 Ph.D.</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c3a871ca-00006321calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 26, 2024 1:30 PM - 3:00 PM - A memorial service for Trustee Emeritus Neal Barton ’58, ’63G, ’66 Ph.D. will be held from 1:30PM to 3:00PM at Rensselaer’s Chapel and Cultural Center, located at 2125 Burdett Avenue in Troy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c3a871ca-00006321calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Evelyn’s Café Now Open for Lunch Service on Wednesdays</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-dda368e7-00006aa0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 11:00 AM - 2:00 PM - EMPAC invites you to Evelyn’s Café for lunch with a view! Located on EMPAC’s Level 5 beneath the hull of the building’s Concert Hall, the space offers sweeping views, as well as a tempting outdoor terrace, and is always open during EMPAC building hours for studying, relaxing, and gatherings. Café service is available 11AM to 2PM on Wednesdays when classes are in session.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-dda368e7-00006aa0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>American Welding Society, Wire-Arc Additive Manufacturing Event to be Held September 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e6830939-00005cc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 19, 2024 3:00 PM - 7:00 PM - The Manufacturing Innovation Center will host the American Welding Society and SERVO-ROBOT for a conference and demonstration of Wire-Arc Additive Manufacturing, robotic welding and advanced sensors for welding automation. Please &lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/rpi-x-servo-robot-wire-arc-additive-manufacturing-demonstration-tickets-983937281897?aff=oddtdtcreator"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0191-e6830939-00005cc0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rajani Bhatia to Speak at STS Colloquium September 18</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-speaker-rajani-bhatia</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled from from 11:30am to 1pm in Sage 5711, this talk argues that, in the context of intensifying climate change impacts, populationist thinking and agendas tempt broad audiences by providing an easy scapegoat. Analyzing how mainstream and extreme rhetoric on population amplify one another, Bhatia turns to feminist critics of population control to affirm the possibility of another future based on the vision articulated by reproductive and environmental justice movements.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-speaker-rajani-bhatia</guid></item><item><title>Golf Opens 2024-25 Season at The Gauntlet</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/15/golf-opens-fall-season-at-the-gauntlet.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, September 15, the Rensselaer golf team opened its 2024-2025 season at the Gauntlet on the 6,295-yard, par 70 Bucknell Golf Course in Lewisburg, Pennsylvania. The Engineers, ranked 33rd nationally by the Golf Coaches Association of America (GCAA), put out an experienced lineup, with all five players seeing significant tournament play last year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/15/golf-opens-fall-season-at-the-gauntlet.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Continue Graduate Certificate Review Sessions September 19</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8fedc273-00005283calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 19, 2024 3:00 PM - 3:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for this information session highlighting the whole range of Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs. Three courses in length, developing targeted ability groups, and able to be completed in as little as seven months, the certificates can add up to a customized, career-aligned master’s degree. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/certs16"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-8fedc273-00005283calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Mercer XLab Grand Renovation Opening Event to be Held September 25</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/bicentennial-event-september-25th-mercer-xlab-grand-renovation-opening</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Attend this event featuring the Douglas A. Mercer ’77 Innovation and Exploration Laboratory ribbon-cutting ceremony, an XCorridor of Student Creativity and Community reception with refreshments served, and a panel discussion on the convergence of AI and higher education regarding human behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/bicentennial-event-september-25th-mercer-xlab-grand-renovation-opening</guid></item></channel></rss>
