<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:36:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CCPD Virtual Summer Series: Velan Studios | June 03</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-virtual-summer-series-velan-studios-june-03</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Velan Studios will be hosting a virtual info session on Tuesday, June 3rd, 2025 to discuss life at the company and their internship and co-op opportunities! Log on and learn more about available opportunities with them. This session will begin at 4:30pm and is 45 minutes in duration. Additional details, registration, and available positions can be found in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:36:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-virtual-summer-series-velan-studios-june-03</guid></item><item><title>Analytics, Machine Learning &amp; AI Information Session with Rensselaer at Work | June 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-96ac81ec-0196-d440993d-00004439calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, June 3, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., on a 30-minute information session highlighting Rensselaer online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning &amp;amp; AI. Expect to learn how data can inform better decisions and review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please complete the form below if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:36:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-96ac81ec-0196-d440993d-00004439calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Surfing the Manifold: Adventures in Latent Space with David Rokeby | June 4</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/surfing-manifold-adventures-latent-space-david-rokeby</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As they learn, AI systems build rich and nuanced fields of possibilities, often called latent spaces. At BMO Lab we love to make this latent space tangible and explorable. Director of the BMO Lab, David Rokeby, will do live demonstrations of a few of the systems the lab has been developing, and there will be a chance for attendees to interact with them themselves. Join us on June 4 from 4-6pm in the CBIS Auditorium.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:36:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/surfing-manifold-adventures-latent-space-david-rokeby</guid></item><item><title>Fiscal Year 2026 Holiday Schedule is Now Available</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/fiscal-year-2026-holiday-schedule-now-available</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer is pleased to offer 10 paid employee holidays during the 2026 fiscal year (July 1, 2025 – June 30, 2026). As part of this, the Institute will be closed for the Holiday Winter Break from Wednesday, December 24, 2025, through Friday, January 2, 2026, and will reopen and resume normal operations on Monday, January 5, 2026. The full Holiday Schedule, including Winter Break Appreciation Days, for FY26 can be found at https://hr.rpi.edu/benefits/paid-time-holidays.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:36:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/fiscal-year-2026-holiday-schedule-now-available</guid></item><item><title>Teaching During the Summer Semester? Please Complete Your Syllabus in HelioCampus</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/teaching-during-summer-semester-please-complete-your-syllabus-heliocampus</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Just a quick reminder to please complete your syllabus in HelioCampus. Based on the requirements from the Provost’s office, faculty should have their syllabi published in HelioCampus by June 2, 2025. HelioCampus will publish all syllabi automatically on June 9, 2025. If you need assistance, contact oira@rpi.edu or speak with your department or school administrator who assists with HelioCampus. You can access the Institute Syllabus Template on RPI Info&amp;gt;Faculty and Staff Resources&amp;gt;Syllabus…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:36:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/teaching-during-summer-semester-please-complete-your-syllabus-heliocampus</guid></item><item><title>CDPHP Cycle is Back!</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/cdphp-cycle-back</link><description>&lt;p&gt;CDPHP Cycle! Season 9 is here! Visit https://www.cdphpcycle.org/ for information, bike locations and to download the app or search “CDPHP Cycle” in your smartphone app store. Use your RPI email address and promo code GoRed for special rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:36:17 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/cdphp-cycle-back</guid></item></channel></rss>
