<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:35:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>DotCIO to Host Retirement Party for Jeff Miner July 12</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-host-retirement-party-jeff-miner-july-12</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 1:00 PM to 4:00 PM on Friday, July 12 in the Heffner Alumni House Great Hall, all members of the campus community are welcome to join DotCIO in extending their best wishes to Jeff Miner, who is retiring after his many years of dedicated service here at Rensselaer. Please be sure to &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/rsvp-jeffrey-miners-retirement-party"&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; by Wednesday, July 3.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-host-retirement-party-jeff-miner-july-12</guid></item><item><title>“Center of Gravity” Series Continues June 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-87e4177a-00001b6ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 26, 2024 4:00 PM - 10:00 PM - The Center of Gravity is your one-stop for personal, academic and well-being success this summer! Activities include novelty food and snacks, academic support from peer tutors and course TAs, away semester searches with the CCPD, wellness and well-being activities, water coloring, Legos, book clubs and more, so be sure to visit weekly!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-87e4177a-00001b6ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Be a Part of the Incoming RPI Student Sendoff!</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22878&amp;ecid=22878&amp;ciid=79412&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 1PM to 3PM on Sunday, August 11 at Pat’s Barn in the Rensselaer Technology Park, come join the RPI Alumni Chapter of Hudson Mohawk to meet and welcome local first-year students from the Class of 2028! It’s a great way to enjoy food and refreshments while making connections, sharing stories, and networking with our newest class. The cost is $10 per person; all local current and incoming RPI students area are invited free of charge courtesy of the Hudson Mohawk Chapter alumni.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=22878&amp;ecid=22878&amp;ciid=79412&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>“Remembering the Stonewall Uprising – 55 Years Later” Exhibit on Display in Folsom Library</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-3c597c8b-00001908calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, June 21, 2024 5:00 PM - Sun , July 21, 2024 7:00 PM - On June 28, 1969, LGBTQ+ patrons at the Stonewall Inn in New York fought back against police harassment, helping to spawn the LGBTQIA+ rights movement. To honor this event, the LGBTQ+ Task Force is proud to present an exhibit on the history of the Stonewall Uprising on the main floor of Folsom Library, using archival sources from the Stonewall National Museum, Archives, and Library to show the Uprising’s important history.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-0190-3c597c8b-00001908calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Off-Campus Housing Series Continues with Pizza Time June 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-2b6d622a-00002f11calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 26, 2024 12:00 PM - 2:00 PM - Stop by with your friends and have a slice of pizza, all while learning about off-campus housing options with Amicus Properties! The Associate Dean for Off-Campus Commons will also be available to answer questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-2b6d622a-00002f11calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Brunch with Benefits (IN-PERSON) with CDPHP!</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/brunch-benefits-person-cdphp</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the Division of Human Resources and CDPHP IN-PERSON on Thursday, June 27 at 11am at the CBIS Bruggeman Room for this month’s Brunch with Benefits session: “Getting the Most From Your Health Plan.” Learn how to use your health plan, plus get the full scoop on programs and services that will help you save money, improve your health and have lunch. Registration is REQUIRED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/brunch-benefits-person-cdphp</guid></item></channel></rss>
