<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Campus Community Invited to Cybersecurity Meetup with FBI, ISC2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-b7104493-0000484fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 24, 2024 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM - All are welcome to join the Rensselaer Cybersecurity Collaboratory and DotCIO in Carnegie 113 for the first meeting of the new ISC2 Capital District NY Chapter, which will meet monthly. This month, Samantha Baltzersen, Supervisory Special Agent in Charge of Cyber for Albany FBI Field Office, will give a talk. Please &lt;a href="mailto:callab5@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Dr. Callahan&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-b7104493-0000484fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Quantum Computing Users Group Meeting</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-meeting</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Quantum Computing Users Group will meet on Wednesday, July 31st, from noon to 1 pm, in Amos Eaton 214. A number of our members are attending the IBM Qiskit Summer School. Their experiences and other topics the group is interested in will be discussed. Please join us! RSVP: Tom Morgan, morgat5@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-meeting</guid></item><item><title>Tanglewood Music Center’s Fromm Quartet to Perform at EMPAC</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/18/tanglewood-music-centers-fromm-quartet-perform-empac-rpi</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Presented by RPI, the Tanglewood Music Center’s Fromm Quartet will perform “Storytelling and Memory” at the Curtis R. Priem Experimental Music and Performing Arts Center (EMPAC) on Friday, August 2 at 7:00PM, featuring works by members of Tanglewood’s composition faculty and co-directors of the Festival of Contemporary Music. Please &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/storytelling-memory-tanglewood-music-center"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; for free admission!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/07/18/tanglewood-music-centers-fromm-quartet-perform-empac-rpi</guid></item><item><title>Arts Department to Present “Transcroporeality” Installation at EMPAC</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/transcroporeality</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, July 26, 2024 – “Transcroporeality” is a trial of immersive multi-modal work by Allie Wist that incorporates smell and video related to the anthropocene, microplastics, hybrid geology, and late industrialisms. Most information about ecological demise is depicted through data or visuals, and this installation attempts to prioritize more embodied contact points with Anthropogenic changes to the environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/transcroporeality</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Virtual Summer Series Continues with Crane Currency Info Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2632</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the team at Crane Currency from 6:30PM to 7:30PM on Thursday, July 25 to learn about career paths and company culture within the organization, as well as upcoming opportunities for Arch students seeking an Away experience! Also please review the&lt;a href="https://rpi.joinhandshake.com/edu/jobs/8907483"&gt;Chemical Engineering R&amp;amp;D Internship or Co-Op opportunity&lt;/a&gt; posted in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2632</guid></item><item><title>Summer Outdoor Program Series to Include River Tubing Trip</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-aab4dab6-000024a4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, July 27, 2024 11:00 AM - 4:00 PM - Arch students are invited to join the Mueller Center’s river tubing trip, which will take place on the Battenkill River, located on the New York/Vermont border! This trip is limited to ten participants and registration is required; please look for information and registration on the Muller Center’s Instagram page, or &lt;a href="mailto:weinew2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Will Weinert&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-aab4dab6-000024a4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Summer Arch 2024 NYC Trip Slated for July 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90976b31-0190-a806c949-000019c0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, July 27, 2024 8:00 AM - The Class of 2026 Council and The Arch Summer Ambassadors would like to invite current Arch students to join them for a day in New York City. Space is limited and registration is required, so &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeNSWwU4gQnmtovupuP2aSdG0RELQmsew7YK4d2eYdAj8bG0g/viewform"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; soon!…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90976b31-0190-a806c949-000019c0calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Update: Time Changed for CCPD July 29 URP/Handshake Faculty Training Session</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/urphandshake-faculty-training-session-july-29</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday, July 29 from 2:00PM to 3:30PM in the CCPD conference room, the CCPD will host an interactive opportunity for faculty members to learn how to use Handshake for posting undergraduate research positions. Light snacks will be provided. Space is limited, so interested faculty should &lt;a href="https://webforms.rpi.edu/form/urp-handshake-training-7-29"&gt;submit a registration webform&lt;/a&gt; to sign up as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/urphandshake-faculty-training-session-july-29</guid></item></channel></rss>
