<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:32:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Ph.D. Hooding Ceremony 2025 | May 9</title><link>https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/phd-hooding-ceremony-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When: Friday, May 9, 2025 Where: EMPAC - Concert Hall Check-in starts- at 7:45 AM ( coffee will be served) Ceremony- at 8:30 AM Refreshments- after the ceremony concludes. The hooding ceremony is a unique recognition of the achievement of each student who has earned a doctorate. Each doctoral candidate is introduced individually during the ceremony. They will have their hood placed on them while standing on the stage in the concert hall.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://graduate.rpi.edu/announcements/phd-hooding-ceremony-2025</guid></item><item><title>Handshake’s Just In Time Engineering Virtual Career Fair | May 9</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/handshakes-just-time-engineering-virtual-career-fair-may-9-2025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to explore exciting opportunities and connect with industry leaders? This VIRTUAL engineering-focused fair is the perfect opportunity to do so! Join Handshake, the CCPD, and other schools across the country on Friday, May 9, 2025 between 12-3pm to network with employers who are eager to recruit for internships, co-ops, and full-time positions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/handshakes-just-time-engineering-virtual-career-fair-may-9-2025</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Reviews Single Course Enrollment Options for Summer Term | May 6</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5ef1ddff-00003bfbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, May 6, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., will host this Rensselaer at Work information session reviewing the online graduate programs for working professionals and provide course enrollment options to make an immediate impact on one’s work. Participants can also explore courses for developing valuable skills that benefit employee and employer alike. Please register to attend&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5ef1ddff-00003bfbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Arch Summer Kick-Off Event | May 19 at 12 PM</title><link>https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/arch-summer-kick-event-may-19-12-2-pm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting at 12PM, you are invited to kick off the Arch Summer featuring a fun BBQ, good company, inflatable obstacle course, and great music by DJ Kev! It’s a perfect opportunity to relax, connect with the community, and celebrate the start of the season together. Be sure to visit the Resource tent, where you can find student support offices and grab some free swag!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/arch-summer-kick-event-may-19-12-2-pm</guid></item><item><title>From Systems to Satellites: How Don Thoma ’83 Blends Innovation and Safety to Lead in Aerospace</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/systems-satellites-how-don-thoma-83-blends-innovation-and-safety-lead-aerospace</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Alumni Spotlight! Don Thoma blends systems thinking with bold leadership as CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of Aireon, revolutionizing air traffic surveillance from space. His advice? “Step in. Be curious. Solve problems.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/systems-satellites-how-don-thoma-83-blends-innovation-and-safety-lead-aerospace</guid></item><item><title>You’re Invited to a Special Fireside Chat: May 9</title><link>https://commencement.rpi.edu/announcements/youre-invited-special-fireside-chat-presidents-commencement-colloquy-driving</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Martin A. Schmidt ’81, Ph.D., and his wife, Lyn, invite you to the President’s Commencement Colloquy, a special Fireside Chat featuring Lisa Su, Ph.D., chair and CEO of AMD, TIME’s CEO of the Year, and one of TIME’s 100 Most Influential People in AI. Don’t miss this opportunity to hear firsthand from two visionary leaders about driving technology innovation in industry. This free event is open to the public and will be followed by a reception with refreshments in Evelyn’s Café.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://commencement.rpi.edu/announcements/youre-invited-special-fireside-chat-presidents-commencement-colloquy-driving</guid></item><item><title>Student Success Announced 2025 Last Lecture Speakers</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/2025lastlecture</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Over 300 graduating seniors chose Christianna Bennett, Ron Hedden, Benjamin Weissman, Wes Turner, and Sarah Parker Ward for the Class of 2025 Last Lecture Series. Inspired by Dr. Randy Pausch’s tradition, five 20-minute talks will be held, followed by a reception. The event is open to the Rensselaer community, with priority for graduating students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/2025lastlecture</guid></item></channel></rss>
