<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>ECSE Schedules Co-Term/BS-PhD Info Session</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-1ef5f21d-0000008ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 2, 2024 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Attend this session in JEC 6012 to learn more about ECSE’s Co-term/BS-PhD program! Students interested in Co-term will want to apply during the first semester of their senior year; those interested in BS-PhD should apply in their junior year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-1ef5f21d-0000008ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Student Health Center Provides Students with Viral Upper Respiratory Infection Guidance for Fall 2024</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/viral-uri-guidance-fall-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Viral upper respiratory infections or URIs, often known as “the common cold,” are illnesses caused by one of a variety of different pathogens, including rhinoviruses, adenoviruses, and coronaviruses like Covid-19. Rensselaer’s Student Health Center recently passed along some information about recognizing and managing URI symptoms, as well as warning signs that indicate you should schedule an appointment with the Health Center or with your primary care provider.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/viral-uri-guidance-fall-2024</guid></item><item><title>NSBE/SHPE 46th Annual Career Fair Opens</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-2a49f17a-00000dadcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 26, 2024 10:00 AM - 4:00 PM - Still trying to figure out what you will be doing next summer? Or are you graduating but still not sure where you would like to work? Why not come and see over 150 companies that will be attendance at this year’s Career Fair? It’s still not too late to register via Handshake to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-2a49f17a-00000dadcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Applications Now Open for 2024-2025 Barry Goldwater Scholarship</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/23/2024/applications-now-open-2024-2025-barry-goldwater-scholarship</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Established by Congress in 1986 to foster and encourage excellence in science and mathematics, the Barry Goldwater Scholarship and Excellence in Education Foundation runs an educational scholarship program designed to provide opportunities for U.S. undergraduate students with strong academic records and outstanding research potential. The pre-application deadline is Monday, November 25, 2024; the final application deadline for nominated students is Monday, January 20, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/23/2024/applications-now-open-2024-2025-barry-goldwater-scholarship</guid></item><item><title>CCPD: RPI-Only Info Table with Fast Enterprises Scheduled for October 1</title><link>https://app.joinhandshake.com/events/1595001/share_preview</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From 10:30AM to 12:30PM on Tuesday, October 1, students are invited to stop by the 15th Street lobby in the Rensselaer Union, and speak to representatives from Fast Enterprises to learn how to become a “FASTie,” an energetic, intelligent, enthusiastic person who works at Fast Enterprises! The company works directly with governments to implement essential software used to administer a wide range of programs, and offers commercial software that helps agencies in a variety of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.joinhandshake.com/events/1595001/share_preview</guid></item><item><title>SWE to Hold Professional Body Meeting with FAST Enterprises</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-9217650f-00007b89calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 1, 2024 2:30 PM - 4:00 PM - Join the Society of Women engineers for a late lunch and to learn more about professional information topics hosted by Fast Enterprises!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-9217650f-00007b89calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Research Tools &amp; Techniques” Symposium Scheduled for October 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-0783665d-00003caecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 2, 2024 2:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Discover the magic of research tools with the Graduate Student Council’s upcoming symposium in the CBIS Auditorium that will explore essential apps, workflows, and services that streamline your graduate studies and your personal life. Don’t miss this opportunity to learn, share, and connect with fellow researchers!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-0783665d-00003caecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Rensselaereum: An Exhibit of 200 Years of RPI History” Opening September 27</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90976b31-0190-a753f8c5-00007157calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 27, 2024 6:00 PM - Tue , December 31, 2024 12:00 AM - An exhibit featuring the work of 14 RPI School of Architecture students will be presented in the windows of the Chasan Building in downtown Troy at 405 Broadway. Exhibit opening on September 27 at 6 p.m. and the exhibit will be on display through December 2024.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90976b31-0190-a753f8c5-00007157calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI Space, Science, and Technology Day to be Held September 30</title><link>https://eng.rpi.edu/rpi-space-science-and-technology-day</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 30, 2024 8:00 AM - 6:00 PM - As part of its Bicentennial celebration, Rensselaer will be hosting RPI Space, Science and Technology Day! During the event, multiple RPI astronautics and alums who have become international leaders in the world’s space effort will address the rapid development of commercial space science and technology, highlight current RPI research in space science and technology, and celebrate the Institute’s long history in the exploration of space.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://eng.rpi.edu/rpi-space-science-and-technology-day</guid></item><item><title>Student Health Center Posts Mpox Update for Fall 2024</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/mpox-update-fall-2024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mpox is a viral illness that can be spread between people or between people and certain animals, and generally causes mild flu-like symptoms and a rash. On August 14, the World Health Organization declared the mpox outbreak as a public health emergency of international concern in the Democratic Republic of the Congo and neighboring countries. Although the current risk to Rensselaer is very low, the campus should be aware of the disease and note what can be done to prevent an outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/mpox-update-fall-2024</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Researcher Receives $3 Million Grant to Explore Gut Health</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/09/19/rensselaer-researcher-receives-3-million-grant-explore-gut-health</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Blanca Barquera’s investigation into the energy-generating processes of Bacteroides, the most abundant member of the gut microbiome, and their impact on our well-being holds the promise of significant advancements in human health. Barquera is a professor in Rensselaer’s departments of Biological Sciences and Chemistry and Chemical Biology.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/09/19/rensselaer-researcher-receives-3-million-grant-explore-gut-health</guid></item><item><title>Heffner Alumni House Parking Lot Closed Through Sunday</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23206&amp;ecid=23206&amp;ciid=80533&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All members of the campus community should note that the parking lot behind the Heffner Alumni House will be closed all week through Sunday, September 29 for Reunion &amp;amp; Homecoming set-up and festivities. Drivers will need to find an alternate parking location.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=252&amp;cid=23206&amp;ecid=23206&amp;ciid=80533&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>Collegiate Store Announces Hours for Reunion &amp; Homecoming Weekend 2024</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/collegiate-store/09/24/2024/reunion-homecoming-weekend-2024-hours</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer Collegiate Store will have extended hours from Friday, September 27 through Sunday, September 29 for the upcoming Reunion &amp;amp; Homecoming Weekend. The store is located on the lower level of the Rensselaer Student Union at the corner of 15th Street and Sage Avenue.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/collegiate-store/09/24/2024/reunion-homecoming-weekend-2024-hours</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC Fall Building Tours to Begin September 28</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/fall-building-tours</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Each of EMPAC’s tours takes visitors behind the scenes to experience the center’s infrastructure as few do, so plan to join Associate Director Jonas Braasch for a free public tour of the building at 1:00PM on Saturday, September 28. Each tour is hosted by an EMPAC staff member with a different area of expertise, so there’s always something new to learn and discover! Tours begin in the main lobby and run approximately 90 minutes; please arrive 15 minutes before tour time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/fall-building-tours</guid></item><item><title>Rebecca Taylor Joins Women’s Hockey Coaching Staff</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/19/womens-ice-hockey-rebecca-taylor-joins-womens-hockey-coaching-staff.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rensselaer women’s ice hockey team has named Rebecca Taylor assistant coach. Taylor, who arrives in Troy after spending 2023-24 as an assistant coach at Curry College, was part of an impressive turnaround in her one season with the Colonels women’s hockey program, improving from 34 goals scored in 2022-23 to 61 goals netted this past winter.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/9/19/womens-ice-hockey-rebecca-taylor-joins-womens-hockey-coaching-staff.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Engineering student brings bioinspired armor to Wikipedia</title><link>https://wikiedu.org/blog/2024/09/06/engineering-student-brings-bioinspired-armor-to-wikipedia/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Bioinspired armor – it may sound like something out of a science fiction novel, but what exactly is it? Thanks to the brand-new &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bioinspired_armor"&gt;Wikipedia article&lt;/a&gt; Liv Vizzini and her classmates at Rensselaer created this spring, our curiosity can be satisfied.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://wikiedu.org/blog/2024/09/06/engineering-student-brings-bioinspired-armor-to-wikipedia/</guid></item><item><title>TIAA Confidential In-Person Retirement Counseling Sessions to be Held October 1</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6fb44d84-00006c0acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, October 1, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - A TIAA Financial Consultant will be available for one-on-one consultations on a broad range of retirement topics. Attend this upcoming event to help you become better informed and more confident about Rensselaer’s retirement plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6fb44d84-00006c0acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
