<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Deadline Approaching for December 2024 Late Degree Application</title><link>https://registrar.rpi.edu/announcements/deadline-december-2024-late-degree-application</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The late application deadline for December 2024 graduation is Friday, October 25. The Registrar’s Office won’t accept any applications after that date, so apply today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://registrar.rpi.edu/announcements/deadline-december-2024-late-degree-application</guid></item><item><title>Engineering Ambassadors Recruitment Open as of October 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-4f3b0ebf-00003defcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, October 7, 2024 12:00 AM - Tue , November 12, 2024 12:00 AM - Attention, all freshmen and sophomores! Applications are now open for the Engineering Ambassadors, a group that works with local schools to promote STEM exploration and make engineering more accessible to a younger audience. A recruitment information session will be held from 6PM to 7PM on November 12 in JEC 3232 to allow interested students to learn more about the organization and meet current Ambassadors.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-4f3b0ebf-00003defcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Second Game Jam to be Held October 25</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/october-game-jam</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Game Dev Club is hosting its second Game Jam of the year starting on Friday, October 25 at 5pm in VAST (Sage 2411). Please join us once again (or for the first time!) for a 48-hour jam (with overnight breaks beginning at 10:00 PM both Friday and Saturday nights with doors opening again at 8:00 AM each morning). Teams will be formed to design their own game from scratch. Students of all years, areas of study, and experience levels are welcome to participate!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/october-game-jam</guid></item><item><title>Special Chemistry Seminar Scheduled for October 28</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-bad74839-0000772bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, October 28, 2024 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - This special seminar will be presented by R. Andrew Byrd, of UConn’s Department of Molecular Biology and Biophysics, and National Cancer Institute NIH Scientist Emeritus, who will speak on “Surface Dancing: Peripheral Membrane Complexes at the Surface–Challenges for Integrated Structural Biology.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-bad74839-0000772bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty Seeking Feedback with Home Energy Efficiency Survey</title><link>https://research.rpi.edu/announcements/home-energy-efficiency-survey</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join a team of Rensselaer faculty who are helping to shape the future of eco-friendly home energy efficiency by developing siding material made from hemp that can boost home comfort and energy efficiency! Campus community members are invited to take a quick &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/gPstCHusUEmdn25k6"&gt;survey&lt;/a&gt; to provide feedback to help the team tailor this groundbreaking product.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://research.rpi.edu/announcements/home-energy-efficiency-survey</guid></item><item><title>United Way to Hold Election Day Barbeque Fund Raiser</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-6dd568ef-0000332ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 5, 2024 2:30 PM - 5:30 PM - In conjunction with Sodexho, the Rensselaer United Way Campaign will hold an Election Day chicken barbeque fund raiser, featuring your choice of a full takeout-only meal for only $16! Please contact any of the United Way committee members to purchase your dinner(s) and also let them know what time you will pick up your food at EMPAC. Dinners must be paid in advance by cash, or with a check made to Rensselaer, by noon Tuesday, October 29.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-6dd568ef-0000332ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Be the Media” Workshop with Film Director Mark Decena Scheduled for October 25</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/be-media-workshop-film-director-mark-decena</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join HASS at 5pm on October 25 at The Sanctuary for Independent Media in North Troy for a “Be the Media” workshop and film screening with film director Mark Decena, Founder of Kontent Films and Director of “Farming While Black.” The film examines the historical plight of Black farmers in the United States, as well as the rising generation of Black farmers reclaiming their rightful ownership to land and reconnecting with their ancestral roots.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/be-media-workshop-film-director-mark-decena</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work to Host Systems Engineering &amp; Technology Management Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9afec06e-000020f1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 31, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Hosted by Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., this information session focuses on Rensselaer’s flexible, project-based, online Systems Engineering and Technology Management graduate degree that will help prepare decision-makers with broader and deeper capabilities in leading dynamic organizations. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/SETM31"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9afec06e-000020f1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Simonetti Wins 8K, RPI Places Second Overall at Geneseo</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/10/19/mens-cross-country-simonetti-wins-8k-rpi-places-second-overall-at-geneseo.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Vincent Simonetti of the Rensselaer men’s cross country team cross the line first in the men’s 8K on October 19 at the Mike Woods Invite hosted by SUNY Geneseo. Simonetti posted a winning time of 24:08, and his victory propelled the Engineers to a second place finish out of the 33 teams at the invitational.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/10/19/mens-cross-country-simonetti-wins-8k-rpi-places-second-overall-at-geneseo.aspx</guid></item><item><title>10 Everyday Apps That Put Your Data at Risk in 2024: How to Protect Yourself?</title><link>https://www.techopedia.com/everyday-apps-that-put-your-data-at-risk</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Brian Callahan, Director of Rensselaer’s Cybersecurity Collaboratory, offers some comments in this article, which appeared in the October 19 edition of Techopedia.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.techopedia.com/everyday-apps-that-put-your-data-at-risk</guid></item><item><title>Don’t Miss “I Dream” in Concert on November 1!</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/i-dream-concert</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, November 1, 2024 at 7:00 pm – In partnership with RPI, the Musical Dramatic Arts Foundation is proud to present a concert version of the musical “I Dream,” which tells the story of the final 36 hours of Martin Luther King Jr.’s life as seen through the eyes of his closest friend, Ralph Abernathy, as the Civil Rights leaders grappled with justice, identity, and the burden of leadership. &lt;a href="https://www.rpi.edu/bicentennial/i-dream"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://tickets.empac.rpi.edu/TheatreManager/1/online?performance=525"&gt;Buy tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2024/i-dream-concert</guid></item><item><title>NIGMS T32 Seminar Scheduled for October 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-ba018520-000010bacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, October 30, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Attend this seminar for a presentation by Dr. Ruogang Zhao, Associate Professor of Biomedical Engineering at the University at Buffalo, who will be discussing “Engineered fibrotic tissue models for disease modeling and drug testing.” Please &lt;a href="mailto:felchg@rpi.edu"&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; by October 28 with Gigi Felch to secure your spot!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-ba018520-000010bacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
