<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Calling all new students! Join us for RPI Libraries’ Open House (pssst… there’s ice cream and raffle prizes!) | Sept. 3</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/calling-all-new-students-join-us-rpi-libraries-open-house-pssst-theres-ice-cream-and</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, Sept 3 from 2-3:30pm. Enjoy some ice cream and enter to win raffle prizes from local establishments. Complete your raffle entry card by visiting each library station to learn about our services, including the library’s service desk, discovery tool, individual and group study rooms, interlibrary loan, LibKey Nomad, the Architecture Library, Institute Archives, and the Student Success Center.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/calling-all-new-students-join-us-rpi-libraries-open-house-pssst-theres-ice-cream-and</guid></item><item><title>Fellowship info Session to Highlight Competitions for Grad School Salary and Tuition | Sept. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-aeefb2db-000063d1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 3, 2025 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM - Competitive fellowships provide salary and tuition for masters and PhD students. Seniors and graduate students will learn how to find and apply to appropriate programs that will fund fall 2026 and beyond. Programs are available for all stages of your academic career. International students are welcome! Register for the virtual session. Email madige@rpi.edu for information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-aeefb2db-000063d1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>First Gen &amp; BIPOC Students Ice Cream Social | Sept 4th</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/first-gen-bipoc-students-ice-cream-socia-sept-4th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us in Academy Hall 4600 on Thursday, September 4th between 4-6 PM for some free ice cream! Meet faculty &amp;amp; staff who can help you throughout your time at RPI!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/first-gen-bipoc-students-ice-cream-socia-sept-4th</guid></item><item><title>CMDIS BYOND Build Your Own Nano Device Program | Sept. 15-Nov. 14 (Applications due by Sept. 5)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-426e8069-00001212calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 15, 2025 12:00 AM - Fri , November 14, 2025 12:00 AM - Fall 2025 Applications Now Open for CMDIS BYOND Build Your Own Nano Device Program. The Center for Materials, Devices and Integrated Systems’, Micro and NanoFabrication Clean Room, offers a four-module certificate program for undergraduates, an exciting opportunity for those planning to pursue a graduate degree or those looking to prepare for a professional career in microelectronics, medical, and energy industries…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9364e181-0194-426e8069-00001212calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Level Up with Lally Clubs | Sept. 4</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/level-lally-clubs</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for Level Up Lally on September 4th from 5:00–6:00 PM in Lally Hall 104! Kick off the semester by connecting with RCC and Lally’s top clubs, including Women in Business, Finance Club, and the Business Honors Society. Meet upperclassmen and alumni, learn how to get involved in real-world projects, and discover the club that best aligns with your goals. Contact: saunde2@rpi.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/level-lally-clubs</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources: Getting the Most from Percipio (Getting Started with Percipio: Navigation Q&amp;A) | Sept. 5</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-42bec315-00007b41calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, September 5, 2025 9:00 AM - 9:30 AM - This brief course is designed to help you get comfortable using Percipio, RPI’s digital learning platform. You’ll learn how to navigate the main dashboard, search for content, access assigned learning, and track your progress. We’ll also walk through common questions users have and show you where to find help when needed. Whether you’re brand new or just need a refresher, this session will ensure you’re ready to make the most of Percipio.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0198-42bec315-00007b41calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Analytics, Machine Learning &amp; AI Review | Sept. 9</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f89066-0000408dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 9, 2025 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., on a 30-minute information session highlighting Rensselaer online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning &amp;amp; AI. Expect to learn how data can inform better decisions and review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please RSVP if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-0198-c7f89066-0000408dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>iEAR Presents: Visiting Critic Lane Relyea | Sept. 10</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-visiting-critic-lane-relyea</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Visiting Critic Lane Relyea will give a lecture titled “Friendship, Community and Other Neoliberal Propaganda in Recent Art and Culture”. Lane Relyea is Associate Professor of Art Theory and Practice at Northwestern University. His essays and reviews have appeared in such magazines as Artforum, Afterall, Art in America, Flash Art, Frieze, Parkett, Modern Painters and Texte zur Kunst. Join us in the CBIS Auditorium at 5pm on Wednesday, September 10.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/iear-presents-visiting-critic-lane-relyea</guid></item><item><title>Fire Evacuation Drills to be Conducted in Residential Buildings</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/fire-evacuation-drills-be-conducted-residential-buildings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fire evacuation drills will take place in residential buildings during the first two weeks of the fall semester. These unannounced drills are required by New York State Fire Code and provide residents an opportunity to practice safe evacuation procedures.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/fire-evacuation-drills-be-conducted-residential-buildings</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Connect Through Conversations” Part 1</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-connect-through</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Much of a leader’s work is accomplished through daily conversations with team members and others. These interactions, especially the tough ones, often involve intensely personal feelings (on both sides) that have an impact on the practical outcome of the conversation and the personal connection between the leader and the person. Part 1 of 2.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-connect-through</guid></item><item><title>Webex: Recording to the Cloud and Storage Quota</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-recording-cloud-and-storage-quota</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As the semester begins, Multimedia Services recommends that all community members review any Webex recordings stored in the cloud. Each user has an allotted quota of storage space, and exceeding that quota will disallow recording to the cloud. Any recordings which are no longer required for future viewing or archival purposes should be removed. For assistance with Webex recording management, please submit a Help Desk request.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-recording-cloud-and-storage-quota</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff In-Person Workshop: Get Wise with the Owl | Sept. 15</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-be9f4a82-00007d88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, September 15, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Discover how to make the most of your Meeting Owl! Whether your department already has an Owl or you’re considering one, this hands-on workshop will walk you through everything you need to know — from setup and placement to an overview of benefits and key features like 360° video, automatic speaker tracking, and pairing devices. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-be9f4a82-00007d88calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
