<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:34:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>New at RPI Libraries: Tech &amp; Textile Research Tools</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/new-rpi-libraries-tech-textile-research-tools</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI Libraries is pleased to announce access to two newly added research tools: O’Reilly for Higher Education – A robust collection of e-books, videos, audiobooks, and curated expert playlists spanning technology and business fields, including programming, cybersecurity, project management, communications, and presentation skills. Textile Technology Complete – A full-text database covering the scientific and technological dimensions of textile production and processing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/new-rpi-libraries-tech-textile-research-tools</guid></item><item><title>Understanding Today’s Students: Practical tools to support learning, engagement, and well-being</title><link>https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/understanding-todays-students-practical-tools-support-learning-engagement-and-well</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mainstreaming Mental Wellbeing Taskforce, in collaboration with the Provost’s office and the Division of Human Resources, has developed a two workshop training series to provide RPI faculty and staff with practical tools for understanding today’s students and responding to their evolving needs. Registration for Spring 2026 sessions is open. Lunch is provided!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studenthealth.rpi.edu/announcements/understanding-todays-students-practical-tools-support-learning-engagement-and-well</guid></item></channel></rss>
