<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Three Minute Thesis Info Session | Jan 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-b86481e3-00003a0fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, January 23, 2026 12:30 PM - 1:00 PM - PhD students who are interested in participating in the Three Minute Thesis competition at RPI are invited to attend an information session to learn more about this program. Additional info can be found here: https://graduate.rpi.edu/three-minute-thesis-3mtr-competition&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-b86481e3-00003a0fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Lean Green Belt Certification - register by 1/16 for discount</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/lean-green-belt-certification-register-116-discount</link><description>&lt;p&gt;At the end of this month the Industrial Engineering Student Chapter will host the Lean Green Belt certification taught by MANE professor and Master Black Belt Dr. Ashish Ghosh! Lean Green Belt is a 3-day intensive course about Lean manufacturing, waste management, and engineering management. Any student is welcome to sign up! For a discounted price register by this Friday 1/16/26. Registration is open until the week of the course.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/lean-green-belt-certification-register-116-discount</guid></item><item><title>Off Campus Housing Search Support | Jan. 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-c225690c-00003e5bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Monday, January 26, 2026 11:30 AM - 1:30 PM - Off-Campus Services will be available to answer questions and provide support for an off-campus Housing Search. Stop by and meet the staff and Resources available.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-c225690c-00003e5bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPIRates Monthly Meeting - R Micro-bootcamp: Getting Started with R &amp; RStudio!” | Jan. 21</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/r-micro-bootcamp-getting-started-r-rstudio-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-21-jan-6p-ae217</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI R users are invited to the January meeting of RPIrates: The RPI R Users Group! Our topic for Weds, 21 Jan (6p, AE217) will be “Getting Started with R and RStudio!” led by Dr. John S. Erickson, DirResOps for the Rensselaer FOCI. This special session is designed for anyone who is new to R. We’ll review the R Studio IDE, R syntax, and R’s basic data structures; provide helpful tips for troubleshooting your code; and point to helpful tutorials and other resources that will lead to R success!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/r-micro-bootcamp-getting-started-r-rstudio-rpirates-monthly-meeting-weds-21-jan-6p-ae217</guid></item><item><title>ASCE Spring Kick Off Meeting</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-db89ba6a-0000152fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, January 22, 2026 6:00 PM - 7:00 PM - Join ASCE members for the first meeting of the semester. Representatives from WSP will be on hand to discuss what their firm does and the opportunities that they offer. This is a great way to network with professionals and spend time with fellow students. Refreshments will be served, (bring your own drink). Please note the room change for this semester, LOW 3130&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-db89ba6a-0000152fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Parking enforcement begins January 26, 2026</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/parking-enforcement-begins-january-26-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A variety of parking permit options are available to meet the needs of students, faculty, and staff. Please review the parking policies and make sure your vehicle information is up to date. If you have questions or need help getting a permit, contact Parking at parking@rpi.edu or 518-276-8528.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/parking-enforcement-begins-january-26-2026</guid></item><item><title>Campus Card Office Grand Opening</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/campus-card-office-grand-opening</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us at the Campus Card Office on Wednesday, January 21st between 11 am - 2 pm as we celebrate our move back into the Student Union Room 1502. We will have samples from Pepsi and snacks while supplies last. We look forward to seeing you!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/campus-card-office-grand-opening</guid></item><item><title>Radical Imagination: Person-Centric Approaches to Music Making</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/radical-imagination-person-centric-approaches-music-making</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Prize-winning composer, improviser, and multi-instrumentalist Nick Dunston brings his multiple musical talents to RPI on January 22 with a presentation on “Radical Imagination,” drawing on his prolific body of work spanning jazz, electro-acoustics, and sound art. Dunston views improvisation not merely as a skill, but as a practice that fundamentally shapes the artists who engage in it. Join at 7pm at West Hall 326.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/radical-imagination-person-centric-approaches-music-making</guid></item><item><title>Professor Alhussein (Hussein) Abouzeid Appointed the next Head of Electrical, Computer, and Systems Engineering</title><link>https://ecse.rpi.edu/news/professor-alhussein-hussein-abouzeid-appointed-next-head-electrical-computer-and-systems</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The ECSE Department is excited to welcome Prof. Abouzeid as our new department head effective Jan 1st, 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ecse.rpi.edu/news/professor-alhussein-hussein-abouzeid-appointed-next-head-electrical-computer-and-systems</guid></item><item><title>Annual State Fire Inspections Begin January 13</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/annual-state-fire-inspections-begin-january-13</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The New York State Office of Fire Prevention and Control (OFPC) conducts annual building inspections of all colleges and universities in New York State. This year, inspections of RPI’s academic and administrative buildings will begin on January 13 and are expected to take approximately six to seven weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/annual-state-fire-inspections-begin-january-13</guid></item><item><title>Webex Application Training Session on Friday January 23, 2026</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-application-training-session-friday-january-23-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on Friday, January 23, from 11am-12pm for a hands-on Webex Training Session, part of the MMS Collaboration Software Training series. This session focuses on the Webex application and its integration with Outlook and Blackboard, so you can efficiently schedule, launch, and manage meetings directly from the tools you use every day. Register now: https://rensselaer.webex.com/webappng/sites/rensselaer/webinar/webinarSeries/register/783d951c6ab8482e9198a7bd6075a700&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-application-training-session-friday-january-23-2026</guid></item><item><title>RPI Chemical Hygiene Plan</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-chemical-hygiene-plan</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI Chemical Hygiene Plan (CHP) is annually reviewed by EHS and the new version is available to all RPI Faculty, Staff, and Students on the EHS Chemical Safety website.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-chemical-hygiene-plan</guid></item><item><title>Teaching and Learning Collaboratory Faculty Call for Proposals: Submissions due March 9, 2026</title><link>https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory-faculty-call-proposals-submissions-due-march-9</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The OUE and the TLC invites proposals from full time tenure track faculty members or lecturers/Professors of Practice for piloting and assessing pedagogical innovations, especially those integrating interactive technologies into the classroom. We wish to fund seed projects that will serve as the foundation for external grant applications. Project proposals should entail the implementation of new interactive approaches, gaming, remote laboratories, or other innovative methods.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/teaching-and-learning-collaboratory-faculty-call-proposals-submissions-due-march-9</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff Webinar: Tips for Incorporating Digital Story Telling as Assignments</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-b887bf07-0000730ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, January 27, 2026 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - In this quick learn webinar, we will discuss a high overview of the meaning of digital story telling, advantages, story telling assignment practices, and review the Six-Word Story, Six Unique Shots assignment concept. Maureen Fodera (Office of Undergraduate Education) will be presenting this workshop. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9b28bc7c-019b-b887bf07-0000730ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty Staff Appreciation Lunch January 21st</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-january-21st</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to celebrate you! Please join us for a Faculty and Staff Appreciation Lunch on January 21 as a small thank-you for everything you do to support our campus community. On this special day, faculty and staff are invited to enjoy lunch for just $6 plus tax at Commons and Russell Sage Dining Halls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-staff-appreciation-lunch-january-21st</guid></item></channel></rss>
