<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Women’s Soccer Set to Host Prospect Day on September 22</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/8/12/womens-soccer-set-to-host-prospect-day-on-september-22.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI Women’s Soccer will be hosting a prospect day on Sunday, September 22 from 10am to 3:00pm at East Campus Athletic Village. Prospective student-athletes from the Classes of 2025, 2026, 2027, and 2028 who are interested in competing at the collegiate level are welcome to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/8/12/womens-soccer-set-to-host-prospect-day-on-september-22.aspx</guid></item><item><title>Book Your COMM+D Appointment Online!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/08/20/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you working on a writing assignment, oral presentation, or visual design project? Whether you’re at the beginning brainstorming stages or finishing up your final revisions, the Center for Global Communication+Design (Comm+D) can help! Just &lt;a href="https://rpi.mywconline.com/"&gt;schedule an appointment&lt;/a&gt; with a member of our trained staff, then stop by the Comm+D offices on the lower level of Folsom Library.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/08/20/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</guid></item><item><title>CCPD Announces Western Digital HDD Teardown Workshop</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2686</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Scheduled from 4:00PM to 5:00PM on September 24 in the Rensselaer Union’s Shelnutt Gallery, this hands-on workshop related to data storage gives students the opportunity to learn about the cloud, including the various types of storage devices and the considerations that are most important for the cloud. Participants will also disassemble an actual hard-drive and discuss the engineering behind it. Space is limited to 25, so &lt;a href="https://app.joinhandshake.com/login"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/node/2686</guid></item><item><title>Division of Finance Announces E-Business Name Change</title><link>https://finance.rpi.edu/announcements/division-finance-announces-e-business-name-change</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Eileen McLoughlin and Rensselaer’s Division of Finance are excited to announce that the E-Business Department has officially changed its name to the Finance Applications Systems and Technologies (FAST) Department. Since fully transitioning to AVP Kelli Perry’s team, the E-Business Department has grown to include multiple new applications, tools, and areas, and this new name better reflects the Department’s areas of focus and its mission to improve systems, tools, and processes for campus.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.rpi.edu/announcements/division-finance-announces-e-business-name-change</guid></item><item><title>LaTeX to be Topic of Graduate “Lunch and Learn” Session</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-97a8c4a4-000010c2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 12:00 PM - 2:30 PM - Professor Ali Tajer will highlight LaTeX, a high-quality typesetting system that includes features designed for producing technical and scientific documentation, and which is also the de facto standard for the communication and publication of scientific documents and doctoral dissertations. Lunch will be served from noon to 12:30.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90976c21-0190-97a8c4a4-000010c2calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Sarah Davachi to Present “Constants” at EMPAC</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c8f716d2-00004e03calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, September 18, 2024 7:00 PM - Join EMPAC for “Constants,” a concert by musician and composer Sarah Davachi! Performing a single work of electronic analog synthesizer-based music, Davachi will fill EMPAC’s Concert Hall with gradually transforming musical strata, inviting listeners to an inner world of sonic detail informed by minimalist tenets, formal concepts from early music, and experimental recording practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c8f716d2-00004e03calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>SoA to Host “24 Hours @ Once” Prototype Live Music Performance and Video Installation</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-d78418a8-0000551ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, September 14, 2024 4:00 PM - 10:00 PM - Dean Douglis and RPI’s School of Architecture will welcome and host this event, which explores human collectivity and temporality. The project features live video feeds from 24 time zones around the planet which will be simultaneously projected onto 24 screens, as live musical performances based on North Indian classical ragas corresponding to the hours of the Earth’s daily cycle take place.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-d78418a8-0000551ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>OUE Announces ChatGPT/AI Tools Informal Community Space</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/06/05/2024/chatgptai-tools-informal-community-space</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Undergraduate Education is pleased to announce that an informal community Webex space has been created to focus directly on AI tools being used in the classroom, and is available to share, collaborate, and brainstorm on this topic. Faculty, staff, or graduate TAs who would like to join this space should &lt;a href="mailto:foderm@rpi.edu?subject=Please%20add%20me%20to%20the%20ChatGPT%2FAI%20Tools%20Informal%20Webex%20Space"&gt;email Maureen Fodera&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/06/05/2024/chatgptai-tools-informal-community-space</guid></item><item><title>TIAA Holding Confidential In-Person Retirement Counseling Sessions September 17</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6fb36dad-00006b46calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 17, 2024 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM - A TIAA Financial Consultant will be available for one-on-one consultations on a broad range of retirement topics. Attend this upcoming event to help you become better informed and more confident about Rensselaer’s retirement plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-0190-6fb36dad-00006b46calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HR to Hold “4 Steps to Effective Communication: Extended DISC” Professional Development Workshop</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-4-steps-effective-1</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, participants will receive individualized Extended DISC reports (based on the completion of the Extended DISC questionnaire) that reflect both their “natural” and “adjusted” behavioral styles and learn strategies which promote successful interactions with others. Please &lt;a href="https://share.percipio.com/cd/dmKnMSEhl"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-4-steps-effective-1</guid></item><item><title>HR Professional Development Workshop, “Leading Virtually,” to be Held September 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-999afcb9-00007e2fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, September 26, 2024 9:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Virtual and remote work creates both challenges and opportunities to work as a cohesive team focused on achieving results. This seminar explores the fundamentals of Rensselaer’s Flexible Work Program, teaches leaders how to communicate more effectively in a virtual environment and focus their team by keeping team members and their goals visible and in sight, and how to enhance trust among members separated by time and/or distance.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-999afcb9-00007e2fcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Fac/Staff Quick Learn Webinar, “Considering Brave Spaces vs. Safe Spaces in Discussions,” to be Held September 24</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-d77d6a6e-000051d9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, September 24, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - In this workshop, Maureen Fodera of the Office of Undergraduate Education will look at the strategies around building brave spaces versus safe spaces, and what that means in situations when in a learning environment with a group of peers discussing challenging topics. Be sure to &lt;a href="https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/ra1747a7b03fe78c3c1473cd22a444f27"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you’d like to participate!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-d77d6a6e-000051d9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
