<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Dining Halls Point of Sale System Upgrade Coming Soon</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/dining-halls-point-sale-system-upgrade-coming-soon</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Dining will soon be implementing an update to our POS (point of sale) systems across all dining halls. This enhancement will improve our ability to identify meal plan holders during entry by displaying the RPI ID photo for cashiers, resulting in a faster transaction process.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/dining-halls-point-sale-system-upgrade-coming-soon</guid></item><item><title>Tokyo Electron Site Visit | Nov. 12</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/tokyo-electron-site-visit</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD and Tokyo Electron on Wednesday, November 12th for an on-site info session where you can network with Tokyo Electron (TEL) employees, gain insights into their company culture and cutting-edge technologies, and take a guided tour of their facility. Don’t miss this opportunity to explore career possibilities and ask questions in an informal setting. Lunch and transportation will be provided, but space is limited–register in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/tokyo-electron-site-visit</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; Abbott Info Session | Nov. 11</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-abbott-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come learn about Abbott’s Clinical Associates program and discover a career in electrophysiology! Meet with a representative from Abbott on Tuesday, November 11th from 6-7pm–details and registration can be found in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-abbott-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Department of Economics Fall Seminar Series Presents Dr. Stephen Wu on 11/19</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/health-effects-urgent-care-center-entry-case-wellnow-dr-stephen-wu</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Economics is excited to welcome Dr. Stephen Wu, who will be presenting “Health Effects of Urgent Care Center Entry: The Case of WellNow” on Wednesday, November 19 at 3:30 PM in SAGE 5101. We encourage all interested members of the RPI community to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/health-effects-urgent-care-center-entry-case-wellnow-dr-stephen-wu</guid></item><item><title>Fully Funded PhD Student Positions for Fall 2026 in Decision Sciences and Engineering Systems - Info. Session Nov. 7</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/fully-funded-phd-student-positions-fall-2026</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The ISE Dept. is actively recruiting students with a strong background in engineering, mathematics, computer science, or other related fields. We offer fully funded PhD positions in optimization, data science, manufacturing systems, supply chain and logistics. We encourage you to attend our webinar on Nov. 7, 8:30 AM to 9:30 AM EST. All information session attendees will receive an application fee waiver. Webinar registration: https://apply.rpi.edu/register/ISE117&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/fully-funded-phd-student-positions-fall-2026</guid></item><item><title>Resolved: Cable Television Outage in Specific Campus Buildings</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/resolved-cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the campus that the issue affecting CATV services in several buildings–Sage, Troy, Ricketts, and 87Gym–has been resolved. If any continued issues are observed, please file a support request: https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=12539963570701&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/resolved-cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 UGED Buzz Newsletter</title><link>https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-2025-uged-buzz-newsletter</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Undergraduate Education is excited to announce the Fall 2025 UGED Buzz Newsletter which highlights happenings from spring/summer 2025. UGED publishes a newsletter each fall and spring term to our campus community so everyone can hear about the exciting initiatives that are going on within the department. Enjoy reading!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://undergrad.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-2025-uged-buzz-newsletter</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop- Book Discussion-“Powered by Me: From Burned Out to Fully Charged at Work and in Life” – Virtual Class</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-book-discussion-powered-me</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join an instructor-led discussion of Powered by Me: From Burned Out to Fully Charged at Work and in Life by Neha Sangwan (Available in Percipio). Burnout is an energy crisis across five key dimensions—physical, mental, emotional, social, and spiritual. Together, we’ll explore how chronic stress depletes our energy, erodes our relationships, and diminishes our sense of purpose. Through guided conversation and reflection, participants will uncover practical strategies to restore balance,…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-book-discussion-powered-me</guid></item><item><title>Fall 2025 End of Term Course Surveys in HelioCampus: Adding Additional Questions to a Course Section (Faculty/Instructor Training) | Nov. 11</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-0270ca00-00001d96calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 11, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - This webinar offers faculty/instructors of course sections to add additional questions to their student end of term course evaluations. This is an optional process and only needed if instructors wanted to add other questions than what is on the institute course evaluation. Please click the link in the See section to register for the session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:31:29 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-0270ca00-00001d96calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
