<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Co-Term MS in Econ Program: Virtual Info Session on October 1</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/co-term-ms-econ-program-virtual-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us from 4:30pm-5:00pm virtually on October 1 to learn how our STEM-Designated MS in Economics can help you advance your career. We’ll discuss the program structure, funding, and application process. Registration is required.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/co-term-ms-econ-program-virtual-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Apply to Be an RA! (Apply by Oct. 3)</title><link>https://sll.rpi.edu/announcements/be-ra</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Student Living and Learning are now hiring RAs for Spring 2026! The RA Application for the Spring 2026 semester is due October 3rd. &lt;a href="https://rensselaerpolytechnicinstitute.formstack.com/forms/returning_ra_application2026"&gt;Apply here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sll.rpi.edu/announcements/be-ra</guid></item><item><title>Cable Television Outage in Specific Campus Buildings</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings-1</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the campus about an issue affecting CATV services in several buildings: Sage, Troy, Ricketts, and 87Gym. Our service provider has identified the issue–an underground cable–and will implement repairs as soon as possible. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause and appreciate patience as we work toward a resolution. New information will be provided as soon as it becomes available. Thank you for your understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/cable-television-outage-specific-campus-buildings-1</guid></item><item><title>Register for the Investiture of Shekhar Garde</title><link>https://www.rpi.edu/announcements/register-investiture-shekhar-garde</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us November 5 as Dean Shekhar Garde formally assumes the first endowed deanship in RPI’s history, made possible through the generosity of Thomas R. Farino, Jr. ’67 and Patricia E. Farino. Please &lt;a href="https://www.alumni.rpi.edu/s/1225/alumni/index.aspx?sid=1225&amp;amp;gid=1&amp;amp;pgid=10869&amp;amp;cid=24521&amp;amp;ecid=24521"&gt;register online&lt;/a&gt; by Wednesday, October 29.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.rpi.edu/announcements/register-investiture-shekhar-garde</guid></item><item><title>Robust Admission Via Two-Stage Matching under Ranking Uncertainty</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/robust-admission-two-stage-matching-under-ranking-uncertainty</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join ISE for a Colloquium Speaker: Dr. Gustavo Angulo and his seminar on Robust Admission Via Two-Stage Matching under Ranking Uncertainty. Dr. Gustavo Angulo is an associate professor at the Department of Industrial and Systems Engineering of Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile. His research interests are in mixed-integer programming and stochastic programming All Faculty and students are welcome to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/robust-admission-two-stage-matching-under-ranking-uncertainty</guid></item><item><title>2025 RPI Graduate School Expo</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-rpi-graduate-school-expo</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Register for the CCPD’s Graduate School Expo! On Thursday, October 23rd, all students are welcome to interact with graduate schools and learn about their programs. This event will be from 1-4pm in Sage Banquet Hall. Whether you’re actively applying to grad schools, just beginning to consider it, or aren’t sure if it’s the decision you’ll make, this is a great opportunity to meet with graduate school representatives (including RPI!). Learn more, register, and view attending schools in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-rpi-graduate-school-expo</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff Quick Learn Webinar: Considering Brave Spaces vs. Safe Spaces in Discussions | Oct. 9</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-7d5abfae-00005b0ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 9, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - In this workshop we will look at the strategies around building brave spaces versus safe spaces and what that means in situations when in a learning environment with a group of peers discussing challenging topics. Maureen Fodera (Office of Undergraduate Education) will be presenting this workshop. &lt;a href="https://rensselaer.webex.com/weblink/register/r0b2a16caf2576cc8fcf7b9408422a5e3"&gt;Register here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-7d5abfae-00005b0ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Flu Shot Clinic for Faculty &amp; Staff</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/flu-shots-faculty-staff</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Flu Shot Appointments are still available for Friday, October 3 and Wednesday, October 22.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/flu-shots-faculty-staff</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Supervisory Essentials”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-2</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience a “day in the life” of a Supervisor. In addition, the importance of managing employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team capacity will be explored.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-2</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar – “Assigning Learning in Percipio: A Guide for Supervisors”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-assigning-learning-percipio</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This course provides supervisors with a step-by-step overview of how to assign learning content to employees using Percipio. You’ll learn how to search for relevant courses, create and manage assignments, track completion, and support your team’s development goals. Designed to be quick and practical, this session equips you with the tools needed to guide your team’s learning journey effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-assigning-learning-percipio</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: “Connect Through Conversations” Part 2. | Oct. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-bead6c3c-0000046dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 3, 2025 9:00 AM - 11:00 AM - Much of a leader’s work is accomplished through daily conversations with team members and others. These interactions, especially the tough ones, often involve intensely personal feelings (on both sides) that have an impact on the practical outcome of the conversation and the personal connection between the leader and the person. The leader’s level of emotional intelligence—the ability to manage oneself and one’s relationships—is a critical…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0198-bead6c3c-0000046dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review on Friday, October 3 at 12 PM</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-5333387c-00003ee7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 3, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join RPI at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-5333387c-00003ee7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff Quick Learn Webinar - Creating Basic Pivot Tables with Excel for Windows | Oct. 3</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-53028bb4-0000350acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, October 3, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Do you work with data in Excel? Are you always manipulating the content with filters and sorting? If so, taking a look at Pivot Tables in Excel could be beneficial. This workshops will focus on using Pivot Tables in Excel to summarize, filter and group data. Basic functions will be applied as well as a quick look at charts. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:33:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-53028bb4-0000350acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
