<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:34:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Lally Seeking Interest in Multidisciplinary Student Consultancy Club</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/multidisciplinary-student-consultancy-club-interest</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Lally School of Management is looking to support a multidisciplinary student consultancy club that will be open to all RPI students, supported by Lally, and have leadership that includes students in Lally majors. The consultancy’s mission will be to foster and facilitate challenge-based learning through project-oriented management consulting. Please take a moment to complete this &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/yYE5Bia34K8RvgSM6"&gt;form&lt;/a&gt; if you’re interested in taking on such a leadership position!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:34:57 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/announcements/multidisciplinary-student-consultancy-club-interest</guid></item><item><title>Dave Bebb to Lead December 14 EMPAC Tour</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c91944b3-00005dc7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, December 14, 2024 11:00 AM - Join Senior Network Administrator Dave Bebb and tour EMPAC’s advanced capabilities from an information technology perspective! With miles of fiber optic cable linking all four venues as well as the audio and video recording facilities, EMPAC is a phenomenal environment where physical and digital worlds seamlessly intersect on a human scale. There’s always something new to learn and discover!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:34:57 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0191-c91944b3-00005dc7calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Charles Curtis to Play “Nadjorlak” by Éliane Radigue</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0193-8956a2ed-00004b0bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, December 13, 2024 7:00 PM - Composed specifically for internationally acclaimed cellist Charles Curtis and premiered in 2005, French composer Éliane Radigue’s hour-long “Naldjorlak” exists at the instrument’s limits—at the threshold of resonance and its disappearance. Performed in EMPAC Studio 2, with a reception to follow, this performance is a rare opportunity to experience its intensity up-close!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:34:57 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0193-8956a2ed-00004b0bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Dr. Yinan Wang Selected for IBM-RPI FCRC Project</title><link>https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/dr-yinan-wang-selected-ibm-rpi-fcrc-project</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yinan Wang’s proposal, “Model Optimization and Hardware-aware Neural Architecture Search for Spatiotemporal Data Mining,” was selected as a Future of Computing Research Collaboration (FCRC) project, a partnership between RPI and IBM. This research program is focused on developing a comprehensive framework for hardware-aware neural architecture search and model optimization for on-edge spatiotemporal data mining.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:34:57 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ise.rpi.edu/announcements/dr-yinan-wang-selected-ibm-rpi-fcrc-project</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Syllabus Available for Spring ‘25 Term</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-available-spring-25-term</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The HelioCampus syllabus module is available for faculty to access for the spring beginning on December 12, 2024. Per requirements from the Provost’s office, faculty should have their syllabi published by January 20, 2025, two weeks after the start of classes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:34:57 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-available-spring-25-term</guid></item></channel></rss>
