<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Review the Master of Engineering in Mechanical Engineering with Rensselaer at Work | March 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-67049e72-00004fe9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, March 26, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work faculty on a 30-minute information session covering Rensselaer’s online, project-based Master of Engineering program in Mechanical Engineering. Experienced engineers are asked to take on larger and more complex tasks as they progress in their careers, and this program provides the necessary breadth and depth, no matter where one’s career takes them. &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/MECLMARCH26"&gt;Please register&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0195-67049e72-00004fe9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Explore Rensselaer’s Online Graduate Certificate Programs | March 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-66feb2d1-00003556calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, March 20, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for a 30-minute information session showcasing Rensselaer’s full range of online, project-based graduate certificate programs. Each certificate consists of three courses, focuses on developing targeted skill sets, and can be completed in as little as seven months. Please complete the form to RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0195-66feb2d1-00003556calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>March (e-MADNESS) Mercer X Workshops and Seminars</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/march-mercer-x-clubhouse-workshops-and-seminars</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mercer X Affiliated Clubs are offering workshops for any RPI student in March! Upcoming workshops include: R-PI (Raspberry Pi) Day (3/14), Soldering (3/18), MATLAB System Design Workshop (Filters) (3/26) and Ladder Line Antenna Build (3/24). Microelectronics Packaging Seminars are every Thursday. All are held in JEC 6203/6204 and hosted by the Embedded Hardware Club, NSBE, W2SZ Radio Club, Girls Who Code, and IEEE EPS! Contact sawyes@rpi.edu to receive more information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/march-mercer-x-clubhouse-workshops-and-seminars</guid></item><item><title>CBIS: Frontiers in Alzheimer’s Research Seminar Series | March 19</title><link>https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/cbis-dr-michael-wolfe-search-pathogenic-trigger-alzheimers-disease-0319-1-pm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join CBIS and Dr. Michael S. Wolfe for his lecture - In Search of the Pathogenic Trigger of Alzheimer’s Disease on Wednesday March 19th, at 1:00 pm in Bruggeman.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/cbis-dr-michael-wolfe-search-pathogenic-trigger-alzheimers-disease-0319-1-pm</guid></item><item><title>STS Colloquium presents Dr. Sara Black, “Grow food, not prisons!” Innocence and abolition in rural New York</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-presents-dr-sara-black-grow-food-not-prisons-innocence-and-abolition</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Drawing on over 10 years of organizing and scholarship at the intersections of struggles over food, housing, and incarceration in New York, this research presentation mobilizes the concept of “abolition geography” (Gilmore 2023) as an antidote to agendas structured in agrarian innocence. This talk will be held on March 19, at 1pm in Sage 5711.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-presents-dr-sara-black-grow-food-not-prisons-innocence-and-abolition</guid></item><item><title>Sodexo Customer Satisfaction Survey | March 21</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/auxiliary-services/03/17/2025/sodexo-customer-satisfaction-survey</link><description>&lt;p&gt;SODEXO CUSTOMER SATISFACTION SURVEYTell us what would make your dining experience more memorable and you’ll be entered into a drawing for a chance to win a LAPTOP SCREEN EXTENDERHurry, the last day to enter is Friday, March 21st &lt;a href="https://experience.sodexo.com/cgi-bin/qwebcorporate?idx=85YEJY&amp;amp;ACCOUNT_SOFORCE_ID18=0011t00000teIXFAA2&amp;amp;IM_UNIQUELINK=No&amp;amp;uc=2&amp;amp;LType=1"&gt;https://experience.sodexo.com/cgi-bin/qwebcorporate?idx=85YEJY&amp;amp;ACCOUNT_SOFORCE_ID18=0011t00000teIXFAA2&amp;amp;IM_UNIQUELINK=No&amp;amp;uc=2&amp;amp;LType=1&lt;/a&gt; Tags: &lt;a href="https://tags/sodexo-announcement"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/auxiliary-services/03/17/2025/sodexo-customer-satisfaction-survey</guid></item><item><title>RAF Guide to Sponsored Programs Update</title><link>https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/raf-guide-sponsored-programs-update</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RAF has updated the RPI Guide to Sponsored Programs to reflect recommendations resulting from an recent internal audit. Updates were made to Part II, Section 2.2 Research Involving Human Subjects, Animals, and Recombinant DNA and Part IV Proposal Approval Process, to clarify that awards will not be set up until all required campus approvals are received. While this Guide contains helpful guidance, nothing within the Guide to Sponsored Programs should be interpreted as formal institute policy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/raf-guide-sponsored-programs-update</guid></item><item><title>CBIS: Frontiers in Alzheimer’s Research Seminar Series | March 19</title><link>https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/cbis-dr-michael-wolfe-search-pathogenic-trigger-alzheimers-disease-0319-11-am</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to join us on Wednesday in Bruggeman for Dr. Michael S Wolfe seminar. Dr Wolfe works for the Dept of Medicinal Chemistry, University of Kansas.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/cbis-dr-michael-wolfe-search-pathogenic-trigger-alzheimers-disease-0319-11-am</guid></item><item><title>STS Colloquium with Ina Kim - Navigating Unnatural Bodies in Nuclear Ecology | March 20</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-ina-kim</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This talk explores the boundary between normal and abnormal bodies in a world saturated with toxins through ethnographic cases of citizen radiation detection labs in post-nuclear Japan. Ina examines how the concept of a “natural” body is understood and experienced when toxins become normalized by the nation-state, and how varying definitions of abnormality shape the way in which proper care for bodies is understood and provided after nuclear disaster. This will be held at 4pm in Sage 2313.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/sts-colloquium-ina-kim</guid></item><item><title>Doane Stuart Tuition Discount</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/doane-stuart-tuition-discount-rpi-faculty-and-staff</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI faculty and staff, families of educators, medical professionals, first responders, veterans, and non-profit employees enjoy a 10% tuition discount at the Doane Stuart School, a private college preparatory school in Rensselaer, New York. To learn more about what Doane Stuart has to offer, view the Doane Stuart Website or contact Doane Stuart Admissions at admissions@doanestuart.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/doane-stuart-tuition-discount-rpi-faculty-and-staff</guid></item><item><title>Helping Students Learn: Session 2-Making It Stick</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/helping-students-learn-session-2-making-it-stick</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Faculty are invited to participate in the second workshop of the 3-part series, Helping Students Learn. The topic of the second session is Making it Stick: Enhancing Practice and Transfer of New Knowledge and will be led by Eric Burkholder (Auburn University, Engineering Education Researcher). Participants will be able to apply research from cognitive psychology directly to their instructional approach in a way that centers and promotes student learning and success. This series focuses on research-based teaching theories and methods funded by the NSF as part of the MANE RED grant. Session 2:…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:31:27 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/helping-students-learn-session-2-making-it-stick</guid></item></channel></rss>
