<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>NSF 3 Year Graduate Fellowship Information Session to be held Feb. 18th</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019c-1eff0a7e-000063bbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 18, 2026 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - The NSF GRFP provides 3 years of salary and tuition for Masters and PhD students in 30+ STEM fields. Rensselaer students earn this prestigious award every year. Seniors, 1st year grad students (fall 2026) who are U.S. citizens and permanent residents are eligible. Email madige@rpi.edu for information or Register for the virtual session: https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV_6L3FFwv0qCROrvE&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019c-1eff0a7e-000063bbcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>The Office of Graduate Education &amp; Graduate Experience invites you to attend the Graduate Student Cultural Celebration</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-bd17077a-000024e3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, February 24, 2026 5:00 PM - 8:00 PM - Join us for an eventful evening filled with engaging conversations, delectable food, lively music, and exciting games. Take this opportunity to unwind and mingle with your fellow students. REGISTRATION IS REQUIRED.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-bd17077a-000024e3calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>2026-27 Learning Assistant Applications Open!</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-27-learning-assistant-applications-open-0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Apply today to become a Learning Assistant for the 2026-27 Academic Year! Our Learning Assistants (LAs) support RPI’s orientation experiences and host interactive first-year and sophomore workshops and programs throughout the year to help students thrive academically, socially, and personally. Applications are due on February 26th!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/2026-27-learning-assistant-applications-open-0</guid></item><item><title>Success Center Exam Prep.: Physics II &amp; Strengths of Materials</title><link>https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/exam-prep-physics-ii-strengths-materials</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Dates: February 18 Drop-in Sessions in the Success Center, Folsom Library 1st Floor: Physics II - 7-9pm Strength of Materials - 7-9pm&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://successcenter.rpi.edu/announcements/exam-prep-physics-ii-strengths-materials</guid></item><item><title>Frosty February Fling</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c22e423-019c-58f2b793-0000077ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 18, 2026 3:00 PM - 5:00 PM - All Civil, Environmental, and Undeclared Engineering students are invited to this CEE event. Let’s celebrate the half way point of the semester and hopefully say good bye to the frosty weather and welcome the warm sunshine. A great way to catch up with old friends and meet other students. There will be food, fun, and prizes. RSVP to Debbie, rodend3@rpi.edu by 2-17.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c22e423-019c-58f2b793-0000077ccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>ECSE Topical Seminar: “Dissecting 5G in the Wild: Performance, Coverage, and Support for Next-Gen Applications”</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019c-0f1fabd8-00005ab9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, February 19, 2026 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Join us for an ECSE Topical Seminar: “Dissecting 5G in the Wild: Performance, Coverage, and Support for Next-Gen Applications” with Moinak Ghoshal. Abstract and speaker bio can be found at the event URL.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019c-0f1fabd8-00005ab9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Study Abroad Application Portal Open!</title><link>https://isss.rpi.edu/announcements/study-abroad-application-portal-now-open-summer-fall-2026-and-academic-year-2026-2027</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you an undergraduate student who is ready to study abroad? The application portal for summer/fall ’26 &amp;amp; AY ’26-’27 is open! Application deadlines are March 1 for affiliated exchanges and April 1 for non-affiliated study abroad. Visit the Education Abroad website for more information and application instructions: https://isss.rpi.edu/education-abroad/program-information/application-process-and-deadlines. Have questions? Contact Karen Dvorak, Education Abroad Program Manager, dvorak2@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://isss.rpi.edu/announcements/study-abroad-application-portal-now-open-summer-fall-2026-and-academic-year-2026-2027</guid></item><item><title>Division of Finance - The Controller’s Office is Moving!</title><link>https://finance.rpi.edu/announcements/division-finance-controllers-office-moving</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Finance teams that were located downtown in the Proctor’s Building will be moving! Effective February 17, 2026, the Accounting, Accounts Payable, FAST, Payroll, RAF, and Tax teams, will be located in the Troy Building, 5th Floor. Effective on or about March 2, 2026, the Procurement Office will be located at 185 Jordan Rd, Rensselaer Technology Park. Contact information for the teams remains the same. Please contact Debbie Maloney (malond6@rpi.edu, x6426) if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.rpi.edu/announcements/division-finance-controllers-office-moving</guid></item><item><title>STEM-Designated MS in Econ Info Session on 2/18</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/stem-designated-ms-econ-info-session-218</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Discover how our STEM-Designated MS in Economics can help you advance your career. Join us for a virtual information session on 2/18 at 3pm featuring: * An overview of the program structure and areas of focus * Insights into funding opportunities * Guidance on the application process&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/stem-designated-ms-econ-info-session-218</guid></item><item><title>Department of Economics Spring Seminar Series: Dr. Kwabena Bediako</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/department-economics-spring-seminar-series-dr-kwabena-bediako</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join the Department of Economics for a presentation by Dr. Kwabena Bediako (Memorial University of Newfoundland), titled “Exploring climate change mitigation indicators on a global scale: The role of institutional governance” on Wednesday, February 18 at 3:30 PM virtually over Webex.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/department-economics-spring-seminar-series-dr-kwabena-bediako</guid></item><item><title>Kipu Quantum Iskay Optimizer — Onboarding Workshop for RPI Students and Researchers</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/kipu-quantum-iskay-optimizer-onboarding-workshop-rpi-students-and-researchers</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI is in the process of onboarding Kipu Quantum Iskay Optimizer. The solver will be available via the IBM Quantum Qiskit Catalogue in the near future. To help you you with Iskay Optimizer you are invited to a concise, high-impact onboarding workshop to be held: Wednesday, February 18th at 9:30 AM in CII 3206. If your work involves optimization, scheduling, routing, portfolio design, materials discovery, or related areas, this session is for you. Please click in for more details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/kipu-quantum-iskay-optimizer-onboarding-workshop-rpi-students-and-researchers</guid></item><item><title>Coming Soon! Staging Grounds Arts Festival</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2026/staging-grounds</link><description>&lt;p&gt;February 20-28, 2026 staging grounds Arts Festival 2026 is a platform of performances, open installations, and public programs. New commissions by Korakrit Arunanondchai and Jewyo Rhii, with additional artworks by Na Mira, Samson Young, and Li Yi-Fan explore how art, cultural memory, and experience are shaped by structures that re-animate events across time. Festival Korakrit Arunanondchai, Li Yi-Fan, Na Mira, Jewyo Rhii, and Samson Young&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/events/2026/staging-grounds</guid></item><item><title>Mercer X Project Management Q&amp;A Seminar and Hands-on Workshop with Monica Johns (TTM Technologies)</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-x-project-management-qa-seminar-and-hands-workshop-monica-johns-ttm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come to our Mercer X Scrum/Agile Project Management Q&amp;amp;A Session (Friday, February 20th) and/or Hands-on Workshop (Saturday, February 21st) with Monica Johns (TTM Technologies)! We have Sticky notes, Poster paper, a Mercer XLab dynamic workspace, and a veteran project management professional to help organize your projects. Join us for an engaging, hands-on workshop designed to introduce (or deepen) your understanding of Scrum and Agile methodologies from Project Management. BYOP!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-x-project-management-qa-seminar-and-hands-workshop-monica-johns-ttm</guid></item><item><title>Webinar Friday February 20: Webex Application Training</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-february-20-webex-application-training</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on Friday, February 20, from 11am-12pm for a hands-on Webex Training Session, part of the MMS Collaboration Software Training series. This session focuses on the Webex application and its integration with Outlook and Blackboard, so you can efficiently schedule, launch, and manage meetings directly from the tools you use every day. Register now: https://rensselaer.webex.com/webappng/sites/rensselaer/webinar/webinarSeries/register/783d951c6ab8482e9198a7bd6075a700&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webinar-february-20-webex-application-training</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Seminar: Supervisory Essentials</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-4</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, Managers and Supervisors will learn from each other and our Facilitators about important topics such as the Employee Value Proposition and Employee Experience, the six fundamental Leadership competencies at Rensselaer, and experience a “day in the life” of a Supervisor. In addition, the importance of managing employee performance, providing both rewards and recognition, employment law fundamentals and tools for building team capacity will be explored. For more information…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-seminar-supervisory-essentials-4</guid></item><item><title>SoE Spring 2026 Midterm Course Surveys: Adding Additional Questions to a Course Section (Instructor Training)</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c22e423-019c-48414c92-0000190dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 18, 2026 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn how to add additional questions to your School of Engineering Student Survey Midterm. The institute has standard defined questions for the SoE midterm, but if you wanted to add a few questions on top of what is already defined this training is for you. Please click the link in the See section to register.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-9c22e423-019c-48414c92-0000190dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professional Review</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-c276327e-0000320bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, February 18, 2026 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join RPI at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for Professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:31:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9b28bd5c-019b-c276327e-0000320bcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
