<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Applications Now Open for 2024-2025 Barry Goldwater Scholarship</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/23/2024/applications-now-open-2024-2025-barry-goldwater-scholarship</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Established by Congress in 1986 to foster and encourage excellence in science and mathematics, the Barry Goldwater Scholarship and Excellence in Education Foundation runs an educational scholarship program designed to provide opportunities for U.S. undergraduate students with strong academic records and outstanding research potential. The pre-application deadline is Monday, November 25, 2024; the final application deadline for nominated students is Monday, January 20, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/08/23/2024/applications-now-open-2024-2025-barry-goldwater-scholarship</guid></item><item><title>Game Dev Club to Host November Game Jam</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/november-game-jam</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Game Dev Club is hosting its third Game Jam of the semester starting at 5PM Friday, November 15 in Sage 2411! Please join them once again (or for the first time!) for a 48-hour jam, with overnight breaks beginning at 10:00 PM on both Friday and Saturday nights and doors re-opening at 8:00 AM each morning. Teams will be formed to design their own game from scratch; students of all years, areas of study, and experience levels are welcome to participate!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/november-game-jam</guid></item><item><title>Spring 2025 Arch Away Registration to be Held November 20</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-away-registration-arch-2025-be-held-november-20</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have your Spring 2025 Arch Away registered? If you need help discussing your opportunities, reviewing application materials, or discussing other options, stop by the CCPD on November 20 between 1 and 3 PM!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-away-registration-arch-2025-be-held-november-20</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Posts Reminder Regarding Compliance with Campus Email Policy</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-posts-reminder-regarding-compliance-campus-email-policy</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Members of DotCIO’s IT Security team wish to remind all members of the Rensselaer community that Institute policy states that email accounts obtained through third parties may not be used in conducting the business of the Institute, and that ensuring &lt;a href="https://dotcio.rpi.edu/it-security/compliance-rensselaer-email-policy"&gt;compliance with the Rensselaer email policy&lt;/a&gt; is crucial.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-posts-reminder-regarding-compliance-campus-email-policy</guid></item><item><title>BME Seminar Scheduled for November 14</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-e29f20b8-00000dbccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 14, 2024 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - During this seminar, Dr. Faisal Mahmood, Associate Professor of Pathology at Harvard University, will present “Multimodal, Generative and Agentic AI for Pathology.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0192-e29f20b8-00000dbccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Quantum Computing Users Group Monthly Meeting Scheduled for November 13</title><link>https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-monthly-meeting-1</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join students and colleagues interested in quantum computing, or those currently working on the subject, at noon on Wednesday, November 13 in Amos Eaton 214. If you are interested in presenting, please &lt;a href="mailto:morgat5@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Tom Morgan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://idea.rpi.edu/media/quantum-computing-users-group-monthly-meeting-1</guid></item><item><title>TWed Talk, “Intro to Quantum Fourier Transform on the RPI Quantum One,” Scheduled for November 13</title><link>https://tw.rpi.edu/media/twed-talk-intro-quantum-fourier-transforms-rpi-quantum-one-4p-13-nov-winslow-1140</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All are welcome to attend this special TWed Talk as guest speaker Dr. Thomas R. Morgan, Senior Scientist with the Future of Computing Institute (FOCI) at Rensselaer, leads a very applied introduction to quantum computing as he discusses the use of the Qiskit toolkit and Jupyter Notebooks on the FOCI Cluster to evaluate Fourier Transforms using the RPI Quantum One.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://tw.rpi.edu/media/twed-talk-intro-quantum-fourier-transforms-rpi-quantum-one-4p-13-nov-winslow-1140</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Seminar Slated for November 13</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0193-0cada0b4-00007c4ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 13, 2024 12:00 PM - 1:30 PM - The advent of AI foundation models promises transformative advancements in medical applications, an area central to our research. In a presentation titled “AI Foundation Models in Medicine,” Professor Wang will highlight two key developments: Specialty-Oriented Generalist Medical AI (SOGMAI) models and physics-inspired generative AI models for medical imaging.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0193-0cada0b4-00007c4ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>C. Fred Higgs to Speak as Part of MANE Fall Colloquium BLAST Series</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-210fb329-00002a98calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, November 13, 2024 10:30 AM - 11:30 AM - C. Fred Higgs, III, John &amp;amp; Ann Doerr Professor of Mechanical Engineering and Vice Provost of Academic Affairs at Rice University, will present “Balancing Acts: An RPI Mechanical Engineer’s Strain as a University Administrator in the Midst of an Industrial Revolution.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-210fb329-00002a98calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>“Investigating Trigger Mechanisms, Machine Learning, and Bodily Gesture” Coming to EMPAC</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-20f042b5-00002272calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 14, 2024 6:00 PM - Known for experiments with noisy, electronic sculpture and a unique approach to expanded cinema, new media artist Shawné Michaelain Holloway shapes grammars of computer programming and sadomasochism into tools for exposing structures and narratives of power. Attend this free event to learn about recent developments in her current project, which uses interactive cuing technology to transform physical gestures into light, sound, and video in real time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-90e4f2dd-0193-20f042b5-00002272calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Find Out What “The Buzz” is All About!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/10/28/2024/fall-2024-uged-buzz</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Undergraduate Education is excited to announce the Fall 2024 &lt;a href="https://rpi.app.box.com/s/ym9u6zvsnkqymo3dbphj4mdikygnlhrh"&gt;UGED Buzz newsletter&lt;/a&gt;, which highlights happenings from spring/summer 2024. UGED will publish a newsletter each fall and spring term so everyone in the campus community can hear about the exciting initiatives that are going on within the department!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/undergraduate-education/10/28/2024/fall-2024-uged-buzz</guid></item><item><title>Mercer XLab Now Accepting Printed Circuit Board Designs to Prototype Projects</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-now-accepting-printed-circuit-board-designs-prototype-projects</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have a PCB design for a personal project, course project, or research project that you’d like to print out and test within 24 hours before sending it out for manufacturing? The Mercer XLab’s LPKF S104 Milling System, CONTAC S4 Copper Plating System, and Multipress S4 allow them to print multilayer boards, so &lt;a href="mailto:MercerXLab@rpi.edu"&gt;email the lab&lt;/a&gt; to get the request form and help make the lab’s prototyping process more efficient by giving them a chance to print your board!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/mercer-xlab-now-accepting-printed-circuit-board-designs-prototype-projects</guid></item><item><title>November 19 Session to Review Certificates in Analytics, Machine Learning and AI</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9b093649-0000340dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 19, 2024 7:00 PM - 7:30 PM - Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., for a session highlighting Rensselaer’s online, project-based graduate certificate programs in Analytics, Machine Learning and AI. Attendees can expect to learn how data can inform better decisions, and will review an analytic method that can be used regardless of the tools at hand. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/analytics19"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0192-9b093649-0000340dcalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>United Way Holiday Wreath, Poinsettia Sale Open Through November 26</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0193-07d1f8ab-00000d82calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 7, 2024 11:00 AM - Tue , November 26, 2024 11:00 AM - The annual United Way Holiday Wreath and Poinsettia pre-order sale is now open through Tuesday, November 26! You must submit your order form with payment by Tuesday, November 26; pickup will be during the Armory’s community fair/supplier showcase between the hours of 11 a.m. and 2 p.m. on Thursday, December 5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:09 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-90e4dd11-0193-07d1f8ab-00000d82calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
