<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer Community Members Encouraged to Integrate Campus Applications with Single Sign-On</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-community-members-encouraged-integrate-campus-applications-single-sign</link><description>&lt;p&gt;DotCIO strongly encourages the adoption of Single Sign-On (SSO) for all campus-related applications, especially those handling sensitive information. SSO provides centralized visibility and control over client access, making it easier to demonstrate compliance with regulatory requirements such as GDPR, HIPAA, and FERPA.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-community-members-encouraged-integrate-campus-applications-single-sign</guid></item><item><title>Webex Education Connector to Automatically Migrate to Webex LTI Legacy June 2</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-education-connector-automatically-migrate-webex-lti-legacy-june-2</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Multimedia Services would like to inform the Rensselaer community that the Webex Education Connector used to connect Webex and Blackboard will be automatically migrated to Webex LTI Legacy on Sunday, June 2, 2024. Please refer to the “Authorization Error in LMS Webex Education Connector” &lt;a href="https://itssc.rpi.edu/hc/en-us/articles/360058176031-Authorization-Error-in-LMS-Webex-Education-Connector"&gt;ITSSC article&lt;/a&gt; for more information if you need to reauthorize the connection.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/webex-education-connector-automatically-migrate-webex-lti-legacy-june-2</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Information Session Scheduled for June 7</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-3493d0f0-00001b8ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, June 7, 2024 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., will review the online, project-based graduate degrees and certificates, and participants will learn how RPI Instructor Mentors provide industry expertise, advice, and mentorship in a targeted and experiential learning environment. Please &lt;a href="https://apply.rpi.edu/register/general7"&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-3493d0f0-00001b8ecalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Shay Receives IWLCA First Team All-Empire Region Honors</title><link>https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/5/21/womens-lacrosse-shay-receives-iwlca-first-team-all-empire-region-honors.aspx</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Midfielder Megan Shay of the Rensselaer women’s lacrosse team has received first team All-Empire Region accolades from the Intercollegiate Women’s Lacrosse Coaches Association (IWLCA). With this first team all-region nod, Megan is now eligible to be named to a national IWLCA All-American team.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://rpiathletics.com/news/2024/5/21/womens-lacrosse-shay-receives-iwlca-first-team-all-empire-region-honors.aspx</guid></item><item><title>The Rise Of AI Deception In Elections: Deepfakes, Voice Cloning, And Robocalls Pose New Challenges</title><link>https://www.outlookindia.com/elections/the-rise-of-ai-deception-in-elections-deepfakes-voice-cloning-and-robocalls-pose-new-challenges</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Selmer Bringsjord, Director of the AI &amp;amp; Reasoning Lab at Rensselaer, offers brief comments in this article, which appeared in the May 27 online edition of Outlook.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.outlookindia.com/elections/the-rise-of-ai-deception-in-elections-deepfakes-voice-cloning-and-robocalls-pose-new-challenges</guid></item><item><title>How a Tiny Device Could Lead to Big Physics Discoveries and Better Lasers</title><link>https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/28/how-tiny-device-could-lead-big-physics-discoveries-and-better-lasers</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer researchers have fabricated a device no wider than a human hair that will help physicists investigate the fundamental nature of matter and light. Their findings, published in the journal Nature Nanotechnology, could also support the development of more efficient lasers, which are used in fields ranging from medicine to manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.rpi.edu/2024/05/28/how-tiny-device-could-lead-big-physics-discoveries-and-better-lasers</guid></item><item><title>RAF Announces Mary Ellen Mainello’s Retirement</title><link>https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/mary-ellen-mainello-retirement</link><description>&lt;p&gt;After more than 25 years of service at Rensselaer, Mary Ellen Mainello will be retiring on June 30. On behalf of the Institute, the Division of Research Administration and Finance would like to take this opportunity to thank Mary Ellen for everything that she has done for RPI, and in particular for the Research Finance division. Please join RAF in congratulating Mary Ellen and wishing her well in her future endeavors!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://raf.rpi.edu/announcements/mary-ellen-mainello-retirement</guid></item><item><title>SWE to Host “Arch Away Semester Planning with the CCPD” Workshop</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-018f-c09b8c60-00001b29calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, June 5, 2024 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - Worried about landing an internship/co-op for your away semester? Don’t be! The Society of Women Engineers is hosting a workshop on how to explain the Arch program to employers, navigate networking, and use the campus’ career resources to better prepare for your away semester. Don’t miss out on this great opportunity to use Rensselaer’s resources to your advantage!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8f78a55a-018f-c09b8c60-00001b29calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
