<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:32:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Deepak Vashishth Named CEPM Co-Director</title><link>https://president.rpi.edu/announcements/deepak-vashishth-named-cepm-co-director</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Deepak Vashishth, Ph.D., Director of the Shirley Ann Jackson, Ph.D. Center for Biotechnology and Interdisciplinary Studies (CBIS) and Yamada Corporation Chaired Professor of Biomedical Engineering, has been named the RPI Co-Director of the Center for Engineering and Precision Medicine (CEPM) in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:32:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://president.rpi.edu/announcements/deepak-vashishth-named-cepm-co-director</guid></item><item><title>DotCIO Announces Next Phase of AFS Retirement</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-announces-next-phase-afs-retirement</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As previously announced, Andrew File System (AFS), a legacy file storage system, needs to be retired to maintain an acceptable cybersecurity posture for the Institute. The service will be retired in stages and sunsetting completely in September 2024. Among affected services, AFS housed all content for homepages.rpi.edu and dept.rpi.edu. The next stage of this process, access to departmental and personal AFS space (homepages/dept), will be discontinued on June 5, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:32:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/dotcio-announces-next-phase-afs-retirement</guid></item><item><title>Save the Date for This Year’s Annual Lavender Graduation!</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-0767c695-00006753calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 16, 2024 3:00 PM - 4:30 PM - The campus community is welcome to join Rensselaer’s LGBTQ+ Task Force for the 7th Annual Lavender Graduation to help celebrate our LGBTQ+ graduates! Graduating students, please &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/lavgradreg"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; if you plan to attend. The Task Force is also seeking &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/rpilavgradaward23"&gt;nominations&lt;/a&gt; for various student, faculty, and staff awards; nominations are due by 5:00PM on Friday, May 10.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:32:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-8ef2b4fa-018f-0767c695-00006753calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Appointments Now Available at COMM+D!</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/01/16/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you working on a writing assignment, oral presentation, or visual design project? Whether you’re still in the initial brainstorming stages or finishing up your final revisions, the Center for Global Communication+Design can help, so &lt;a href="https://rpi.mywconline.com/"&gt;schedule an appointment&lt;/a&gt; with a member of COMM+D’s trained staff today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:32:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/center-global-communication-and-design/01/16/2024/appointments-are-available-commd-book-online</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff Climate Survey Closes Friday</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-climate-survey-closes-friday</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Faculty and Staff Climate Survey launched by email on April 2, and so far, we have approximately 43% of faculty and staff who have completed the survey, compared to over 70% who completed a similar survey in 2021. Strong participation ensures that Rensselaer is capturing the best possible picture of the university and can track changes over time, so all faculty and staff are encouraged to submit the completely anonymous survey by this Friday, May 10.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:32:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-climate-survey-closes-friday</guid></item><item><title>EMPAC to Host Gameful and Immersive Learning Symposium May 13-14</title><link>https://empac.rpi.edu/research/2024/gameful-and-immersive-learning-symposium</link><description>&lt;p&gt;May 13-14, 2024 – Presented by EMPAC Research, this two-day symposium discusses innovative methods and technologies for teaching, offers invited talks by field experts and panel discussions with your RPI colleagues, and workshops for creating, curating, and facilitating these types of learning experiences. Registration closes May 10, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:32:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://empac.rpi.edu/research/2024/gameful-and-immersive-learning-symposium</guid></item><item><title>TIAA Holding Confidential In-Person Retirement Counseling Sessions May 23</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8bd40c40-018c-4b40ee32-00002cc6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 23, 2024 9:00 AM - 4:00 PM - A TIAA Financial Consultant will be available for one-on-one consultations on a broad range of retirement topics. Attend this upcoming event to help you become better informed and more confident about Rensselaer’s retirement plan benefits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:32:39 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8bd40c40-018c-4b40ee32-00002cc6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
