<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CCPD &amp; M/E Engineering Info Session | Oct. 7</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-me-engineering-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;M/E Engineering will be hosting an info session on-campus on Tuesday, October 7th from 5:30-7:30pm to discuss their available and upcoming opportunities, including positions for December graduates. Join the CCPD in learning more about the company and network with recruiters! Register and learn more in Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-me-engineering-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Reunion &amp; Homecoming 2025 | Oct. 10-12</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10242&amp;cid=23364&amp;ecid=23364&amp;ciid=83503&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for Reunion &amp;amp; Homecoming 2025: October 10-12, where we will celebrate class years ending in 0 or 5! If you’re interested in helping your class or group with planning an event or volunteering for your Reunion class gift committee, visit our “Volunteer” page on the Reunion website or contact &lt;a href="mailto:alumni@rpi.edu"&gt;alumni@rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10242&amp;cid=23364&amp;ecid=23364&amp;ciid=83503&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>New Jersey | Amazon Fulfillment Center Tour | Oct. 22</title><link>https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10796&amp;cid=24386&amp;ecid=24386&amp;ciid=83520&amp;crid=0</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: 10/22/2025 10:45 AM to 2:30 PM Ever wonder how Amazon gets your packages to you so quickly? Here is your chance to go on a behind-the-scenes tour at the Amazon Fulfillment Center in Edison, NJ. Mario Munoz ’07 will lead RPI alumni on a private guided tour and show you in real time how orders are fulfilled. Space is extremely limited, and you can bring only one guest (age 6 or over). We will have lunch nearby after the tour. Please register ASAP so you won’t miss out.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.alumni.rpi.edu?sid=1225&amp;gid=1&amp;pgid=10796&amp;cid=24386&amp;ecid=24386&amp;ciid=83520&amp;crid=0</guid></item><item><title>GE Vernova Site Visit | Oc.t 8</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ge-vernova-site-visit</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, October 8th, the CCPD will be hosting a site visit to GE Vernova’s Schenectady office! Come learn about opportunities and life at GE Vernova and get a glimpse of what this location has to offer. Registration is available in Handshake, but spots are limited–register today! Transportation provided by the CCPD.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ge-vernova-site-visit</guid></item><item><title>BME Seminar Series | Oct. 2</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-83c90eca-000049b6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, October 2, 2025 2:00 PM - 3:00 PM - Associate Professor Giuliano Scarscelli from the University of Maryland talks about Brillouin Microscopy for Cell and Tissue Biomechanics&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-96ac82aa-0197-83c90eca-000049b6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>EARN YOUR Mercer X Skills Badges</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/earn-your-mercer-xlab-skills-badges</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mercer XLab is now offering a chance to earn limited edition Fall 2025 Skills Badges! To improve your Mercer X Skill Set there are three levels to obtain: Level 1 is your learning, Level 2 is applying your learning to a project, and Level 3, the gold standard, is teaching someone else! We offer the opportunity to earn PCB Pro (printing PCB prototypes), PCB Designer, Hot Worker (soldering), Spice-EE (Spice simulation), Instrument Wiz, and IC Designer skills. Earn yours before they run out!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/earn-your-mercer-xlab-skills-badges</guid></item><item><title>Reduce and Reuse: Introducing the Chemical ReUse Program</title><link>https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/reduce-and-reuse-introducing-chemical-reuse-program</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI is committed to reducing chemical waste and promoting responsible resource management across campus. To advance these goals, Environmental Health &amp;amp; Safety (EHS) is launching a Chemical ReUse Program, a new initiative that helps laboratories share surplus chemicals and reduce disposal needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ehs.rpi.edu/announcements/reduce-and-reuse-introducing-chemical-reuse-program</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer Faculty and Staff Webinar: Active Learning Examples to Keep Your Students Engaged | Oct. 8</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-71fc1cea-00005169calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, October 8, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - If you are interested in hearing more about various active learning exercises that you may be able to implement into your course, then this workshop is for you. Please join me to discuss the practice of active learning, the benefits, and some of the more popular active learning exercises. Maureen Fodera (Office of Undergraduate Education) will be presenting this webinar. Please register using the Event URL in the See section of the calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:31:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-71fc1cea-00005169calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item></channel></rss>
