<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:31:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>CCPD Virtual Summer Series: RBC Bearings | May 20</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-virtual-summer-series-rbc-bearings-may-20</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The CCPD’s series of virtual summer info sessions is back! Join us this summer to learn about companies who will be offering internships and co-ops during the 2025-2026 academic year. RBC Bearings is our first employer on May 20, 2025 starting at 4:30 PM! Registration and more info in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:31:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-virtual-summer-series-rbc-bearings-may-20</guid></item><item><title>Horses on ’86 Field! | Every Wednesday</title><link>https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/horses-86-field</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Did we get your attention? Join us for an engaging experience with Genuine Equine! These summer weekly sessions during the Arch Summer feature Assisted Learning for Wellness in the first hour, followed by Expressive Arts in the second hour. Don’t miss out—use the QR code or use the link provided to sign up and be part of this transformative journey!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:31:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/horses-86-field</guid></item><item><title>Rensselaer at Work Review Single Course Enrollment Options | May 16</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5f0a115b-00004e75calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 16, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Dean Aric Krause, Ph.D., will host this Rensselaer at Work information session reviewing the online graduate programs for working professionals and provide course enrollment options to make an immediate impact on one’s work. Participants can also explore courses for developing valuable skills that benefit employee and employer alike. Please register to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:31:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5f0a115b-00004e75calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Computer Science Colloquia - Rajkumar Buyya - Neoteric Frontiers in Cloud and Quantum Computing | May 16</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-7c4380f7-00001c1acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, May 16, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Dr. Rajkumar Buyya is a Redmond Barry Distinguished Professor and Director of the Quantum Cloud Computing and Distributed Systems (qCLOUDS) Laboratory at the University of Melbourne, Australia. He is also serving as the founding CEO of Manjrasoft, a spin-off company of the University, commercializing its innovations in Cloud Computing. For further information on Dr.Buyya, please visit his cyberhome: www.buyya.com Friday, May&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:31:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-7c4380f7-00001c1acalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Summer 2025 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-summer-2025-course-requests-please-read</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Summer 2025 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:31:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-summer-2025-course-requests-please-read</guid></item><item><title>HR CONNECT - Your Wellbeing Matters</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/hr-connect-your-wellbeing-matters</link><description>&lt;p&gt;May is Mental Health Awareness Month—a meaningful time to recognize the importance of work-life balance. At RPI, we are committed to supporting the mental health of our faculty and staff through services that help ease everyday responsibilities and stress so you can focus on the things that really matter to you. Join the Division of Human Resources on Wednesday, May 14 at 1:00 PM as we learn about the services A New England Nanny (ANEN) offers and how they can help you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:31:14 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/hr-connect-your-wellbeing-matters</guid></item></channel></rss>
