<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>November Dining Events!</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/november-dining-events</link><description>&lt;p&gt;November is packed with delicious events and happenings around campus! Come join us at one or all of these fun, festive events!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/november-dining-events</guid></item><item><title>New Minor in Behavioral Data Science</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-behavioral-data-science</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new interdisciplinary minor is now available for students interested in the intersection between data science and human behavior. The Behavioral Data Science minor combines psychological science, statistics, and computational methods to analyze, predict, and influence human behavior across a wide range of real-world contexts. Minor requirements can be found in the RPI catalog. For questions, please contact the School of HASS advising hub at HASSinfo@rpi.edu.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/new-minor-behavioral-data-science</guid></item><item><title>CCPD &amp; Edgewell Personal Care Info Session | Nov. 4</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-edgewell-personal-care-info-session</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CCPD for a virtual info session hosted by 2 RPI alumni now working at Edgewell Personal Care (Schick), on November 4th! They’ll share insights about the company and hybrid co-op opportunities available across several departments. Whether you’re curious about engineering roles, product development, or innovation in personal care, this is a great chance to learn more and connect with fellow Engineers who’ve walked the same campus halls. Register &amp;amp; find the link to join in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ccpd-edgewell-personal-care-info-session</guid></item><item><title>Ask the Experts: Navigating a Job in Software | Nov. 6</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-e816a3bd-00002f23calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, November 6, 2025 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM - Current students are invited to attend a virtual session on getting started with a career in software engineering and development sponsored by the alumni chapter of S. California. Join us and learn what to expect in this career path, the different potential roles (e.g. coding, testing, architecture, project management), and how things are changing. Jeffrey Wen ’13 (Computer &amp;amp; Systems Engineering) and Linjing Wen ’13 (MBA) will lead the…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-e816a3bd-00002f23calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Complete the Rensselaer Dining Customer Satisfaction Survey</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/students-complete-rensselaer-dining-customer-satisfaction-survey</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rensselaer Dining wants to hear from YOU! Share your feedback by completing the Customer Satisfaction Survey by Saturday, November 1st.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/students-complete-rensselaer-dining-customer-satisfaction-survey</guid></item><item><title>NEW DATE: Information Session: 2026 Project RFP: IBM-RPI Future of Computing Research Collaboration (FCRC) Quantum Computing Track</title><link>https://fcrc.rpi.edu/announcements/new-date-information-session-2026-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us via Microsoft Teams on Tuesday, November 4, 2025, 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM (ET) for an Information Session on the Track-4: Accelerate Quantum Computing Research (2026 Projects) RFP. The Future of Computing Research Center (FCRC)—a partnership between RPI and IBM—advances innovation in AI algorithms, hardware-software co-design, semiconductor technologies, and quantum computing. This session will outline research topics of interest, the proposal template, and submission timelines for Track-4…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://fcrc.rpi.edu/announcements/new-date-information-session-2026-project-rfp-ibm-rpi-future-computing-research</guid></item><item><title>Reflections on Waterways Symposium | Nov. 14</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-symposium-explores-art-environment-and-legacy-erie-canal</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The School of Humanities, Arts, and Social Sciences at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI), in collaboration with the Albany Symphony, the New York State Canal Corporation, and the New York Power Authority, will host a symposium titled Reflections on Waterways: Intersections of Arts, Culture, and the Environment in New York on Friday, November 14, 2025, from 9:30 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. in the Center For Biotechnology and Interdisciplinary Studies (CBIS) Auditorium at RPI. The symposium revisits…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-symposium-explores-art-environment-and-legacy-erie-canal</guid></item><item><title>Chemistry Fall 2025 Seminar Series | Nov. 4</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-3176df9b-00002fd9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 4, 2025 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM - Caelin Celani, Intelligence Community Postdoc Fellow at Department of Chemistry and Biochemistry, University of Delaware, will speak on the topic “From Forests to Facets: Using Chemometrics to Uncover Chemical Insights in Field-Portable Spectroscopy, Catalysis, and Conservation Science”.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-019a-3176df9b-00002fd9calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>11/5 Cognitive Science Colloquium - Dr. Brandon Turner</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cognitive-science-colloquium-dr-brandon-turner</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join the Cognitive Science Department in Carnegie 113 on Wednesday, November 5th at noon for a presentation titled “Mechanisms of Selective Attention during Learning” by Dr. Brandon Turner of Ohio State University. Dr. Turner’s research interests include dynamic models of cognition and perceptual decision making, efficient methods for performing likelihood-free and likelihood-informed Bayesian inference, and unifying behavioral and neural explanations of cognition.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/cognitive-science-colloquium-dr-brandon-turner</guid></item><item><title>MSE Seminar: Dr. Takayuki Harada | Nov. 4</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-0cf0c063-00003619calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 4, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM - Metallic delafossites: low-dimensionality and polarity for advanced electronics Takayuki Harada National Institute for Materials Science (NIMS), Japan&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-0cf0c063-00003619calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Halloween Fun with Presidential Pups Easton and Jofa | Oct. 31 | Commons Dining Hall</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-177b884d-000036c1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, October 31, 2025 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM - Come out to see Presidential Pups Easton and Jofa in their Halloween Costumes. Stop by for visit or just say hello on your way in/out for lunch. They will be at the entry vestibule of the Commons Dining Hall from 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Free Candy and Treats&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-98a4f95c-019a-177b884d-000036c1calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Call for Survey Participants - First Generation Faculty &amp; Staff</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/call-survey-participants-first-generation-faculty-staff</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As we prepare for our National First-Generation Student week November 3-7, the Office of Inclusive Excellence invites you to complete this short survey if you are a faculty or staff member who identifies—or has identified—as a first-generation college graduate- (defined as someone whose parent(s)/guardian(s) did not complete a four-year college degree).&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/call-survey-participants-first-generation-faculty-staff</guid></item><item><title>Division of Human Resources Professional Development Workshop: “Leading from Anywhere”</title><link>https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere-111425</link><description>&lt;p&gt;At Rensselaer, we maintain that “leadership” involves a learnable set of actions and behaviors that is available to everyone. Whether it be leading a particular project or initiative, assisting others in overcoming obstacles and capitalizing on opportunities, or catalyzing co-creation with colleagues, Rensselaer community members model leadership every day. In this workshop, participants will explore the tenants that comprise everyday leadership and discuss the behaviors that define leadership…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hr.rpi.edu/announcements/division-human-resources-professional-development-workshop-leading-anywhere-111425</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff: Sign up for Community RAD</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-sign-community-rad</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Faculty and Staff: If you haven’t already signed up for a Community RAD account, now’s a great time to get started and take advantage of the added convenience, flexibility, and savings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-sign-community-rad</guid></item></channel></rss>
