<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:31:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>DotCIO Announces Change to Single Sign-On Process, Effective May 22</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/change-single-sign-process-effective-05222024</link><description>&lt;p&gt;To improve security, DotCIO is releasing a change to the single sign-on process that will become effective as of Wednesday, May 22, 2024. Under this updated process, the initial login page will only prompt users to enter their Username and then click Login; the next page will ask for their password, and to click Login a second time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/change-single-sign-process-effective-05222024</guid></item><item><title>Parking and Transportation Alerts Campus of Sage Avenue Road Closure</title><link>https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/05/20/2024/sage-avenue-road-closure</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The campus community should note that, beginning Wednesday, May 29, a project to repair condensate leaks will involve excavating portions of the Sage Avenue entrance to the academic campus. As a result, Sage Avenue is currently expected to be closed to traffic for three to four week while this work is being done.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://info.rpi.edu/rpi-parking-and-transportation/05/20/2024/sage-avenue-road-closure</guid></item><item><title>Farewell Gathering for Father Larry Rice to be Held May 29</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7cf7b2b6-00007297calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, May 29, 2024 12:00 PM - 2:00 PM - All are welcome to join the Office of the Provost in bidding farewell to Father Larry Rice, who is embarking on a new chapter and extending his support to another community in need after dedicating three years to Rensselaer as its Chaplain. Feel free to stop by the Russell Sage Dining Hall to help honor Father Larry’s contributions and wish him success in his future endeavors!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7cf7b2b6-00007297calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Western Digital Session Part of CCPD’s Virtual Employer Engagement Series</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7c89802e-000038f6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, May 30, 2024 6:30 PM - 7:30 PM - Through August 1, the Center for Career and Professional Development will be offering a virtual employer series every Thursday at 6:30PM that will help students find an away experience. On May 30, Western Digital will recruiting for Fall 2024 internships; interested students should register via Handshake.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-8f78a96a-018f-7c89802e-000038f6calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Reminder to Faculty: Update and Publish Summer Term Course Syllabi in HelioCampus</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/reminder-faculty-update-and-publish-summer-term-course-syllabi-heliocampus</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of the Provost reminds all faculty that they are required to enter and publish their syllabi two weeks after the semester begins; for the summer 2024 semester, that deadline date is June 3. HelioCampus will publish the syllabi automatically on June 10. Those needing help with entering and/or publishing their syllabi can get in-person assistance at 3:00PM on Wednesday, May 29 in Sage 2313; for assistance at other times, &lt;a href="mailto:svirsa2@rpi.edu"&gt;contact Amy Svirsky&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/reminder-faculty-update-and-publish-summer-term-course-syllabi-heliocampus</guid></item></channel></rss>
