<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>New Undergraduate Research Project (URP) and Undergraduate Independent Study (UIS) Registration Process</title><link>https://registrar.rpi.edu/announcements/new-undergraduate-research-project-urp-and-undergraduate-independent-study-uis</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Beginning Fall 2025, undergraduate students will no longer submit physical forms to register for URP and/or UIS courses. Instead, students will register online via the Student Information System (SIS)! For more information on this exciting change, please visit the Office of the Registrar website! https://registrar.rpi.edu/services/course-registration/undergraduate-research-and-independent-study&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://registrar.rpi.edu/announcements/new-undergraduate-research-project-urp-and-undergraduate-independent-study-uis</guid></item><item><title>Department of Defense college student programs information session | April 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0193-92e1f98b-000018bccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 30, 2025 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM - Learn about SMART Scholars and the National Defense Science Engineering Graduate Fellowship which provide funding for undergraduate and graduate students for up to five years. Citizens of the U.S., UK, Canada, Australia, and New Zealand are eligible. For information, email madige@rpi.edu or register at https://surveys.rpi.edu/jfe/form/SV_85M3eKII9idFy5M&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-9364dfac-0193-92e1f98b-000018bccalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>RPI Libraries is here to support you during study days and finals</title><link>https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-here-support-you-during-study-days-and-finals</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Study late at the Folsom Library on reading and study days. We’re open during finals week until 1 am most days. Argo Tea will also have extended hours. Schedule your study breaks! Folsom Library will have crafts, activities, games, and plushie study buddies available. Show off your RPI knowledge in our staff-created Jeopardy game and exchange your answer card for some study candy at the Service Desk. Bring your family in after commencement! We are open on Saturday, 5/10, from 2 pm to 6 pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://library.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-libraries-here-support-you-during-study-days-and-finals</guid></item><item><title>Arch Summer Kick-Off Event | May 19 at 12 PM</title><link>https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/arch-summer-kick-event-may-19-12-2-pm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting at 12PM, you are invited to kick off the Arch Summer featuring a fun BBQ, good company, inflatable obstacle course, and great music by DJ Kev! It’s a perfect opportunity to relax, connect with the community, and celebrate the start of the season together. Be sure to visit the Resource tent, where you can find student support offices and grab some free swag!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://the-arch.rpi.edu/announcements/arch-summer-kick-event-may-19-12-2-pm</guid></item><item><title>Temporary Closure of Portions of Sage Avenue</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/temporary-closure-portions-sage-avenue</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We would like to inform you that essential repairs to a low-pressure condensate line serving our steam and heating systems will require the temporary closure of portions of Sage Avenue. The affected area is located near the Sage Avenue entrance to the academic campus, between the Ricketts Building and the 87’ Gymnasium. This work is scheduled to occur from approximately mid-July through mid-August, with completion planned before the start of the fall semester.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/temporary-closure-portions-sage-avenue</guid></item><item><title>Colorado | New Grad/Young Professional Job Search Strategies (Virtual) | April 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-1626b6d6-000049cacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 30, 2025 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM - Join RPI alumnus, Mark Eagle ’79, for a free 60-minute live webinar designed to equip you with the knowledge and confidence to launch your career. As a C-level executive, startup founder, and technology leader with over 30 years of experience, Mark Eagle has built and grown companies through innovative technology solutions. Mark’s insights come from real-world hiring, leadership, and industry experience, making his guidance practical, no…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-94f1324e-0196-1626b6d6-000049cacalendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>MBA for Professionals Review with Rensselaer at Work | April 30</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5eeeca7a-00003720calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Wednesday, April 30, 2025 12:00 PM - 12:30 PM - Learn to lead from every aspect of an organization with a real-world MBA experience. Prepare to lead the most dynamic and innovative organizations. Engage, involve, motivate, and lead others to reach their fullest potential. Join Rensselaer at Work Dean Aric Krause, Ph. D., as he reviews this innovative project-based, online MBA for professionals program. Please register to receive login details to join this virtual event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-94f1347a-0196-5eeeca7a-00003720calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HelioCampus Syllabus Available for Summer Term April 28</title><link>https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-available-summer-term-april-28</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The HelioCampus syllabus module is available for faculty to access for the summer term beginning on April 28, 2025. Per requirements from the Provost’s office, faculty should have their syllabi published by June 2, 2025, two weeks after the start of classes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:33:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://provost.rpi.edu/announcements/heliocampus-syllabus-available-summer-term-april-28</guid></item></channel></rss>
