<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Mario Kart &amp; Cocoa Break with Lally</title><link>https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/mario-kart-cocoa-break-lally</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Take a break from classes and join students from across campus for an afternoon of Mario Kart, snacks, and hot chocolate in PITTS 4204 (Sa Lounge). Whether you’re racing to win or just here for the cocoa and snacks, it’s the perfect way to relax before finals and connect before the holidays. Wednesday, December 10 | 2–4 p.m. No sign-up needed, just drop in and play!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lally.rpi.edu/engage/news/announcements/mario-kart-cocoa-break-lally</guid></item><item><title>Now Accepting Spring Applications for RPI’s Collegiate Science &amp; Technology Entry Program!</title><link>https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/now-accepting-spring-applications-rpis-collegiate-science-technology-entry-program</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Collegiate Science &amp;amp; Technology Entry Program (CSTEP) is excited to announce that applications for the Spring semester are now open! CSTEP is an academic enrichment program designed to support New York State residents who are economically disadvantaged and pursuing careers in STEM or health-related fields. Apply today by visiting the CSTEP website&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://success.studentlife.rpi.edu/announcements/now-accepting-spring-applications-rpis-collegiate-science-technology-entry-program</guid></item><item><title>Spring 2026 Mercer XLab: Join Our Team!</title><link>https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-2026-mercer-xlab-join-our-team</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mercer XLab is looking for curious individuals passionate about learning, helping others, and making the TECH in PolyTECHnic visible all over campus! Please fill out the Join Our Team Form to be considered for Spring 2026. We offer a collaborative work environment, opportunities to lead, and continuous professional development. Paid positions are available. Curiosity, creativity, and communication are the only requirements for the For-Credit option. All majors are welcome to apply!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mercerxlab.rpi.edu/announcements/spring-2026-mercer-xlab-join-our-team</guid></item><item><title>Gateway Shuttle for Winter Break Sign Ups</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/gateway-shuttle-winter-break-sign-ups</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI’s Department of Parking and Transportation will again offer Gateway shuttle service to the Albany International Airport, Albany Bus Terminal, and Amtrak Train Station for Winter Break. Shuttles depart from the RPI Student Union horseshoe via CDTA bus and RPI Transportation. Deadline to sign up is December 17th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/gateway-shuttle-winter-break-sign-ups</guid></item><item><title>RPI’s Inaugural Festival of Lessons and Carols on Dec 11</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpis-inaugural-festival-lessons-and-carols</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The RPI Concert Choir, with RPI’s Office of Religious and Spiritual Life, will present its inaugural Festival of Lessons and Carols. Following the format of the University of Cambridge’s famous festival, RPI’s program will interweave readings and music that celebrate charity and benevolence. The program will feature the RPI Concert Choir performing music of Durufle, Chesnokov, Rachmaninoff, Brahms and U2 alongside readings by several distinguished surprise guest readers! Admission is free.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/rpis-inaugural-festival-lessons-and-carols</guid></item><item><title>Fall Parking Permits to expire on 12/22/2025</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-parking-permits-expire-12222025</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please note that any Fall semester only parking permits will expire on 12/22/2025. Spring semester only permits will be available starting on 12/23/2025. If you purchased a full year permit, no further action is needed. Continue to park as normal.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/fall-parking-permits-expire-12222025</guid></item><item><title>The Design Lab Showcase welcomes Justin Weinstein from GlobalFoundries!</title><link>https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-showcase-welcomes-guest-speaker-globalfoundries</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Come and hear Justin Weinstein, an alumnus from the Class of 2019, speak about his experiences and the exciting work he is doing at GlobalFoundries. Don’t miss out on this chance to be inspired! We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-showcase-welcomes-guest-speaker-globalfoundries</guid></item><item><title>Design Lab Showcase to be held Wednesday, December 10 from 2:00 - 5:00 P.M.</title><link>https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-will-host-their-design-showcase-wednesday-december-10th-2025-dcc-great</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Design Showcase will be held on Wednesday, December 10th, 2025 from 2:00 to 5:00 p.m. in the DCC Great Hall. Students from multiple engineering disciplines (Computer &amp;amp; Systems, Electrical, Industrial &amp;amp; Management, Materials and Mechanical Engineering) solve real-world design challenges for industry, entrepreneurs and academic/medical partners. Visit the showcase to: Interact with project teams and view their achievements. Learn how students solve complex design challenges. Get inspired by…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://designlab.rpi.edu/announcements/design-lab-will-host-their-design-showcase-wednesday-december-10th-2025-dcc-great</guid></item><item><title>Help Stock the RPI STEP Food Pantry</title><link>https://pre-college.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/help-stock-rpi-step-food-pantry</link><description>&lt;p&gt;RPI STEP is accepting donations to benefit our food pantry, which keeps our students full and focused when they attend programs on campus. Donate $10 or more before Friday, December 12 at 12 noon and you will be offered your choice of apple or pumpkin pie as a sign of our gratitude. Pies will be available for pick up at the J-Building on Dec. 19 &amp;amp; 20! To make a donation, please see the announcement! Monetary donations for the food pantry will be accepted through January 31.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://pre-college.admissions.rpi.edu/announcements/help-stock-rpi-step-food-pantry</guid></item><item><title>Fidelity Confidential Consultation (In Person) | Dec. 12</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-76ca9c63-00002448calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, December 12, 2025 8:00 AM - 4:30 PM - Schedule a confidential consultation to help you become better informed and more confident about your workplace retirement savings plan benefits. To schedule an appointment, call 1-800-642-7131, Monday through Friday, 8:00 am to midnight, or online at https://nb.fidelity.com/public/nbpreloginnav/rpi/microsite/#/tem/meet-with-us&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc5-98a4d199-0199-76ca9c63-00002448calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>Faculty and Staff Appreciation Lunch on December 10th</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-appreciation-lunch-december-10th</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us for a special appreciation lunch as we celebrate the hard work, dedication, and contributions of our incredible faculty and staff. Come enjoy a delicious meal, connect with colleagues, and take a well-deserved break! Price: $6 plus tax&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/faculty-and-staff-appreciation-lunch-december-10th</guid></item></channel></rss>
