<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Morning Mail</title><link>https://morningmail.rpi.edu/</link><description>Stay updated on the latest news and events happening in the RPI community.</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rensselaer Handbook of Student Rights &amp; Responsibilities</title><link>https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-handbook-student-rights-responsibilities</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Review the Rensselaer Handbook of Student Rights &amp;amp; Responsibilities, which outlines important policies, resources, and community expectations that help us maintain a respectful, inclusive, and safe environment for all students.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://doso.rpi.edu/announcements/rensselaer-handbook-student-rights-responsibilities</guid></item><item><title>Information Security Scam</title><link>https://studentexperience.rpi.edu/announcements/information-security-scam</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Please be advised of a recent information security scam involving an individual falsely claiming to be an employee of RPI. This person, who has no affiliation with our Institute, contacted a recent RPI graduate and transferred them to someone posing as an immigration official. The caller then threatened to withhold or revoke the student’s degree and attempted to extort money.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://studentexperience.rpi.edu/announcements/information-security-scam</guid></item><item><title>RPI Capital Region Careers Networking Night | June 25</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-capital-region-careers-networking-night-june-25</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you eager to explore internship, co-op and job opportunities in the Capital Region? Look no further! Join the CCPD for an engaging evening of networking with esteemed local employers representing various industries. On Wednesday, June 25th 2025 from 6 to 8 PM in the Russell Sage Banquet Hall. Register today in Handshake and see all the employers who plan to participate!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/rpi-capital-region-careers-networking-night-june-25</guid></item><item><title>School of Science Arch Field Trip: Utica Zoo | June 21</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-96ac81ec-0197-403ef73b-000055a5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, June 21, 2025 7:30 AM - 7:30 PM - ALL MAJORS WELCOME! Students will explore the Utica Zoo, which exhibits over 140 individual animals representing 64 species. Free breakfast and lunch will be provided. Meet at RPI Union horseshoe entrance at 7:30 AM, bus departure at 8:00 AM. Bus will return to RPI by 7:30 PM. Sign-up ends 4 PM on June 20.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Students</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-96ac81ec-0197-403ef73b-000055a5calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>AI: How We Can Shape Its Impact on the Future of Society, Education, Research, &amp; Work | June 18</title><link>https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ai-how-we-can-shape-its-impact-future-society-education-research-work-june-18</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Victor Peng ’81 is a prominent figure in the semiconductor industry, best known for his leadership at Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) and Xilinx, Inc. Victor will give an informal talk about his career and professional experience in the semiconductor industry and will leave time to take questions. The event will be held in the Troy Building, Room 2012 from 12:30 p.m. – 1:30 p.m. on Wednesday, June 18th. Register in Handshake!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ccpd.rpi.edu/announcements/ai-how-we-can-shape-its-impact-future-society-education-research-work-june-18</guid></item><item><title>2025 National Organic Chemistry Symposium (NOS) June 22-26</title><link>https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-national-organic-chemistry-symposium</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The 49th NOS will be held June 22–26, at RPI! Sponsored by the ACS Division of Organic Chemistry, this 100th-anniversary event is expected to welcome over 450 participants from across the United States &amp;amp; around the world. It will feature top speakers highlighting advances in synthesis, biocatalysis, polymers, and drug discovery. Nobel Laureate Dr. Morton Medhal will give the keynote. The program also includes poster sessions and career panels. More info: https://www.nationalorganicsymposium.org/&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://biotech.rpi.edu/announcements/2025-national-organic-chemistry-symposium</guid></item><item><title>Distinguished Bedford Visiting Professor Seminar - Nic Goldsmith, FAIA, LEED AP | June 20</title><link>https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0197-797d8430-000038c4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Date: Friday, June 20, 2025 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM - “Design and Engineering of Lightweight Structures” Nic Goldsmith, FAIA, LEED AP Founding Director, Lightweight Structures Group, TYLin. Nic Goldsmith has spent his entire professional life in pursuit of efficient structural forms, going back as far as when he started EZ Builders while still a student at Cornell University. After completing a thesis on cold climate membrane mega envelopes in Alaska. Further details provided in the seminar.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://events.rpi.edu/cal/event/eventView.do?b=de&amp;calPath=%2Fpublic%2Fcals%2FMainCal&amp;guid=CAL-00f19cc6-97552ccd-0197-797d8430-000038c4calendars%40rpi.edu&amp;recurrenceId=</guid></item><item><title>HASS Arch Field Trip: Garden Planting and Trail Work in Frear Park | June 19</title><link>https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/hass-arch-field-trip-garden-planting-and-trail-work-frear-park</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us from 10am to 2pm on June 19 in Frear Park to plant native wildflower plants in the native plant gardens. This is open to students of all majors, staff and faculty. This will be followed by a walk on the nature trails in Frear Park. Tools, gloves, lunch, and water will be provided. Students must register on Handshake to join the field trip. Carpooling is recommended. Contact bram@rpi.edu if you need assistance coordinating transportation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hass.rpi.edu/announcements/hass-arch-field-trip-garden-planting-and-trail-work-frear-park</guid></item><item><title>Dining Hours of Operation for Juneteenth</title><link>https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/dining-hours-operation-juneteenth</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In observance of Juneteenth on June 19, 2025, please note the following locations will be closed that day: Russell Sage Dining Hall, DCC Cafe, Argo Tea, Bird n Brine. For a complete list of what is open and hours of operation please visit rpi.sodexomyway.com or follow Rensselaer Dining on social media &lt;span class="citation" data-cites="rensseleardining"&gt;@rensseleardining&lt;/span&gt;. Thank you&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Community</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://administration.rpi.edu/announcements/dining-hours-operation-juneteenth</guid></item><item><title>An Important Notice to All Instructors Regarding LMS Summer 2025 Course Requests</title><link>https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-summer-2025-course-requests-please-read</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Rensselaer Learning Management System (Blackboard Learn SaaS) instructors, designers, and TAs who are planning on having an LMS course site for the Summer 2025 term should note that “Do submit” and “Do not submit” conditionals are still in place for submitting their course requests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For information about sharing your news or events, or to change your subscription settings, visit &lt;a href="http://morningmail.rpi.edu"&gt;morningmail.rpi.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Faculty and Staff</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dotcio.rpi.edu/announcements/lms-summer-2025-course-requests-please-read</guid></item></channel></rss>
